const destinationQuestions = {
    "level 1": [
        {
            "Question": "yengmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "beat",
            "options": [
                "work out",
                "watch out",
                "sort out"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "stol o‘yini",
            "RightAnswer": "board game",
            "options": [
                "a number of",
                "a solution to",
                "an advantage of"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kapitan",
            "RightAnswer": "captain",
            "options": [
                "under pressure",
                "in trouble",
                "in my view"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qiyinchilik, chaqiriq",
            "RightAnswer": "challenge",
            "options": [
                "upset",
                "hurt",
                "get rid of"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chempion",
            "RightAnswer": "champion",
            "options": [
                "captain",
                "under pressure",
                "in trouble"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aldamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "cheat",
            "options": [
                "beat",
                "work out",
                "watch out"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "klassik musiqa",
            "RightAnswer": "classical music",
            "options": [
                "board game",
                "a number of",
                "a solution to"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "klub",
            "RightAnswer": "club",
            "options": [
                "champion",
                "captain",
                "under pressure"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "murabbiy",
            "RightAnswer": "coach",
            "options": [
                "club",
                "champion",
                "captain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "musobaqa",
            "RightAnswer": "competition",
            "options": [
                "coach",
                "club",
                "champion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kontsert",
            "RightAnswer": "concert",
            "options": [
                "competition",
                "coach",
                "club"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mag‘lubiyat, mag‘lub etmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "defeat",
            "options": [
                "challenge",
                "upset",
                "hurt"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qiziqarli",
            "RightAnswer": "entertaining",
            "options": [
                "simple",
                "silent",
                "incorrect"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xalq musiqasi",
            "RightAnswer": "folk music",
            "options": [
                "classical music",
                "board game",
                "a number of"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "guruh",
            "RightAnswer": "group",
            "options": [
                "concert",
                "competition",
                "coach"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sport zali",
            "RightAnswer": "gym",
            "options": [
                "group",
                "concert",
                "competition"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xursandchilik qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "have fun",
            "options": [
                "rely on",
                "insist on",
                "hide sth from sb"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qiziqish, qiziqtirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "interest",
            "options": [
                "defeat",
                "challenge",
                "upset"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "a’zo",
            "RightAnswer": "member",
            "options": [
                "gym",
                "group",
                "concert"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "raqib",
            "RightAnswer": "opponent",
            "options": [
                "member",
                "gym",
                "group"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tashkil qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "organise",
            "options": [
                "cheat",
                "beat",
                "work out"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zavq, huzur",
            "RightAnswer": "pleasure",
            "options": [
                "opponent",
                "member",
                "gym"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hakam",
            "RightAnswer": "referee",
            "options": [
                "pleasure",
                "opponent",
                "member"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ritm",
            "RightAnswer": "rhythm",
            "options": [
                "referee",
                "pleasure",
                "opponent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tavakkal qilmoq, xavf",
            "RightAnswer": "risk",
            "options": [
                "interest",
                "defeat",
                "challenge"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hisob, gol urmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "score",
            "options": [
                "risk",
                "interest",
                "defeat"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo‘llab-quvvatlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "support",
            "options": [
                "score",
                "risk",
                "interest"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jamoa",
            "RightAnswer": "team",
            "options": [
                "rhythm",
                "referee",
                "pleasure"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mashq qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "train",
            "options": [
                "organise",
                "cheat",
                "beat"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "video o‘yin",
            "RightAnswer": "video game",
            "options": [
                "folk music",
                "classical music",
                "board game"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "davom ettirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "carry on",
            "options": [
                "back",
                "boiling",
                "handle"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tashqarida ovqatlanmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "eat out",
            "options": [
                "carry on",
                "back",
                "boiling"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tashlab qo‘ymoq",
            "RightAnswer": "give up",
            "options": [
                "eat out",
                "carry on",
                "go back"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qatnashmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "join in",
            "options": [
                "give up",
                "eat out",
                "carry on"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "(o‘yindan) haydamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "send off",
            "options": [
                "join in",
                "give up",
                "eat out"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boshlamoq (xobbi, sport)",
            "RightAnswer": "take up",
            "options": [
                "send off",
                "join in",
                "give up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ovozni pasaytirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "turn down",
            "options": [
                "take up",
                "send off",
                "join in"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ovozni ko‘tarmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "turn up",
            "options": [
                "turn down",
                "take up",
                "send off"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uzoq vaqt davomida",
            "RightAnswer": "for a long time",
            "options": [
                "luckily",
                "naturally",
                "deeply"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qiziqish uchun",
            "RightAnswer": "for fun",
            "options": [
                "for a long time",
                "luckily",
                "naturally"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o‘rtasida",
            "RightAnswer": "in the middle",
            "options": [
                "for fun",
                "for a long time",
                "luckily"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "vaqtida",
            "RightAnswer": "in time",
            "options": [
                "in the middle",
                "for fun",
                "for a long time"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sahnada",
            "RightAnswer": "on stage",
            "options": [
                "in time",
                "in the middle",
                "for fun"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "harakat",
            "RightAnswer": "action",
            "options": [
                "team",
                "rhythm",
                "referee"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aktyor",
            "RightAnswer": "actor",
            "options": [
                "action",
                "team",
                "rhythm"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sportchi",
            "RightAnswer": "athlete",
            "options": [
                "actor",
                "action",
                "team"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sportga oid",
            "RightAnswer": "athletic",
            "options": [
                "entertaining",
                "silent",
                "incorrect"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bola",
            "RightAnswer": "child",
            "options": [
                "athlete",
                "actor",
                "action"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bolalar",
            "RightAnswer": "children",
            "options": [
                "child",
                "athlete",
                "actor"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bolalik",
            "RightAnswer": "childhood",
            "options": [
                "children",
                "child",
                "athlete"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to‘plamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "collect",
            "options": [
                "train",
                "organise",
                "cheat"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to‘plam",
            "RightAnswer": "collection",
            "options": [
                "childhood",
                "children",
                "child"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kollektor",
            "RightAnswer": "collector",
            "options": [
                "collection",
                "childhood",
                "children"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko‘ngil ochmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "entertain",
            "options": [
                "collect",
                "train",
                "organise"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko‘ngilocharlik",
            "RightAnswer": "entertainment",
            "options": [
                "collector",
                "collection",
                "childhood"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qahramon",
            "RightAnswer": "hero",
            "options": [
                "entertainment",
                "collector",
                "collection"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qahramonlarcha",
            "RightAnswer": "heroic",
            "options": [
                "athletic",
                "entertaining",
                "mental"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qahramon ayol",
            "RightAnswer": "heroine",
            "options": [
                "hero",
                "entertainment",
                "collector"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "musiqa",
            "RightAnswer": "music",
            "options": [
                "heroine",
                "hero",
                "entertainment"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "musiqiy",
            "RightAnswer": "musical",
            "options": [
                "heroic",
                "athletic",
                "entertaining"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "musiqachi",
            "RightAnswer": "musician",
            "options": [
                "music",
                "heroine",
                "hero"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o‘ynash",
            "RightAnswer": "play",
            "options": [
                "entertain",
                "collect",
                "train"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o‘yinchi",
            "RightAnswer": "player",
            "options": [
                "musician",
                "music",
                "heroine"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sho‘x",
            "RightAnswer": "playful",
            "options": [
                "musical",
                "heroic",
                "athletic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "suzmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "sail",
            "options": [
                "play",
                "entertain",
                "collect"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "suzish",
            "RightAnswer": "sailing",
            "options": [
                "player",
                "musician",
                "music"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dengizchi",
            "RightAnswer": "sailor",
            "options": [
                "sailing",
                "player",
                "musician"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kuylamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "sing",
            "options": [
                "sail",
                "play",
                "entertain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo‘shiq",
            "RightAnswer": "song",
            "options": [
                "sailor",
                "sailing",
                "player"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo‘shiqchi",
            "RightAnswer": "singer",
            "options": [
                "song",
                "sailor",
                "sailing"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo‘shiq aytish",
            "RightAnswer": "singing",
            "options": [
                "singer",
                "song",
                "sailor"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zerikkan",
            "RightAnswer": "bored with",
            "options": [
                "preferable",
                "unlucky",
                "lucky"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "juda qiziqqan",
            "RightAnswer": "crazy about",
            "options": [
                "bored with",
                "preferable",
                "unlucky"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yaxshi ko‘radigan",
            "RightAnswer": "good at",
            "options": [
                "crazy about",
                "bored with",
                "preferable"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qiziqqan",
            "RightAnswer": "interested in",
            "options": [
                "good at",
                "crazy about",
                "bored with"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishqiboz",
            "RightAnswer": "keen on",
            "options": [
                "interested in",
                "good at",
                "crazy about"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "orasida mashhur",
            "RightAnswer": "popular with",
            "options": [
                "keen on",
                "interested in",
                "good at"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xohlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "feel like",
            "options": [
                "felt",
                "spoke",
                "forgave"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...ni tinglamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "listen to",
            "options": [
                "feel like",
                "felt",
                "spoke"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...da qatnashmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "take part in",
            "options": [
                "listen to",
                "feel like",
                "felt"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "haqidagi kitob",
            "RightAnswer": "a book about",
            "options": [
                "suggestion",
                "solution",
                "refusal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...ning ishqibozi",
            "RightAnswer": "a fan of",
            "options": [
                "a book about",
                "suggestion",
                "solution"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...ga qarshi o‘yin",
            "RightAnswer": "a game against",
            "options": [
                "a fan of",
                "a book about",
                "suggestion"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 2": [
        {
            "Question": "erishmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "achieve",
            "options": [
                "sing",
                "sail",
                "play"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "miya",
            "RightAnswer": "brain",
            "options": [
                "singing",
                "singer",
                "song"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aqlli",
            "RightAnswer": "clever",
            "options": [
                "playful",
                "musical",
                "heroic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "diqqatni jamlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "concentrate",
            "options": [
                "achieve",
                "sing",
                "sail"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko‘rib chiqmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "consider",
            "options": [
                "concentrate",
                "achieve",
                "sing"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kurs",
            "RightAnswer": "course",
            "options": [
                "brain",
                "singing",
                "singer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "daraja (diplom)",
            "RightAnswer": "degree",
            "options": [
                "course",
                "brain",
                "singing"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tajriba; boshdan kechirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "experience",
            "options": [
                "support",
                "score",
                "risk"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ekspert; tajribali",
            "RightAnswer": "expert",
            "options": [
                "sense of humour",
                "solar system",
                "bank account"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muvaffaqiyatsizlikka uchramoq",
            "RightAnswer": "fail",
            "options": [
                "consider",
                "concentrate",
                "achieve"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taxmin qilmoq; taxmin",
            "RightAnswer": "guess",
            "options": [
                "experience",
                "support",
                "score"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ikkilanmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "hesitate",
            "options": [
                "fail",
                "consider",
                "concentrate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko‘rsatma",
            "RightAnswer": "instruction",
            "options": [
                "degree",
                "course",
                "brain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taraqqiy etmoq, rivojlanmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "make progress",
            "options": [
                "have fun",
                "rely on",
                "insist on"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "amin bo‘lmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "make sure",
            "options": [
                "make progress",
                "have fun",
                "rely on"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "baholamoq; baho",
            "RightAnswer": "mark",
            "options": [
                "guess",
                "experience",
                "support"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aqliy",
            "RightAnswer": "mental",
            "options": [
                "clever",
                "playful",
                "musical"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o‘tmoq (imtihondan)",
            "RightAnswer": "pass",
            "options": [
                "hesitate",
                "fail",
                "consider"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "malaka",
            "RightAnswer": "qualification",
            "options": [
                "instruction",
                "degree",
                "course"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "eslatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "remind",
            "options": [
                "pass",
                "hesitate",
                "fail"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hisobot",
            "RightAnswer": "report",
            "options": [
                "qualification",
                "instruction",
                "degree"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "takrorlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "revise",
            "options": [
                "remind",
                "pass",
                "hesitate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qidirmoq; qidiruv",
            "RightAnswer": "search",
            "options": [
                "mark",
                "guess",
                "experience"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko‘nikma",
            "RightAnswer": "skill",
            "options": [
                "report",
                "qualification",
                "instruction"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aqlli, chiroyli",
            "RightAnswer": "smart",
            "options": [
                "mental",
                "clever",
                "playful"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "fan",
            "RightAnswer": "subject",
            "options": [
                "skill",
                "report",
                "qualification"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "imtihon topshirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "take an exam",
            "options": [
                "make sure",
                "make progress",
                "have fun"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "iqtidorli",
            "RightAnswer": "talented at",
            "options": [
                "popular with",
                "keen on",
                "interested in"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o‘quv davri (semestr)",
            "RightAnswer": "term",
            "options": [
                "subject",
                "skill",
                "report"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hayron qolmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "wonder",
            "options": [
                "revise",
                "remind",
                "pass"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ustidan chizib tashlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "cross out",
            "options": [
                "turn up",
                "turn down",
                "take up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ma’lumot qidirmoq (kitobdan va h.k.)",
            "RightAnswer": "look up",
            "options": [
                "cross out",
                "turn up",
                "turn down"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muhim ma’lumotni aytmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "point out",
            "options": [
                "look up",
                "cross out",
                "turn up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "baland ovozda o‘qib eshittirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "read out",
            "options": [
                "point out",
                "look up",
                "cross out"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yirtib tashlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "rip up",
            "options": [
                "read out",
                "point out",
                "look up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o‘chirg‘ich bilan o‘chirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "rub out",
            "options": [
                "rip up",
                "read out",
                "point out"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ag‘darmoq, aylantirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "turn over",
            "options": [
                "rub out",
                "rip up",
                "read out"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yozib qo‘ymoq",
            "RightAnswer": "write down",
            "options": [
                "turn over",
                "rub out",
                "rip up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yoddan",
            "RightAnswer": "by heart",
            "options": [
                "on stage",
                "in time",
                "in the middle"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "masalan",
            "RightAnswer": "for instance",
            "options": [
                "by heart",
                "on stage",
                "in time"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xulosa qilib",
            "RightAnswer": "in conclusion",
            "options": [
                "for instance",
                "by heart",
                "on stage"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aslida",
            "RightAnswer": "in fact",
            "options": [
                "in conclusion",
                "for instance",
                "by heart"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "foydasiga",
            "RightAnswer": "in favour",
            "options": [
                "in fact",
                "in conclusion",
                "for instance"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "umuman olganda",
            "RightAnswer": "in general",
            "options": [
                "in favour",
                "in fact",
                "in conclusion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boshlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "begin",
            "options": [
                "wonder",
                "revise",
                "remind"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boshlandi",
            "RightAnswer": "began",
            "options": [
                "spoken",
                "forgiven",
                "flown"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boshlangan",
            "RightAnswer": "begun",
            "options": [
                "suggest",
                "solve",
                "refuse"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yangi boshlovchi",
            "RightAnswer": "beginner",
            "options": [
                "term",
                "subject",
                "skill"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boshlanish",
            "RightAnswer": "beginning",
            "options": [
                "beginner",
                "term",
                "subject"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jasur",
            "RightAnswer": "brave",
            "options": [
                "smart",
                "mental",
                "clever"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jasorat",
            "RightAnswer": "bravery",
            "options": [
                "beginning",
                "beginner",
                "term"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to‘g‘ri qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "correct",
            "options": [
                "begin",
                "wonder",
                "revise"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tuzatish",
            "RightAnswer": "correction",
            "options": [
                "bravery",
                "beginning",
                "beginner"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "noto‘g‘ri",
            "RightAnswer": "incorrect",
            "options": [
                "brave",
                "smart",
                "mental"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bo‘lmoq, ajratmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "divide",
            "options": [
                "correct",
                "begin",
                "wonder"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bo‘linish",
            "RightAnswer": "division",
            "options": [
                "correction",
                "bravery",
                "beginning"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ta’lim bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "educate",
            "options": [
                "divide",
                "correct",
                "begin"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ta’lim",
            "RightAnswer": "education",
            "options": [
                "division",
                "correction",
                "bravery"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko‘rsatma bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "instruct",
            "options": [
                "educate",
                "divide",
                "correct"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o‘qituvchi, instruktor",
            "RightAnswer": "instructor",
            "options": [
                "education",
                "division",
                "correction"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xotira",
            "RightAnswer": "memory",
            "options": [
                "instructor",
                "education",
                "division"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yod olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "memorise",
            "options": [
                "instruct",
                "educate",
                "divide"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yodgorlik",
            "RightAnswer": "memorial",
            "options": [
                "memory",
                "instructor",
                "education"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "havola qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "refer",
            "options": [
                "memorise",
                "instruct",
                "educate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "havola",
            "RightAnswer": "reference",
            "options": [
                "memorial",
                "memory",
                "instructor"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sokin, jim",
            "RightAnswer": "silent",
            "options": [
                "incorrect",
                "brave",
                "smart"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jimlik",
            "RightAnswer": "silence",
            "options": [
                "reference",
                "memorial",
                "memory"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sokin tarzda",
            "RightAnswer": "silently",
            "options": [
                "broke, broken",
                "peaceful(ly)",
                "noisy, noisily"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oddiy",
            "RightAnswer": "simple",
            "options": [
                "silent",
                "incorrect",
                "brave"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "soddalashtirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "simplify",
            "options": [
                "refer",
                "memorise",
                "instruct"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "soddalik",
            "RightAnswer": "simplicity",
            "options": [
                "silence",
                "reference",
                "memorial"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qodir",
            "RightAnswer": "capable of",
            "options": [
                "talented at",
                "popular with",
                "keen on"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aldamoq (o‘yinda/imtihonda)",
            "RightAnswer": "cheat at/in",
            "options": [
                "take part in",
                "listen to",
                "feel like"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nimanidir boshqasi bilan adashtirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "confuse sth with",
            "options": [
                "cheat at/in",
                "take part in",
                "listen to"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "davom ettirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "continue with",
            "options": [
                "confuse sth with",
                "cheat at/in",
                "take part in"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uddalamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "cope with",
            "options": [
                "continue with",
                "confuse sth with",
                "cheat at/in"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kimnidir yordam bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "help (sb) with",
            "options": [
                "cope with",
                "continue with",
                "confuse sth with"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "know about",
            "options": [
                "help (sb) with",
                "cope with",
                "continue with"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "haqidagi ma’lumotlarni o‘rganmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "learn about",
            "options": [
                "know about",
                "help (sb) with",
                "cope with"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muvaffaqiyat qozonmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "succeed in",
            "options": [
                "learn about",
                "know about",
                "help (sb) with"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "... haqidagi fikr",
            "RightAnswer": "an opinion about/of",
            "options": [
                "a game against",
                "a fan of",
                "a book about"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "... haqidagi savol",
            "RightAnswer": "a question about",
            "options": [
                "an opinion about/of",
                "a game against",
                "a fan of"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 3": [
        {
            "Question": "chet elda",
            "RightAnswer": "abroad",
            "options": [
                "silently",
                "broke, broken",
                "peaceful(ly)"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "turar joy",
            "RightAnswer": "accommodation",
            "options": [
                "simplicity",
                "silence",
                "reference"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bron qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "book",
            "options": [
                "simplify",
                "refer",
                "memorise"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tanaffus",
            "RightAnswer": "break",
            "options": [
                "accommodation",
                "simplicity",
                "silence"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bekor qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "cancel",
            "options": [
                "book",
                "simplify",
                "refer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ushlamoq (transportga yetib olish)",
            "RightAnswer": "catch",
            "options": [
                "cancel",
                "book",
                "simplify"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "avtobus (katta qulay)",
            "RightAnswer": "coach",
            "options": [
                "break",
                "accommodation",
                "simplicity"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qulay",
            "RightAnswer": "convenient",
            "options": [
                "simple",
                "silent",
                "incorrect"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "avariya qilmoq; avariya",
            "RightAnswer": "crash",
            "options": [
                "search",
                "mark",
                "guess"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "gavjum",
            "RightAnswer": "crowded",
            "options": [
                "convenient",
                "simple",
                "silent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dengiz sayohati",
            "RightAnswer": "cruise",
            "options": [
                "coach",
                "break",
                "accommodation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kechiktirmoq; kechikish",
            "RightAnswer": "delay",
            "options": [
                "crash",
                "search",
                "mark"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "manzil",
            "RightAnswer": "destination",
            "options": [
                "cruise",
                "coach",
                "break"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "parom",
            "RightAnswer": "ferry",
            "options": [
                "destination",
                "cruise",
                "coach"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "parvoz",
            "RightAnswer": "flight",
            "options": [
                "ferry",
                "destination",
                "cruise"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chet ellik",
            "RightAnswer": "foreign",
            "options": [
                "crowded",
                "convenient",
                "simple"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "port, bandargoh",
            "RightAnswer": "harbour",
            "options": [
                "flight",
                "ferry",
                "destination"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sayohat, safar",
            "RightAnswer": "journey",
            "options": [
                "harbour",
                "flight",
                "ferry"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bagaj",
            "RightAnswer": "luggage",
            "options": [
                "journey",
                "harbour",
                "flight"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yaqin; yaqin joyda",
            "RightAnswer": "nearby",
            "options": [
                "sure about/of",
                "tired of",
                "surprised at/by"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chamadon yig‘moq",
            "RightAnswer": "pack",
            "options": [
                "catch",
                "cancel",
                "book"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "pasport",
            "RightAnswer": "passport",
            "options": [
                "luggage",
                "journey",
                "harbour"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "platforma (poyezd bekati uchun)",
            "RightAnswer": "platform",
            "options": [
                "passport",
                "luggage",
                "journey"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jamoat transporti",
            "RightAnswer": "public transport",
            "options": [
                "video game",
                "folk music",
                "classical music"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yetib bormoq",
            "RightAnswer": "arrive at/in",
            "options": [
                "write down",
                "turn over",
                "rub out"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "(mashinaga) kirib o‘tirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "get in(to)",
            "options": [
                "arrive at/in",
                "write down",
                "turn over"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "avtobus/poyezddan tushmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "get off",
            "options": [
                "get in(to)",
                "arrive at/in",
                "write down"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "avtobus/poyezdga chiqmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "get on(to)",
            "options": [
                "get off",
                "get in(to)",
                "arrive at/in"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mashinadan/binodan chiqmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "get out",
            "options": [
                "get on(to)",
                "get off",
                "get in(to)"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ketmoq (biror joydan)",
            "RightAnswer": "go away",
            "options": [
                "get out",
                "get on(to)",
                "get off"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qaytib bormoq",
            "RightAnswer": "go back (to)",
            "options": [
                "go away",
                "get out",
                "get on(to)"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sayohat boshlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "set off",
            "options": [
                "go back (to)",
                "go away",
                "get out"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "(samolyot) havoga ko‘tarilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "take off",
            "options": [
                "set off",
                "go back (to)",
                "go away"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bortda",
            "RightAnswer": "on board",
            "options": [
                "in general",
                "in favour",
                "in fact"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "piyoda",
            "RightAnswer": "on foot",
            "options": [
                "on board",
                "in general",
                "in favour"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ta’til vaqtida",
            "RightAnswer": "on holiday",
            "options": [
                "on foot",
                "on board",
                "in general"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jadval bo‘yicha",
            "RightAnswer": "on schedule",
            "options": [
                "on holiday",
                "on foot",
                "on board"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qirg‘oqda",
            "RightAnswer": "on the coast",
            "options": [
                "on schedule",
                "on holiday",
                "on foot"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jalb qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "attract",
            "options": [
                "pack",
                "catch",
                "cancel"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jozibali",
            "RightAnswer": "attractive",
            "options": [
                "foreign",
                "crowded",
                "convenient"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "diqqatga sazovor joy",
            "RightAnswer": "attraction",
            "options": [
                "platform",
                "passport",
                "luggage"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "orqaga",
            "RightAnswer": "back",
            "options": [
                "boiling",
                "handle",
                "routine"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "orqaga qarab",
            "RightAnswer": "backwards",
            "options": [
                "abroad",
                "silently",
                "broke, broken"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tanlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "choose",
            "options": [
                "attract",
                "pack",
                "catch"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tanladi",
            "RightAnswer": "chose",
            "options": [
                "began",
                "spoken",
                "forgiven"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tanlangan",
            "RightAnswer": "chosen",
            "options": [
                "begun",
                "suggest",
                "solve"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tanlov",
            "RightAnswer": "choice",
            "options": [
                "attraction",
                "platform",
                "passport"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tasalli bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "comfort",
            "options": [
                "choose",
                "attract",
                "pack"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "(no)qulay",
            "RightAnswer": "(un)comfortable",
            "options": [
                "attractive",
                "foreign",
                "crowded"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jo‘nab ketmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "depart",
            "options": [
                "comfort",
                "choose",
                "attract"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jo‘nab ketish",
            "RightAnswer": "departure",
            "options": [
                "choice",
                "attraction",
                "platform"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yo‘naltirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "direct",
            "options": [
                "depart",
                "comfort",
                "choose"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yo‘nalish",
            "RightAnswer": "direction",
            "options": [
                "departure",
                "choice",
                "attraction"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "haydamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "drive",
            "options": [
                "direct",
                "depart",
                "comfort"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "haydadi",
            "RightAnswer": "drove",
            "options": [
                "chose",
                "began",
                "spoken"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "haydalgan",
            "RightAnswer": "driven",
            "options": [
                "chosen",
                "begun",
                "suggest"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "haydovchi",
            "RightAnswer": "driver",
            "options": [
                "direction",
                "departure",
                "choice"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uchmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "fly",
            "options": [
                "drive",
                "direct",
                "depart"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uchdi",
            "RightAnswer": "flew",
            "options": [
                "drove",
                "chose",
                "began"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uchib ketgan",
            "RightAnswer": "flown",
            "options": [
                "driven",
                "chosen",
                "begun"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sayohat qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "travel",
            "options": [
                "fly",
                "drive",
                "direct"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sayohatchi",
            "RightAnswer": "traveller",
            "options": [
                "driver",
                "direction",
                "departure"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tashrif buyurmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "visit",
            "options": [
                "travel",
                "fly",
                "drive"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mehmon, tashrif buyuruvchi",
            "RightAnswer": "visitor",
            "options": [
                "traveller",
                "driver",
                "direction"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yaqin",
            "RightAnswer": "close to",
            "options": [
                "capable of",
                "talented at",
                "popular with"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mashhur (nimadir bilan)",
            "RightAnswer": "famous for",
            "options": [
                "close to",
                "capable of",
                "talented at"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uzoq",
            "RightAnswer": "far from",
            "options": [
                "famous for",
                "close to",
                "capable of"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kech qolgan",
            "RightAnswer": "late for",
            "options": [
                "far from",
                "famous for",
                "close to"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mos",
            "RightAnswer": "suitable for",
            "options": [
                "late for",
                "far from",
                "famous for"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "(kimdandir) haqida so‘ramoq",
            "RightAnswer": "ask (sb) about",
            "options": [
                "succeed in",
                "learn about",
                "know about"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "so‘ramoq",
            "RightAnswer": "ask for",
            "options": [
                "ask (sb) about",
                "succeed in",
                "learn about"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qaramoq",
            "RightAnswer": "look at",
            "options": [
                "ask for",
                "ask (sb) about",
                "succeed in"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tayyorlanmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "prepare for",
            "options": [
                "look at",
                "ask for",
                "ask (sb) about"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kimnidir ta’minlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "provide sb with",
            "options": [
                "prepare for",
                "look at",
                "ask for"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kutmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "wait for",
            "options": [
                "provide sb with",
                "prepare for",
                "look at"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 4": [
        {
            "Question": "uzr so‘ramoq",
            "RightAnswer": "apologise",
            "options": [
                "visit",
                "travel",
                "fly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yigiti",
            "RightAnswer": "boyfriend",
            "options": [
                "visitor",
                "traveller",
                "driver"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yaqin",
            "RightAnswer": "close",
            "options": [
                "(un)comfortable",
                "attractive",
                "foreign"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishonchli",
            "RightAnswer": "confident",
            "options": [
                "close",
                "(un)comfortable",
                "attractive"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zamonaviy, salqin",
            "RightAnswer": "cool",
            "options": [
                "confident",
                "close",
                "(un)comfortable"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "juftlik",
            "RightAnswer": "couple",
            "options": [
                "boyfriend",
                "visitor",
                "traveller"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bezamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "decorate",
            "options": [
                "apologise",
                "visit",
                "travel"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "himoya qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "defend",
            "options": [
                "decorate",
                "apologise",
                "visit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ajrashgan",
            "RightAnswer": "divorced",
            "options": [
                "cool",
                "confident",
                "close"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kvartira",
            "RightAnswer": "flat",
            "options": [
                "couple",
                "boyfriend",
                "visitor"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "saxiy",
            "RightAnswer": "generous",
            "options": [
                "divorced",
                "cool",
                "confident"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qizi (qiz do‘st)",
            "RightAnswer": "girlfriend",
            "options": [
                "flat",
                "couple",
                "boyfriend"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "minnatdor",
            "RightAnswer": "grateful",
            "options": [
                "generous",
                "divorced",
                "cool"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mehmon",
            "RightAnswer": "guest",
            "options": [
                "girlfriend",
                "flat",
                "couple"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mustaqil",
            "RightAnswer": "independent",
            "options": [
                "grateful",
                "generous",
                "divorced"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tanishtirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "introduce",
            "options": [
                "defend",
                "decorate",
                "apologise"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mehribon",
            "RightAnswer": "kind to",
            "options": [
                "suitable for",
                "late for",
                "far from"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sodiq",
            "RightAnswer": "loyal",
            "options": [
                "independent",
                "grateful",
                "generous"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kayfiyat",
            "RightAnswer": "mood",
            "options": [
                "guest",
                "girlfriend",
                "flat"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo‘shnichilik hududi",
            "RightAnswer": "neighbourhood",
            "options": [
                "mood",
                "guest",
                "girlfriend"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oddiy",
            "RightAnswer": "ordinary",
            "options": [
                "loyal",
                "independent",
                "grateful"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sabrli",
            "RightAnswer": "patient",
            "options": [
                "ordinary",
                "loyal",
                "independent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shaxsiy",
            "RightAnswer": "personal",
            "options": [
                "patient",
                "ordinary",
                "loyal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tanimoq",
            "RightAnswer": "recognise",
            "options": [
                "introduce",
                "defend",
                "decorate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "munosabat",
            "RightAnswer": "relation",
            "options": [
                "neighbourhood",
                "mood",
                "guest"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ijaraga olmoq; ijara",
            "RightAnswer": "rent",
            "options": [
                "delay",
                "crash",
                "search"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hurmat qilmoq; hurmat",
            "RightAnswer": "respect",
            "options": [
                "rent",
                "delay",
                "crash"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yolg‘iz, beva",
            "RightAnswer": "single",
            "options": [
                "personal",
                "patient",
                "ordinary"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "begona",
            "RightAnswer": "stranger",
            "options": [
                "relation",
                "neighbourhood",
                "mood"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishonmoq; ishonch",
            "RightAnswer": "trust",
            "options": [
                "respect",
                "rent",
                "delay"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bolani katta qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "bring up",
            "options": [
                "take off",
                "set off",
                "go back (to)"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "urushib qolmoq, do‘stlikni buzmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "fall out (with)",
            "options": [
                "bring up",
                "take off",
                "set off"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yaxshi munosabatda bo‘lmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "get on (with)",
            "options": [
                "fall out (with)",
                "bring up",
                "take off"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qiz/o‘g‘il do‘sti bo‘lmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "go out with",
            "options": [
                "get on (with)",
                "fall out (with)",
                "bring up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ulg‘aymoq",
            "RightAnswer": "grow up",
            "options": [
                "go out with",
                "get on (with)",
                "fall out (with)"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko‘nglini qoldirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "let down",
            "options": [
                "grow up",
                "go out with",
                "get on (with)"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "g‘amxo‘rlik qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "care",
            "options": [
                "recognise",
                "introduce",
                "defend"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ajrashmoq, munosabatni tugatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "split up",
            "options": [
                "let down",
                "grow up",
                "go out with"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o‘zing",
            "RightAnswer": "on your own",
            "options": [
                "on the coast",
                "on schedule",
                "on holiday"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o‘xshashlik",
            "RightAnswer": "in common (with)",
            "options": [
                "on your own",
                "on the coast",
                "on schedule"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aloqada",
            "RightAnswer": "in contact (with)",
            "options": [
                "in common (with)",
                "on your own",
                "on the coast"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yaxshi ko‘rgan",
            "RightAnswer": "in love (with)",
            "options": [
                "in contact (with)",
                "in common (with)",
                "on your own"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ataylab",
            "RightAnswer": "on purpose",
            "options": [
                "in love (with)",
                "in contact (with)",
                "in common (with)"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qodir",
            "RightAnswer": "able",
            "options": [
                "single",
                "personal",
                "patient"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qobiliyat",
            "RightAnswer": "ability",
            "options": [
                "stranger",
                "relation",
                "neighbourhood"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nogiron",
            "RightAnswer": "disabled",
            "options": [
                "able",
                "single",
                "personal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qodir emas",
            "RightAnswer": "unable",
            "options": [
                "disabled",
                "able",
                "single"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qoyil qolmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "admire",
            "options": [
                "care",
                "recognise",
                "introduce"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qoyil qolish",
            "RightAnswer": "admiration",
            "options": [
                "ability",
                "stranger",
                "relation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ehtiyotkor",
            "RightAnswer": "careful",
            "options": [
                "unable",
                "disabled",
                "able"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "beparvo",
            "RightAnswer": "careless",
            "options": [
                "careful",
                "unable",
                "disabled"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishonch",
            "RightAnswer": "confidence",
            "options": [
                "admiration",
                "ability",
                "stranger"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kechirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "forgive",
            "options": [
                "admire",
                "care",
                "recognise"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kechirdi",
            "RightAnswer": "forgave",
            "options": [
                "flew",
                "drove",
                "chose"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kechirilgan",
            "RightAnswer": "forgiven",
            "options": [
                "flown",
                "driven",
                "chosen"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kechirim",
            "RightAnswer": "forgiveness",
            "options": [
                "confidence",
                "admiration",
                "ability"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "halol",
            "RightAnswer": "honest",
            "options": [
                "careless",
                "careful",
                "unable"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "insofsiz",
            "RightAnswer": "dishonest",
            "options": [
                "honest",
                "careless",
                "careful"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "halollik",
            "RightAnswer": "honesty",
            "options": [
                "forgiveness",
                "confidence",
                "admiration"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tanishtirish",
            "RightAnswer": "introduction",
            "options": [
                "honesty",
                "forgiveness",
                "confidence"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yolg‘on gapirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "lie",
            "options": [
                "forgive",
                "admire",
                "care"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yolg‘onchi",
            "RightAnswer": "liar",
            "options": [
                "introduction",
                "honesty",
                "forgiveness"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yolg‘on gapirish",
            "RightAnswer": "lying",
            "options": [
                "liar",
                "introduction",
                "honesty"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "inson",
            "RightAnswer": "person",
            "options": [
                "lying",
                "liar",
                "introduction"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shaxsiyat",
            "RightAnswer": "personality",
            "options": [
                "person",
                "lying",
                "liar"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aloqador bo‘lmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "relate",
            "options": [
                "lie",
                "forgive",
                "admire"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qarindosh",
            "RightAnswer": "relative",
            "options": [
                "personality",
                "person",
                "lying"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "munosabatlar",
            "RightAnswer": "relationship",
            "options": [
                "relative",
                "personality",
                "person"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yaxshi ko‘radigan",
            "RightAnswer": "fond of",
            "options": [
                "kind to",
                "suitable for",
                "late for"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rashk qiladigan",
            "RightAnswer": "jealous of",
            "options": [
                "fond of",
                "kind to",
                "suitable for"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "turmush qurgan",
            "RightAnswer": "married to",
            "options": [
                "jealous of",
                "fond of",
                "kind to"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "faxrlanadigan",
            "RightAnswer": "proud of",
            "options": [
                "married to",
                "jealous of",
                "fond of"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kimnidir uchun hurmat qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "admire sb for",
            "options": [
                "wait for",
                "provide sb with",
                "prepare for"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "... uchun uzr so‘ramoq",
            "RightAnswer": "apologise (to sb) for",
            "options": [
                "admire sb for",
                "wait for",
                "provide sb with"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "... haqida bahslashmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "argue (with sb) about",
            "options": [
                "apologise (to sb) for",
                "admire sb for",
                "wait for"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ahamiyat bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "care about",
            "options": [
                "argue (with sb) about",
                "apologise (to sb) for",
                "admire sb for"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "... haqida gaplashmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "chat (to sb) about",
            "options": [
                "care about",
                "argue (with sb) about",
                "apologise (to sb) for"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "(kim bilandir) haqida bahs",
            "RightAnswer": "an argument (with sb) about",
            "options": [
                "a question about",
                "an opinion about/of",
                "a game against"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "... bilan munosabat",
            "RightAnswer": "a relationship with",
            "options": [
                "an argument (with sb) about",
                "a question about",
                "an opinion about/of"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 5": [
        {
            "Question": "reklama",
            "RightAnswer": "advertisement",
            "options": [
                "relationship",
                "relative",
                "personality"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qurbi yetmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "afford",
            "options": [
                "relate",
                "lie",
                "forgive"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "savdolashuv",
            "RightAnswer": "bargain",
            "options": [
                "advertisement",
                "relationship",
                "relative"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "brend",
            "RightAnswer": "brand",
            "options": [
                "bargain",
                "advertisement",
                "relationship"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "katalog",
            "RightAnswer": "catalogue",
            "options": [
                "brand",
                "bargain",
                "advertisement"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qaytim pul",
            "RightAnswer": "change",
            "options": [
                "catalogue",
                "brand",
                "bargain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tanga",
            "RightAnswer": "coin",
            "options": [
                "change",
                "catalogue",
                "brand"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "narx; narxga tushmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "cost",
            "options": [
                "trust",
                "respect",
                "rent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xaridor",
            "RightAnswer": "customer",
            "options": [
                "coin",
                "change",
                "catalogue"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qarz",
            "RightAnswer": "debt",
            "options": [
                "customer",
                "coin",
                "change"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "talab qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "require",
            "options": [
                "afford",
                "relate",
                "lie"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "eksport qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "export",
            "options": [
                "require",
                "afford",
                "relate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to‘lov",
            "RightAnswer": "fee",
            "options": [
                "debt",
                "customer",
                "coin"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boylik",
            "RightAnswer": "fortune",
            "options": [
                "fee",
                "debt",
                "customer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "import qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "import",
            "options": [
                "export",
                "require",
                "afford"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "investitsiya qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "invest",
            "options": [
                "import",
                "export",
                "require"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo‘lga kiritmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "obtain",
            "options": [
                "invest",
                "import",
                "export"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qarz bo‘lmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "owe",
            "options": [
                "obtain",
                "invest",
                "import"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "egalik qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "own",
            "options": [
                "owe",
                "obtain",
                "invest"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "foyda",
            "RightAnswer": "profit",
            "options": [
                "fortune",
                "fee",
                "debt"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mulk",
            "RightAnswer": "property",
            "options": [
                "profit",
                "fortune",
                "fee"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xarid qilmoq; xarid",
            "RightAnswer": "purchase",
            "options": [
                "cost",
                "trust",
                "respect"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chek",
            "RightAnswer": "receipt",
            "options": [
                "property",
                "profit",
                "fortune"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sotuv",
            "RightAnswer": "sale",
            "options": [
                "receipt",
                "property",
                "profit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tejamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "save",
            "options": [
                "own",
                "owe",
                "obtain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tanlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "select",
            "options": [
                "save",
                "own",
                "owe"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yetkazib bermoq; ta’minot",
            "RightAnswer": "supply",
            "options": [
                "purchase",
                "cost",
                "trust"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xilma-xillik",
            "RightAnswer": "variety",
            "options": [
                "sale",
                "receipt",
                "property"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "isrof qilmoq; isrof",
            "RightAnswer": "waste",
            "options": [
                "supply",
                "purchase",
                "cost"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hisoblab chiqmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "add up",
            "options": [
                "split up",
                "let down",
                "grow up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qaytib kelmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "come back (from)",
            "options": [
                "add up",
                "split up",
                "let down"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bepul berib yubormoq",
            "RightAnswer": "give away",
            "options": [
                "come back (from)",
                "add up",
                "split up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shoshilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "hurry up",
            "options": [
                "give away",
                "come back (from)",
                "add up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qaytarib bermoq (qarzni)",
            "RightAnswer": "pay back",
            "options": [
                "hurry up",
                "give away",
                "come back (from)"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "(nimadir uchun) pul yig‘moq",
            "RightAnswer": "save up",
            "options": [
                "pay back",
                "hurry up",
                "give away"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qaytarib joyiga qo‘ymoq",
            "RightAnswer": "take back",
            "options": [
                "save up",
                "pay back",
                "hurry up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yuqoridan olib tushirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "take down",
            "options": [
                "take back",
                "save up",
                "pay back"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kredit kartasi/chek orqali",
            "RightAnswer": "by credit card/cheque",
            "options": [
                "on purpose",
                "in love (with)",
                "in contact (with)"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ijaraga",
            "RightAnswer": "for rent",
            "options": [
                "by credit card/cheque",
                "on purpose",
                "in love (with)"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sotuvga",
            "RightAnswer": "for sale",
            "options": [
                "for rent",
                "by credit card/cheque",
                "on purpose"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "naqd pulda",
            "RightAnswer": "in cash",
            "options": [
                "for sale",
                "for rent",
                "by credit card/cheque"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qarzda",
            "RightAnswer": "in debt",
            "options": [
                "in cash",
                "for sale",
                "for rent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yaxshi/yomon holatda",
            "RightAnswer": "in good condition",
            "options": [
                "in debt",
                "in cash",
                "for sale"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo‘shmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "add",
            "options": [
                "select",
                "save",
                "own"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo‘shimcha",
            "RightAnswer": "addition",
            "options": [
                "variety",
                "sale",
                "receipt"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qurbi yetadigan",
            "RightAnswer": "affordable",
            "options": [
                "dishonest",
                "honest",
                "careless"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taqqoslamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "compare sth to",
            "options": [
                "add",
                "select",
                "save"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taqqoslash",
            "RightAnswer": "comparison",
            "options": [
                "addition",
                "variety",
                "sale"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qaror qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "decide on",
            "options": [
                "compare sth to",
                "add",
                "select"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qaror",
            "RightAnswer": "decision",
            "options": [
                "comparison",
                "addition",
                "variety"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xarajat",
            "RightAnswer": "expense",
            "options": [
                "decision",
                "comparison",
                "addition"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "(qimmat)/(arzon)",
            "RightAnswer": "(in)expensive",
            "options": [
                "affordable",
                "dishonest",
                "honest"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "baholamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "judge",
            "options": [
                "decide on",
                "compare sth to",
                "add"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hukm",
            "RightAnswer": "judgement",
            "options": [
                "expense",
                "decision",
                "comparison"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xizmat qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "serve",
            "options": [
                "judge",
                "decide on",
                "compare sth to"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xizmat",
            "RightAnswer": "service",
            "options": [
                "judgement",
                "expense",
                "decision"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xizmatkor",
            "RightAnswer": "servant",
            "options": [
                "service",
                "judgement",
                "expense"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "haqiqat, rost",
            "RightAnswer": "true",
            "options": [
                "(in)expensive",
                "affordable",
                "dishonest"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "haqiqat",
            "RightAnswer": "truth",
            "options": [
                "servant",
                "service",
                "judgement"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yolg‘on",
            "RightAnswer": "untrue",
            "options": [
                "true",
                "(in)expensive",
                "affordable"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rostgo‘y",
            "RightAnswer": "truthful",
            "options": [
                "untrue",
                "true",
                "(in)expensive"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishlatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "use",
            "options": [
                "serve",
                "judge",
                "decide on"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "foydali",
            "RightAnswer": "useful",
            "options": [
                "truthful",
                "untrue",
                "true"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "foydasiz",
            "RightAnswer": "useless",
            "options": [
                "useful",
                "truthful",
                "untrue"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qadrlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "value",
            "options": [
                "use",
                "serve",
                "judge"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qadrli, qimmatbaho",
            "RightAnswer": "valuable",
            "options": [
                "useless",
                "useful",
                "truthful"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "noto‘g‘ri fikrda bo‘lmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "wrong about",
            "options": [
                "proud of",
                "married to",
                "jealous of"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tegishli bo‘lmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "belong to",
            "options": [
                "chat (to sb) about",
                "care about",
                "argue (with sb) about"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...dan qarzga olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "borrow sth from",
            "options": [
                "belong to",
                "chat (to sb) about",
                "care about"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...dan sotib olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "buy sth from",
            "options": [
                "borrow sth from",
                "belong to",
                "chat (to sb) about"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o‘rtasidan tanlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "choose between",
            "options": [
                "buy sth from",
                "borrow sth from",
                "belong to"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qarzga bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "lend sth to",
            "options": [
                "choose between",
                "buy sth from",
                "borrow sth from"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "pul to‘lamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "pay for",
            "options": [
                "lend sth to",
                "choose between",
                "buy sth from"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...ga sarflamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "spend sth on",
            "options": [
                "pay for",
                "lend sth to",
                "choose between"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "... uchun reklama",
            "RightAnswer": "an advert(isement) for",
            "options": [
                "a relationship with",
                "an argument (with sb) about",
                "a question about"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 6": [
        {
            "Question": "sun’iy",
            "RightAnswer": "artificial",
            "options": [
                "valuable",
                "useless",
                "useful"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "avtomatik",
            "RightAnswer": "automatic",
            "options": [
                "artificial",
                "valuable",
                "useless"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "murakkab",
            "RightAnswer": "complicated",
            "options": [
                "automatic",
                "artificial",
                "valuable"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kamaymoq; kamayish",
            "RightAnswer": "decrease",
            "options": [
                "waste",
                "supply",
                "purchase"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "raqamli",
            "RightAnswer": "digital",
            "options": [
                "complicated",
                "automatic",
                "artificial"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kashf qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "discover",
            "options": [
                "value",
                "use",
                "serve"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ta’sir",
            "RightAnswer": "effect",
            "options": [
                "truth",
                "servant",
                "service"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jihozlar",
            "RightAnswer": "equipment",
            "options": [
                "effect",
                "truth",
                "servant"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "baholamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "estimate",
            "options": [
                "discover",
                "value",
                "use"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aniq",
            "RightAnswer": "exact",
            "options": [
                "digital",
                "complicated",
                "automatic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tajriba o‘tkazmoq; tajriba",
            "RightAnswer": "experiment",
            "options": [
                "decrease",
                "waste",
                "supply"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qurilma",
            "RightAnswer": "gadget",
            "options": [
                "equipment",
                "effect",
                "truth"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qurilma (kompyuter)",
            "RightAnswer": "hardware",
            "options": [
                "gadget",
                "equipment",
                "effect"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ixtiro qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "invent",
            "options": [
                "estimate",
                "discover",
                "value"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jalb qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "involve",
            "options": [
                "invent",
                "estimate",
                "discover"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "laboratoriya",
            "RightAnswer": "laboratory",
            "options": [
                "hardware",
                "gadget",
                "equipment"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yetishmaslik; yetishmasligi",
            "RightAnswer": "lack",
            "options": [
                "experiment",
                "decrease",
                "waste"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "noutbuk",
            "RightAnswer": "laptop",
            "options": [
                "laboratory",
                "hardware",
                "gadget"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maksimal",
            "RightAnswer": "maximum",
            "options": [
                "exact",
                "digital",
                "complicated"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "minimal",
            "RightAnswer": "minimum",
            "options": [
                "maximum",
                "exact",
                "digital"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boshqarmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "operate",
            "options": [
                "involve",
                "invent",
                "estimate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "plastmassa; plastik",
            "RightAnswer": "plastic",
            "options": [
                "expert",
                "sense of humour",
                "solar system"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dastur tuzmoq; dastur",
            "RightAnswer": "program",
            "options": [
                "lack",
                "experiment",
                "decrease"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tadqiqot",
            "RightAnswer": "research",
            "options": [
                "laptop",
                "laboratory",
                "hardware"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishlamoq (kompyuter va h.k.)",
            "RightAnswer": "run",
            "options": [
                "operate",
                "involve",
                "invent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ekran",
            "RightAnswer": "screen",
            "options": [
                "research",
                "laptop",
                "laboratory"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dasturiy ta’minot",
            "RightAnswer": "software",
            "options": [
                "screen",
                "research",
                "laptop"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kutilmagan",
            "RightAnswer": "sudden",
            "options": [
                "minimum",
                "maximum",
                "exact"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "texnologiya",
            "RightAnswer": "technology",
            "options": [
                "software",
                "screen",
                "research"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "noyob",
            "RightAnswer": "unique",
            "options": [
                "sudden",
                "minimum",
                "maximum"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "buzilmoq (mashina)",
            "RightAnswer": "break down",
            "options": [
                "take down",
                "take back",
                "save up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tasodifan topmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "come across",
            "options": [
                "break down",
                "take down",
                "take back"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bilib olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "find out",
            "options": [
                "come across",
                "break down",
                "take down"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bahona o‘ylab topmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "make up",
            "options": [
                "find out",
                "come across",
                "break down"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tortib sindirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "pull off",
            "options": [
                "make up",
                "find out",
                "come across"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chiqindiga tashlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "throw away",
            "options": [
                "pull off",
                "make up",
                "find out"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o‘chirib qo‘ymoq",
            "RightAnswer": "turn off",
            "options": [
                "throw away",
                "pull off",
                "make up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yoqmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "turn on",
            "options": [
                "turn off",
                "throw away",
                "pull off"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nihoyat",
            "RightAnswer": "at last",
            "options": [
                "in good condition",
                "in debt",
                "in cash"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tasodifan",
            "RightAnswer": "by chance",
            "options": [
                "at last",
                "in good condition",
                "in debt"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mening fikrimcha",
            "RightAnswer": "in my opinion",
            "options": [
                "by chance",
                "at last",
                "in good condition"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oxirida",
            "RightAnswer": "in the end",
            "options": [
                "in my opinion",
                "by chance",
                "at last"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kelajakda",
            "RightAnswer": "in the future",
            "options": [
                "in the end",
                "in my opinion",
                "by chance"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "buzilgan (ishlamaydigan)",
            "RightAnswer": "out of order",
            "options": [
                "in the future",
                "in the end",
                "in my opinion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qaynamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "boil",
            "options": [
                "run",
                "operate",
                "involve"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qozon",
            "RightAnswer": "boiler",
            "options": [
                "technology",
                "software",
                "screen"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qaynash",
            "RightAnswer": "boiling",
            "options": [
                "handle",
                "routine",
                "criminal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kimyogar",
            "RightAnswer": "chemist",
            "options": [
                "boiler",
                "technology",
                "software"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kimyoviy",
            "RightAnswer": "chemical",
            "options": [
                "unique",
                "sudden",
                "minimum"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kimyo",
            "RightAnswer": "chemistry",
            "options": [
                "chemist",
                "boiler",
                "technology"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xulosa qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "conclude",
            "options": [
                "boil",
                "run",
                "operate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xulosa",
            "RightAnswer": "conclusion",
            "options": [
                "chemistry",
                "chemist",
                "boiler"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tekshirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "examine",
            "options": [
                "conclude",
                "boil",
                "run"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "imtihon",
            "RightAnswer": "examination",
            "options": [
                "conclusion",
                "chemistry",
                "chemist"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "imtihon oluvchi",
            "RightAnswer": "examiner",
            "options": [
                "examination",
                "conclusion",
                "chemistry"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hayratga solmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "fascinate",
            "options": [
                "examine",
                "conclude",
                "boil"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qiziqish",
            "RightAnswer": "fascination",
            "options": [
                "examiner",
                "examination",
                "conclusion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qiziqarli",
            "RightAnswer": "fascinating",
            "options": [
                "chemical",
                "unique",
                "sudden"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tarix",
            "RightAnswer": "history",
            "options": [
                "fascination",
                "examiner",
                "examination"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tarixiy",
            "RightAnswer": "historic",
            "options": [
                "fascinating",
                "chemical",
                "unique"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tarixchi",
            "RightAnswer": "historian",
            "options": [
                "history",
                "fascination",
                "examiner"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bir xil",
            "RightAnswer": "identical",
            "options": [
                "historic",
                "fascinating",
                "chemical"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bir xil tarzda",
            "RightAnswer": "identically",
            "options": [
                "backwards",
                "abroad",
                "silently"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uzun",
            "RightAnswer": "long",
            "options": [
                "identical",
                "historic",
                "fascinating"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uzunlik",
            "RightAnswer": "length",
            "options": [
                "historian",
                "history",
                "fascination"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o‘lchamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "measure",
            "options": [
                "fascinate",
                "examine",
                "conclude"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o‘lchov",
            "RightAnswer": "measurement",
            "options": [
                "length",
                "historian",
                "history"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "fan",
            "RightAnswer": "science",
            "options": [
                "measurement",
                "length",
                "historian"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "olim",
            "RightAnswer": "scientist",
            "options": [
                "science",
                "measurement",
                "length"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "farqli",
            "RightAnswer": "different from/to",
            "options": [
                "wrong about",
                "proud of",
                "married to"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to‘la",
            "RightAnswer": "full of",
            "options": [
                "different from/to",
                "wrong about",
                "proud of"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "... bilan boshlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "begin sth with",
            "options": [
                "spend sth on",
                "pay for",
                "lend sth to"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...ga ulamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "connect sth to",
            "options": [
                "begin sth with",
                "spend sth on",
                "pay for"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...dan uzmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "disconnect sth from",
            "options": [
                "connect sth to",
                "begin sth with",
                "spend sth on"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "... bilan to‘ldirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "fill sth with",
            "options": [
                "disconnect sth from",
                "connect sth to",
                "begin sth with"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...ga olib kelmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "result in",
            "options": [
                "fill sth with",
                "disconnect sth from",
                "connect sth to"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "... orasidagi farq",
            "RightAnswer": "a difference between",
            "options": [
                "an advert(isement) for",
                "a relationship with",
                "an argument (with sb) about"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "... haqidagi g‘oya",
            "RightAnswer": "an idea about",
            "options": [
                "a difference between",
                "an advert(isement) for",
                "a relationship with"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bir nechta",
            "RightAnswer": "a number of",
            "options": [
                "a solution to",
                "an advantage of",
                "a joke about"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "... uchun sabab",
            "RightAnswer": "a reason for",
            "options": [
                "an idea about",
                "a difference between",
                "an advert(isement) for"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "... turi",
            "RightAnswer": "a type of",
            "options": [
                "a reason for",
                "an idea about",
                "a difference between"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 7": [
        {
            "Question": "sheva",
            "RightAnswer": "accent",
            "options": [
                "scientist",
                "science",
                "measurement"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "e’lon",
            "RightAnswer": "announcement",
            "options": [
                "accent",
                "scientist",
                "science"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "efirga uzatmoq; eshittirish",
            "RightAnswer": "broadcast",
            "options": [
                "program",
                "lack",
                "experiment"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kanal",
            "RightAnswer": "channel",
            "options": [
                "announcement",
                "accent",
                "scientist"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aniq, ravshan",
            "RightAnswer": "clear",
            "options": [
                "long",
                "identical",
                "historic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bosmoq (kompyuter sichqonchasi)",
            "RightAnswer": "click",
            "options": [
                "measure",
                "fascinate",
                "examine"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bog‘lanmoq; aloqa",
            "RightAnswer": "contact",
            "options": [
                "broadcast",
                "program",
                "lack"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "fayl",
            "RightAnswer": "file",
            "options": [
                "channel",
                "announcement",
                "accent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rasmiy",
            "RightAnswer": "formal",
            "options": [
                "clear",
                "long",
                "identical"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rasm, tasvir",
            "RightAnswer": "image",
            "options": [
                "file",
                "channel",
                "announcement"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "norasmiy",
            "RightAnswer": "informal",
            "options": [
                "formal",
                "clear",
                "long"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "internet",
            "RightAnswer": "Internet",
            "options": [
                "image",
                "file",
                "channel"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bezovta qilmoq, to‘xtatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "interrupt",
            "options": [
                "click",
                "measure",
                "fascinate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bog‘lamoq; havola",
            "RightAnswer": "link",
            "options": [
                "contact",
                "broadcast",
                "program"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ommaviy axborot vositalari",
            "RightAnswer": "media",
            "options": [
                "Internet",
                "image",
                "file"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mobil telefon",
            "RightAnswer": "mobile phone",
            "options": [
                "public transport",
                "video game",
                "folk music"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "onlayn",
            "RightAnswer": "online",
            "options": [
                "nearby",
                "sure about/of",
                "tired of"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "pauza qilmoq; tanaffus",
            "RightAnswer": "pause",
            "options": [
                "link",
                "contact",
                "broadcast"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko‘ndirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "persuade",
            "options": [
                "interrupt",
                "click",
                "measure"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "talaffuz qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "pronounce",
            "options": [
                "persuade",
                "interrupt",
                "click"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chop etmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "publish",
            "options": [
                "pronounce",
                "persuade",
                "interrupt"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xabar bermoq; hisobot",
            "RightAnswer": "report",
            "options": [
                "pause",
                "link",
                "contact"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "so‘ramoq; so‘rov",
            "RightAnswer": "request",
            "options": [
                "report",
                "pause",
                "link"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo‘ng‘iroq qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "ring",
            "options": [
                "publish",
                "pronounce",
                "persuade"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "signal, belgilar",
            "RightAnswer": "signal",
            "options": [
                "media",
                "Internet",
                "image"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "so‘kinmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "swear",
            "options": [
                "ring",
                "publish",
                "pronounce"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "terib yozmoq (kompyuterda)",
            "RightAnswer": "type",
            "options": [
                "swear",
                "ring",
                "publish"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tomoshabin",
            "RightAnswer": "viewer",
            "options": [
                "signal",
                "media",
                "Internet"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "veb-sayt",
            "RightAnswer": "website",
            "options": [
                "viewer",
                "signal",
                "media"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shivirlashmoq; shivir",
            "RightAnswer": "whisper",
            "options": [
                "request",
                "report",
                "pause"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "telefon qilib qaytib bog‘lanmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "call back",
            "options": [
                "turn on",
                "turn off",
                "throw away"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chop etilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "come out",
            "options": [
                "call back",
                "turn on",
                "turn off"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uzib qo‘ymoq (telefon, elektr va h.k.)",
            "RightAnswer": "cut off",
            "options": [
                "come out",
                "call back",
                "turn on"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to‘ldirmoq (blankalar, shakllar)",
            "RightAnswer": "fill in",
            "options": [
                "cut off",
                "come out",
                "call back"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "telefonni qo‘yib qo‘ymoq",
            "RightAnswer": "hang up",
            "options": [
                "fill in",
                "cut off",
                "come out"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "internetdan chiqmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "log off",
            "options": [
                "hang up",
                "fill in",
                "cut off"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "internetga kirib ulanish",
            "RightAnswer": "log on(to)",
            "options": [
                "log off",
                "hang up",
                "fill in"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chiqarib berish (printerdan)",
            "RightAnswer": "print out",
            "options": [
                "log on(to)",
                "log off",
                "hang up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "email/telefon/xat orqali",
            "RightAnswer": "by e-mail/phone/letter",
            "options": [
                "out of order",
                "in the future",
                "in the end"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "internetda",
            "RightAnswer": "on the Internet",
            "options": [
                "by e-mail/phone/letter",
                "out of order",
                "in the future"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yangiliklarda",
            "RightAnswer": "on the news",
            "options": [
                "on the Internet",
                "by e-mail/phone/letter",
                "out of order"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "telefonda",
            "RightAnswer": "on the phone",
            "options": [
                "on the news",
                "on the Internet",
                "by e-mail/phone/letter"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "radioda",
            "RightAnswer": "on the radio",
            "options": [
                "on the phone",
                "on the news",
                "on the Internet"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "televizorda",
            "RightAnswer": "on TV",
            "options": [
                "on the radio",
                "on the phone",
                "on the news"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aniq",
            "RightAnswer": "certain",
            "options": [
                "informal",
                "formal",
                "clear"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "albatta",
            "RightAnswer": "certainly",
            "options": [
                "identically",
                "backwards",
                "abroad"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishonch",
            "RightAnswer": "certainty",
            "options": [
                "website",
                "viewer",
                "signal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aloqa qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "communicate",
            "options": [
                "type",
                "swear",
                "ring"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aloqa",
            "RightAnswer": "communication",
            "options": [
                "certainty",
                "website",
                "viewer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ulanmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "connect",
            "options": [
                "communicate",
                "type",
                "swear"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ulanish",
            "RightAnswer": "connection",
            "options": [
                "communication",
                "certainty",
                "website"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uzilish",
            "RightAnswer": "disconnect",
            "options": [
                "connect",
                "communicate",
                "type"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yetkazib bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "deliver",
            "options": [
                "disconnect",
                "connect",
                "communicate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yetkazib berish",
            "RightAnswer": "delivery",
            "options": [
                "connection",
                "communication",
                "certainty"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ifoda etmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "express",
            "options": [
                "deliver",
                "disconnect",
                "connect"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ifoda",
            "RightAnswer": "expression",
            "options": [
                "delivery",
                "connection",
                "communication"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ifodali",
            "RightAnswer": "expressive",
            "options": [
                "certain",
                "informal",
                "formal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xabar bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "inform",
            "options": [
                "express",
                "deliver",
                "disconnect"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ma’lumotli",
            "RightAnswer": "informative",
            "options": [
                "expressive",
                "certain",
                "informal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ma’lumot",
            "RightAnswer": "information",
            "options": [
                "expression",
                "delivery",
                "connection"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bashorat qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "predict",
            "options": [
                "inform",
                "express",
                "deliver"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bashorat",
            "RightAnswer": "prediction",
            "options": [
                "information",
                "expression",
                "delivery"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "(no)bashorat qilinadigan",
            "RightAnswer": "(un)predictable",
            "options": [
                "informative",
                "expressive",
                "certain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sir",
            "RightAnswer": "secret",
            "options": [
                "prediction",
                "information",
                "expression"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yashirincha",
            "RightAnswer": "secretly",
            "options": [
                "certainly",
                "identically",
                "backwards"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sir saqlash",
            "RightAnswer": "secrecy",
            "options": [
                "secret",
                "prediction",
                "information"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "gapirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "speak",
            "options": [
                "predict",
                "inform",
                "express"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "gapirdi",
            "RightAnswer": "spoke",
            "options": [
                "forgave",
                "flew",
                "drove"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "gapirilgan",
            "RightAnswer": "spoken",
            "options": [
                "forgiven",
                "flown",
                "driven"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nutq so‘zlovchi",
            "RightAnswer": "speaker",
            "options": [
                "secrecy",
                "secret",
                "prediction"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nutq",
            "RightAnswer": "speech",
            "options": [
                "speaker",
                "secrecy",
                "secret"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tarjima qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "translate",
            "options": [
                "speak",
                "predict",
                "inform"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tarjima",
            "RightAnswer": "translation",
            "options": [
                "speech",
                "speaker",
                "secrecy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tarjimon",
            "RightAnswer": "translator",
            "options": [
                "translation",
                "speech",
                "speaker"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "izoh bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "comment on",
            "options": [
                "result in",
                "fill sth with",
                "disconnect sth from"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "... bilan aloqa qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "communicate with",
            "options": [
                "comment on",
                "result in",
                "fill sth with"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tez qaramoq",
            "RightAnswer": "glance at",
            "options": [
                "communicate with",
                "comment on",
                "result in"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nimanidir ...dan qabul qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "receive sth from",
            "options": [
                "glance at",
                "communicate with",
                "comment on"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "javob bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "reply to",
            "options": [
                "receive sth from",
                "glance at",
                "communicate with"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nimanidir ...ga yubormoq",
            "RightAnswer": "send sth to sb",
            "options": [
                "reply to",
                "receive sth from",
                "glance at"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "... haqida gaplashmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "talk (to sb) about",
            "options": [
                "send sth to sb",
                "reply to",
                "receive sth from"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kimdandir haqida aytmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "tell sb about",
            "options": [
                "talk (to sb) about",
                "send sth to sb",
                "reply to"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...dan ...ga tarjima qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "translate (from sth) into",
            "options": [
                "tell sb about",
                "talk (to sb) about",
                "send sth to sb"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kimdandir haqida yozmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "write (to sb) about",
            "options": [
                "translate (from sth) into",
                "tell sb about",
                "talk (to sb) about"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "... haqidagi ma’lumot",
            "RightAnswer": "information about",
            "options": [
                "a type of",
                "a reason for",
                "an idea about"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "(kimdandir) haqidagi xat",
            "RightAnswer": "a letter (from sb) about",
            "options": [
                "information about",
                "a type of",
                "a reason for"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 8": [
        {
            "Question": "tan olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "admit",
            "options": [
                "translate",
                "speak",
                "predict"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hibsga olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "arrest",
            "options": [
                "admit",
                "translate",
                "speak"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xayriya",
            "RightAnswer": "charity",
            "options": [
                "translator",
                "translation",
                "speech"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jinoyat qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "commit",
            "options": [
                "arrest",
                "admit",
                "translate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jamoa",
            "RightAnswer": "community",
            "options": [
                "charity",
                "translator",
                "translation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sud",
            "RightAnswer": "court",
            "options": [
                "community",
                "charity",
                "translator"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jinoyatchi; jinoyatchilikka oid",
            "RightAnswer": "criminal",
            "options": [
                "plastic",
                "expert",
                "sense of humour"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "madaniyat",
            "RightAnswer": "culture",
            "options": [
                "court",
                "community",
                "charity"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tanish",
            "RightAnswer": "familiar",
            "options": [
                "(un)predictable",
                "informative",
                "expressive"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hukumat",
            "RightAnswer": "government",
            "options": [
                "culture",
                "court",
                "community"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "odat",
            "RightAnswer": "habit",
            "options": [
                "government",
                "culture",
                "court"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shaxsiy guvohnoma",
            "RightAnswer": "identity card",
            "options": [
                "mobile phone",
                "public transport",
                "video game"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "noqonuniy",
            "RightAnswer": "illegal",
            "options": [
                "familiar",
                "(un)predictable",
                "informative"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "siyosat",
            "RightAnswer": "politics",
            "options": [
                "habit",
                "government",
                "culture"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aholi",
            "RightAnswer": "population",
            "options": [
                "politics",
                "habit",
                "government"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qamoqxona",
            "RightAnswer": "prison",
            "options": [
                "population",
                "politics",
                "habit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "norozilik bildirmoq; norozilik",
            "RightAnswer": "protest",
            "options": [
                "whisper",
                "request",
                "report"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yashovchi (rezident)",
            "RightAnswer": "resident",
            "options": [
                "prison",
                "population",
                "politics"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mas’uliyatli",
            "RightAnswer": "responsible",
            "options": [
                "illegal",
                "familiar",
                "(un)predictable"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o‘g‘irlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "steal",
            "options": [
                "commit",
                "arrest",
                "admit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kundalik ish; oddiy, doimiy",
            "RightAnswer": "routine",
            "options": [
                "criminal",
                "plastic",
                "expert"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jadval",
            "RightAnswer": "schedule",
            "options": [
                "resident",
                "prison",
                "population"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "vaziyat",
            "RightAnswer": "situation",
            "options": [
                "schedule",
                "resident",
                "prison"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ijtimoiy",
            "RightAnswer": "social",
            "options": [
                "responsible",
                "illegal",
                "familiar"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jamiyat",
            "RightAnswer": "society",
            "options": [
                "situation",
                "schedule",
                "resident"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "an’ana",
            "RightAnswer": "tradition",
            "options": [
                "society",
                "situation",
                "schedule"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "odatiy",
            "RightAnswer": "typical",
            "options": [
                "social",
                "responsible",
                "illegal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ovoz bermoq; ovoz",
            "RightAnswer": "vote",
            "options": [
                "protest",
                "whisper",
                "request"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yoshlar klubi",
            "RightAnswer": "youth club",
            "options": [
                "identity card",
                "mobile phone",
                "public transport"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "noqonuniy kirib kelmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "break in(to)",
            "options": [
                "print out",
                "log on(to)",
                "log off"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yetib olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "catch up (with)",
            "options": [
                "break in(to)",
                "print out",
                "log on(to)"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jazodan qutulib ketmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "get away with",
            "options": [
                "catch up (with)",
                "break in(to)",
                "print out"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "turmoq (karavotdan)",
            "RightAnswer": "get up",
            "options": [
                "get away with",
                "catch up (with)",
                "break in(to)"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko‘chib kelmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "move in",
            "options": [
                "get up",
                "get away with",
                "catch up (with)"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "joyiga qo‘ymoq",
            "RightAnswer": "put away",
            "options": [
                "move in",
                "get up",
                "get away with"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uyg‘onmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "wake up",
            "options": [
                "put away",
                "move in",
                "get up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "idish-tovoq yuvmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "wash up",
            "options": [
                "wake up",
                "put away",
                "move in"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qonunga zid",
            "RightAnswer": "against the law",
            "options": [
                "on TV",
                "on the radio",
                "on the phone"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "... yoshida",
            "RightAnswer": "at the age of",
            "options": [
                "against the law",
                "on TV",
                "on the radio"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "omma oldida",
            "RightAnswer": "in public",
            "options": [
                "at the age of",
                "against the law",
                "on TV"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...ga javoban",
            "RightAnswer": "in response to",
            "options": [
                "in public",
                "at the age of",
                "against the law"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aloqada",
            "RightAnswer": "in touch (with)",
            "options": [
                "in response to",
                "in public",
                "at the age of"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o‘smirlikda",
            "RightAnswer": "in your teens",
            "options": [
                "in touch (with)",
                "in response to",
                "in public"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rozi bo‘lmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "agree",
            "options": [
                "steal",
                "commit",
                "arrest"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kelishuv",
            "RightAnswer": "agreement",
            "options": [
                "tradition",
                "society",
                "situation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kelishmovchilik",
            "RightAnswer": "disagree",
            "options": [
                "agree",
                "steal",
                "commit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishonch",
            "RightAnswer": "belief",
            "options": [
                "agreement",
                "tradition",
                "society"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishonmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "believe",
            "options": [
                "disagree",
                "agree",
                "steal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "(no)ishonchli",
            "RightAnswer": "(un)believable",
            "options": [
                "typical",
                "social",
                "responsible"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jasorat",
            "RightAnswer": "courage",
            "options": [
                "belief",
                "agreement",
                "tradition"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jasur",
            "RightAnswer": "courageous",
            "options": [
                "(un)believable",
                "typical",
                "social"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "saylamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "elect",
            "options": [
                "believe",
                "disagree",
                "agree"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "saylov",
            "RightAnswer": "election",
            "options": [
                "courage",
                "belief",
                "agreement"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "teng",
            "RightAnswer": "equal",
            "options": [
                "courageous",
                "(un)believable",
                "typical"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tenglik",
            "RightAnswer": "equality",
            "options": [
                "election",
                "courage",
                "belief"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "teng emas",
            "RightAnswer": "unequal",
            "options": [
                "equal",
                "courageous",
                "(un)believable"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hayot",
            "RightAnswer": "life",
            "options": [
                "equality",
                "election",
                "courage"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yashamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "live",
            "options": [
                "elect",
                "believe",
                "disagree"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tirik",
            "RightAnswer": "alive",
            "options": [
                "unequal",
                "equal",
                "courageous"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "millat",
            "RightAnswer": "nation",
            "options": [
                "life",
                "equality",
                "election"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "millat, fuqarolik",
            "RightAnswer": "nationality",
            "options": [
                "nation",
                "life",
                "equality"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "(xalqaro) milliy",
            "RightAnswer": "(inter)national",
            "options": [
                "alive",
                "unequal",
                "equal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tinchlik",
            "RightAnswer": "peace",
            "options": [
                "nationality",
                "nation",
                "life"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tinch (tinch tarzda)",
            "RightAnswer": "peaceful(ly)",
            "options": [
                "noisy, noisily",
                "online",
                "nearby"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mahbus",
            "RightAnswer": "prisoner",
            "options": [
                "peace",
                "nationality",
                "nation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "otmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "shoot",
            "options": [
                "live",
                "elect",
                "believe"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "otish",
            "RightAnswer": "shot",
            "options": [
                "prisoner",
                "peace",
                "nationality"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "otishma",
            "RightAnswer": "shooting",
            "options": [
                "shot",
                "prisoner",
                "peace"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...dan jahli chiqqan",
            "RightAnswer": "angry (with sb) about",
            "options": [
                "full of",
                "different from/to",
                "wrong about"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aybdor",
            "RightAnswer": "guilty of",
            "options": [
                "angry (with sb) about",
                "full of",
                "different from/to"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kimnidir ...da ayblamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "accuse sb of",
            "options": [
                "write (to sb) about",
                "translate (from sth) into",
                "tell sb about"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kimnidir uchun ayblamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "blame sb for",
            "options": [
                "accuse sb of",
                "write (to sb) about",
                "translate (from sth) into"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...ni ...ga yuklamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "blame sth on",
            "options": [
                "blame sb for",
                "accuse sb of",
                "write (to sb) about"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "... uchun tanqid qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "criticise sb for",
            "options": [
                "blame sth on",
                "blame sb for",
                "accuse sb of"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...ni unutmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "forget about",
            "options": [
                "criticise sb for",
                "blame sth on",
                "blame sb for"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "... uchun kechirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "forgive sb for",
            "options": [
                "forget about",
                "criticise sb for",
                "blame sth on"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kimnidir ...ga taklif qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "invite sb to",
            "options": [
                "forgive sb for",
                "forget about",
                "criticise sb for"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "... uchun jazolamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "punish sb for",
            "options": [
                "invite sb to",
                "forgive sb for",
                "forget about"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...ni bilan bo‘lishmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "share sth with",
            "options": [
                "punish sb for",
                "invite sb to",
                "forgive sb for"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...ga tabassum qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "smile at",
            "options": [
                "share sth with",
                "punish sb for",
                "invite sb to"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 9": [
        {
            "Question": "maqsad, orzu",
            "RightAnswer": "ambition",
            "options": [
                "shooting",
                "shot",
                "prisoner"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ariza",
            "RightAnswer": "application",
            "options": [
                "ambition",
                "shooting",
                "shot"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bank hisobi",
            "RightAnswer": "bank account",
            "options": [
                "youth club",
                "identity card",
                "mobile phone"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boshliq",
            "RightAnswer": "boss",
            "options": [
                "application",
                "ambition",
                "shooting"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "martaba",
            "RightAnswer": "career",
            "options": [
                "boss",
                "application",
                "ambition"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hamkasb",
            "RightAnswer": "colleague",
            "options": [
                "career",
                "boss",
                "application"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kompaniya",
            "RightAnswer": "company",
            "options": [
                "colleague",
                "career",
                "boss"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shartnoma",
            "RightAnswer": "contract",
            "options": [
                "company",
                "colleague",
                "career"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bo‘lim",
            "RightAnswer": "department",
            "options": [
                "contract",
                "company",
                "colleague"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "loyi‍q bo‘lmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "deserve",
            "options": [
                "shoot",
                "live",
                "elect"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "pul topmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "earn",
            "options": [
                "deserve",
                "shoot",
                "live"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shuhrat",
            "RightAnswer": "fame",
            "options": [
                "department",
                "contract",
                "company"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maqsad",
            "RightAnswer": "goal",
            "options": [
                "fame",
                "department",
                "contract"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taassurot qoldirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "impress",
            "options": [
                "earn",
                "deserve",
                "shoot"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "daromad",
            "RightAnswer": "income",
            "options": [
                "goal",
                "fame",
                "department"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sanoat",
            "RightAnswer": "industry",
            "options": [
                "income",
                "goal",
                "fame"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "suhbat; suhbat o‘tqazmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "interview",
            "options": [
                "vote",
                "protest",
                "whisper"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yetakchi",
            "RightAnswer": "leader",
            "options": [
                "industry",
                "income",
                "goal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boshqaruvchi",
            "RightAnswer": "manager",
            "options": [
                "leader",
                "industry",
                "income"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nafaqa",
            "RightAnswer": "retirement",
            "options": [
                "manager",
                "leader",
                "industry"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qashshoqlik",
            "RightAnswer": "poverty",
            "options": [
                "retirement",
                "manager",
                "leader"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bosim",
            "RightAnswer": "pressure",
            "options": [
                "poverty",
                "retirement",
                "manager"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oldingi",
            "RightAnswer": "previous",
            "options": [
                "(inter)national",
                "alive",
                "unequal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kasb",
            "RightAnswer": "profession",
            "options": [
                "pressure",
                "poverty",
                "retirement"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nafaqaga chiqmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "retire",
            "options": [
                "impress",
                "earn",
                "deserve"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ish haqi",
            "RightAnswer": "salary",
            "options": [
                "profession",
                "pressure",
                "poverty"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xodimlar jamoasi",
            "RightAnswer": "staff",
            "options": [
                "salary",
                "profession",
                "pressure"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ish tashlash",
            "RightAnswer": "strike",
            "options": [
                "staff",
                "salary",
                "profession"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "soliq solmoq; soliq",
            "RightAnswer": "tax",
            "options": [
                "interview",
                "vote",
                "protest"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "badavlat",
            "RightAnswer": "wealthy",
            "options": [
                "previous",
                "(inter)national",
                "alive"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bekor qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "call off",
            "options": [
                "wash up",
                "wake up",
                "put away"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qaytarib bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "give back",
            "options": [
                "call off",
                "wash up",
                "wake up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sodir bo‘lmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "go on",
            "options": [
                "give back",
                "call off",
                "wash up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kechiktirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "put off",
            "options": [
                "go on",
                "give back",
                "call off"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tashkil qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "set up",
            "options": [
                "put off",
                "go on",
                "give back"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kech uxlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "stay up",
            "options": [
                "set up",
                "put off",
                "go on"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "olib tashlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "take away",
            "options": [
                "stay up",
                "set up",
                "put off"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boshqaruvni qo‘lga olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "take over",
            "options": [
                "take away",
                "stay up",
                "set up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hozirda",
            "RightAnswer": "at the moment",
            "options": [
                "in your teens",
                "in touch (with)",
                "in response to"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mas’ul (biror narsa uchun)",
            "RightAnswer": "in charge",
            "options": [
                "at the moment",
                "in your teens",
                "in touch (with)"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xizmat safarida",
            "RightAnswer": "on business",
            "options": [
                "in charge",
                "at the moment",
                "in your teens"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ish tashlashda",
            "RightAnswer": "on strike",
            "options": [
                "on business",
                "in charge",
                "at the moment"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "vaqtida",
            "RightAnswer": "on time",
            "options": [
                "on strike",
                "on business",
                "in charge"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "navbatchilikda/navbatchilikdan tashqari",
            "RightAnswer": "on/off duty",
            "options": [
                "on time",
                "on strike",
                "on business"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yordam bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "assist",
            "options": [
                "retire",
                "impress",
                "earn"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yordamchi",
            "RightAnswer": "assistant",
            "options": [
                "strike",
                "staff",
                "salary"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yordam",
            "RightAnswer": "assistance",
            "options": [
                "assistant",
                "strike",
                "staff"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tilamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "beg",
            "options": [
                "assist",
                "retire",
                "impress"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tilanchi",
            "RightAnswer": "beggar",
            "options": [
                "assistance",
                "assistant",
                "strike"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "buyruqberuvchi",
            "RightAnswer": "bossy",
            "options": [
                "wealthy",
                "previous",
                "(inter)national"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishga olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "employ",
            "options": [
                "beg",
                "assist",
                "retire"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "(ishsizlik) ish bilan ta’minlash",
            "RightAnswer": "(un)employment",
            "options": [
                "beggar",
                "assistance",
                "assistant"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ish beruvchi",
            "RightAnswer": "employer",
            "options": [
                "(un)employment",
                "beggar",
                "assistance"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishchi",
            "RightAnswer": "employee",
            "options": [
                "employer",
                "(un)employment",
                "beggar"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishsiz",
            "RightAnswer": "unemployed",
            "options": [
                "bossy",
                "wealthy",
                "previous"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mashhur",
            "RightAnswer": "famous",
            "options": [
                "unemployed",
                "bossy",
                "wealthy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "band qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "occupy",
            "options": [
                "employ",
                "beg",
                "assist"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kasb, ish",
            "RightAnswer": "occupation",
            "options": [
                "employee",
                "employer",
                "(un)employment"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "idora",
            "RightAnswer": "office",
            "options": [
                "occupation",
                "employee",
                "employer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ofitser",
            "RightAnswer": "officer",
            "options": [
                "office",
                "occupation",
                "employee"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "(no)rasmiy",
            "RightAnswer": "(un)official",
            "options": [
                "famous",
                "unemployed",
                "bossy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nafaqadagi",
            "RightAnswer": "retired",
            "options": [
                "(un)official",
                "famous",
                "unemployed"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xavfsiz",
            "RightAnswer": "safe",
            "options": [
                "retired",
                "(un)official",
                "famous"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "saqlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "save",
            "options": [
                "occupy",
                "employ",
                "beg"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xavfli",
            "RightAnswer": "unsafe",
            "options": [
                "safe",
                "retired",
                "(un)official"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xavfsizlik",
            "RightAnswer": "safety",
            "options": [
                "officer",
                "office",
                "occupation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muvaffaqiyatga erishmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "succeed",
            "options": [
                "save",
                "occupy",
                "employ"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muvaffaqiyat",
            "RightAnswer": "success",
            "options": [
                "safety",
                "officer",
                "office"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "(no)muvaffaqiyatli",
            "RightAnswer": "(un)successful",
            "options": [
                "unsafe",
                "safe",
                "retired"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ehtiyotkor",
            "RightAnswer": "careful with",
            "options": [
                "guilty of",
                "angry (with sb) about",
                "full of"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qiyin",
            "RightAnswer": "difficult for",
            "options": [
                "careful with",
                "guilty of",
                "angry (with sb) about"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zerikkan",
            "RightAnswer": "fed up with",
            "options": [
                "difficult for",
                "careful with",
                "guilty of"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tayyor",
            "RightAnswer": "ready for",
            "options": [
                "fed up with",
                "difficult for",
                "careful with"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mas’ul",
            "RightAnswer": "responsible for",
            "options": [
                "ready for",
                "fed up with",
                "difficult for"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bog‘liq",
            "RightAnswer": "depend on",
            "options": [
                "smile at",
                "share sth with",
                "punish sb for"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kimnidir xabardor qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "inform sb about",
            "options": [
                "depend on",
                "smile at",
                "share sth with"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taalluqli bo‘lmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "refer to",
            "options": [
                "inform sb about",
                "depend on",
                "smile at"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sifatida ishlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "work as",
            "options": [
                "refer to",
                "inform sb about",
                "depend on"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uchun ishlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "work for",
            "options": [
                "work as",
                "refer to",
                "inform sb about"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ariza bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "apply for",
            "options": [
                "work for",
                "work as",
                "refer to"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "... turi",
            "RightAnswer": "a kind of",
            "options": [
                "a letter (from sb) about",
                "information about",
                "a type of"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 10": [
        {
            "Question": "ta’sir qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "affect",
            "options": [
                "succeed",
                "save",
                "occupy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muvozanat; muvozanat saqlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "balance",
            "options": [
                "tax",
                "interview",
                "vote"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "foyda; foyda keltirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "benefit",
            "options": [
                "balance",
                "tax",
                "interview"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nafas olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "breathe",
            "options": [
                "affect",
                "succeed",
                "save"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chaynamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "chew",
            "options": [
                "breathe",
                "affect",
                "succeed"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maydalamoq, to‘g‘ramoq",
            "RightAnswer": "chop",
            "options": [
                "chew",
                "breathe",
                "affect"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o‘z ichiga olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "contain",
            "options": [
                "chop",
                "chew",
                "breathe"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yo‘tmoq; yo‘tal",
            "RightAnswer": "cough",
            "options": [
                "benefit",
                "balance",
                "tax"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "davolamoq; davolash",
            "RightAnswer": "cure",
            "options": [
                "cough",
                "benefit",
                "balance"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mashq qilmoq; mashq",
            "RightAnswer": "exercise",
            "options": [
                "cure",
                "cough",
                "benefit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "gripp",
            "RightAnswer": "flu",
            "options": [
                "success",
                "safety",
                "officer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "operatsiya qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "have an operation",
            "options": [
                "take an exam",
                "make sure",
                "make progress"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sog‘lom",
            "RightAnswer": "healthy",
            "options": [
                "(un)successful",
                "unsafe",
                "safe"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "e’tibor bermaslik",
            "RightAnswer": "ignore",
            "options": [
                "contain",
                "chop",
                "chew"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "infeksiya",
            "RightAnswer": "infection",
            "options": [
                "flu",
                "success",
                "safety"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ingredient, tarkibiy qism",
            "RightAnswer": "ingredient",
            "options": [
                "infection",
                "flu",
                "success"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jarohat",
            "RightAnswer": "injury",
            "options": [
                "ingredient",
                "infection",
                "flu"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "cheklamoq; chegara",
            "RightAnswer": "limit",
            "options": [
                "exercise",
                "cure",
                "cough"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ovqat",
            "RightAnswer": "meal",
            "options": [
                "injury",
                "ingredient",
                "infection"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tabletka",
            "RightAnswer": "pill",
            "options": [
                "meal",
                "injury",
                "ingredient"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sog‘aymoq",
            "RightAnswer": "recover",
            "options": [
                "ignore",
                "contain",
                "chop"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sho‘r",
            "RightAnswer": "salty",
            "options": [
                "healthy",
                "(un)successful",
                "unsafe"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bo‘laklamoq; bo‘lak",
            "RightAnswer": "slice",
            "options": [
                "limit",
                "exercise",
                "cure"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nordon",
            "RightAnswer": "sour",
            "options": [
                "salty",
                "healthy",
                "(un)successful"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "achchiq",
            "RightAnswer": "spicy",
            "options": [
                "sour",
                "salty",
                "healthy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aralashtirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "stir",
            "options": [
                "recover",
                "ignore",
                "contain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "azoblanmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "suffer",
            "options": [
                "stir",
                "recover",
                "ignore"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ta’m bilmoq; ta’m",
            "RightAnswer": "taste",
            "options": [
                "slice",
                "limit",
                "exercise"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "davolash",
            "RightAnswer": "treatment",
            "options": [
                "pill",
                "meal",
                "injury"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "vitamin",
            "RightAnswer": "vitamin",
            "options": [
                "treatment",
                "pill",
                "meal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kamaytirmoq (masalan, chekish)",
            "RightAnswer": "cut down (on)",
            "options": [
                "take over",
                "take away",
                "stay up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yiqilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "fall down",
            "options": [
                "cut down (on)",
                "take over",
                "take away"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sog‘aymoq (kasallikdan)",
            "RightAnswer": "get over",
            "options": [
                "fall down",
                "cut down (on)",
                "take over"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "buzilib qolmoq (ovqat haqida)",
            "RightAnswer": "go off",
            "options": [
                "get over",
                "fall down",
                "cut down (on)"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yotib olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "lie down",
            "options": [
                "go off",
                "get over",
                "fall down"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "semirmoq (vazn qo‘shmoq)",
            "RightAnswer": "put on",
            "options": [
                "lie down",
                "go off",
                "get over"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o‘tirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "sit down",
            "options": [
                "put on",
                "lie down",
                "go off"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "turmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "stand up",
            "options": [
                "sit down",
                "put on",
                "lie down"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kechasi",
            "RightAnswer": "at night",
            "options": [
                "on/off duty",
                "on time",
                "on strike"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xavf ostida",
            "RightAnswer": "at risk",
            "options": [
                "at night",
                "on/off duty",
                "on time"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo‘shimcha ravishda",
            "RightAnswer": "in addition (to)",
            "options": [
                "at risk",
                "at night",
                "on/off duty"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "solishtirganda",
            "RightAnswer": "in comparison to",
            "options": [
                "in addition (to)",
                "at risk",
                "at night"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "formda (tana holati)",
            "RightAnswer": "in shape",
            "options": [
                "in comparison to",
                "in addition (to)",
                "at risk"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "parhezda",
            "RightAnswer": "on a diet",
            "options": [
                "in shape",
                "in comparison to",
                "in addition (to)"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "pishirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "cook",
            "options": [
                "suffer",
                "stir",
                "recover"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "novvoy",
            "RightAnswer": "baker",
            "options": [
                "vitamin",
                "treatment",
                "pill"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nonvoyxona",
            "RightAnswer": "bakery",
            "options": [
                "baker",
                "vitamin",
                "treatment"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "egilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "bend",
            "options": [
                "cook",
                "suffer",
                "stir"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "egilgan",
            "RightAnswer": "bent",
            "options": [
                "spicy",
                "sour",
                "salty"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "gaz plitasi",
            "RightAnswer": "cooker",
            "options": [
                "bakery",
                "baker",
                "vitamin"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oshpazlik",
            "RightAnswer": "cookery",
            "options": [
                "cooker",
                "bakery",
                "baker"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "niyat qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "intend",
            "options": [
                "bend",
                "cook",
                "suffer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "niyat",
            "RightAnswer": "intention",
            "options": [
                "cookery",
                "cooker",
                "bakery"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qasddan qilingan",
            "RightAnswer": "intentional",
            "options": [
                "bent",
                "spicy",
                "sour"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yugurmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "jog",
            "options": [
                "intend",
                "bend",
                "cook"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yengil yugurish",
            "RightAnswer": "jogging",
            "options": [
                "intention",
                "cookery",
                "cooker"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yuguruvchi",
            "RightAnswer": "jogger",
            "options": [
                "jogging",
                "intention",
                "cookery"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tibbiyot",
            "RightAnswer": "medicine",
            "options": [
                "jogger",
                "jogging",
                "intention"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tibbiy",
            "RightAnswer": "medical",
            "options": [
                "intentional",
                "bent",
                "spicy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "og‘riq",
            "RightAnswer": "pain",
            "options": [
                "medicine",
                "jogger",
                "jogging"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "og‘riqli",
            "RightAnswer": "painful",
            "options": [
                "medical",
                "intentional",
                "bent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "og‘riqsiz",
            "RightAnswer": "painless",
            "options": [
                "painful",
                "medical",
                "intentional"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kamaytirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "reduce",
            "options": [
                "jog",
                "intend",
                "bend"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kamayish",
            "RightAnswer": "reduction",
            "options": [
                "pain",
                "medicine",
                "jogger"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sezmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "sense",
            "options": [
                "reduce",
                "jog",
                "intend"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oqilona",
            "RightAnswer": "sensible",
            "options": [
                "painless",
                "painful",
                "medical"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sezgir",
            "RightAnswer": "sensitive",
            "options": [
                "sensible",
                "painless",
                "painful"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "vazn tortmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "weigh",
            "options": [
                "sense",
                "reduce",
                "jog"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "vazn",
            "RightAnswer": "weight",
            "options": [
                "reduction",
                "pain",
                "medicine"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bog‘langan (odati bo‘lgan)",
            "RightAnswer": "addicted to",
            "options": [
                "responsible for",
                "ready for",
                "fed up with"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "allergiyasi bor",
            "RightAnswer": "allergic to",
            "options": [
                "addicted to",
                "responsible for",
                "ready for"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qoplangan",
            "RightAnswer": "covered in",
            "options": [
                "allergic to",
                "addicted to",
                "responsible for"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mamnun",
            "RightAnswer": "pleased with",
            "options": [
                "covered in",
                "allergic to",
                "addicted to"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...dan o‘lmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "die from/of",
            "options": [
                "apply for",
                "work for",
                "work as"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qarshi kurashmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "fight against",
            "options": [
                "die from/of",
                "apply for",
                "work for"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tuzalmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "recover from",
            "options": [
                "fight against",
                "die from/of",
                "apply for"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hidi kelmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "smell of",
            "options": [
                "recover from",
                "fight against",
                "die from/of"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...ni bilan birlashtirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "combine sth with",
            "options": [
                "smell of",
                "recover from",
                "fight against"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...dan shikoyat qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "complain (to sb) about",
            "options": [
                "combine sth with",
                "smell of",
                "recover from"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "... uchun davo",
            "RightAnswer": "a cure for",
            "options": [
                "a kind of",
                "a letter (from sb) about",
                "information about"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "... uchun retsept",
            "RightAnswer": "a recipe for",
            "options": [
                "a cure for",
                "a kind of",
                "a letter (from sb) about"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 11": [
        {
            "Question": "qadimgi",
            "RightAnswer": "ancient",
            "options": [
                "sensitive",
                "sensible",
                "painless"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "katakli (matoda)",
            "RightAnswer": "checked",
            "options": [
                "ancient",
                "sensitive",
                "sensible"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "paxta",
            "RightAnswer": "cotton",
            "options": [
                "weight",
                "reduction",
                "pain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yaratmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "create",
            "options": [
                "weigh",
                "sense",
                "reduce"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dizayn qilmoq; dizayn",
            "RightAnswer": "design",
            "options": [
                "taste",
                "slice",
                "limit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tuzatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "fix",
            "options": [
                "create",
                "weigh",
                "sense"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "buklamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "fold",
            "options": [
                "fix",
                "create",
                "weigh"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "galereya",
            "RightAnswer": "gallery",
            "options": [
                "cotton",
                "weight",
                "reduction"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yaxshilanish",
            "RightAnswer": "improvement",
            "options": [
                "gallery",
                "cotton",
                "weight"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bo‘sh, keng",
            "RightAnswer": "loose",
            "options": [
                "checked",
                "ancient",
                "sensitive"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "saqlamoq, tutib turmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "maintain",
            "options": [
                "fold",
                "fix",
                "create"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mos kelmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "match",
            "options": [
                "maintain",
                "fold",
                "fix"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "material",
            "RightAnswer": "material",
            "options": [
                "improvement",
                "gallery",
                "cotton"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sezmoq; e’lon",
            "RightAnswer": "notice",
            "options": [
                "design",
                "taste",
                "slice"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "naqsh",
            "RightAnswer": "pattern",
            "options": [
                "material",
                "improvement",
                "gallery"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uyum, g‘aram",
            "RightAnswer": "pile",
            "options": [
                "pattern",
                "material",
                "improvement"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "amaliy",
            "RightAnswer": "practical",
            "options": [
                "loose",
                "checked",
                "ancient"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "dag‘al",
            "RightAnswer": "rough",
            "options": [
                "practical",
                "loose",
                "checked"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shakl",
            "RightAnswer": "shape",
            "options": [
                "pile",
                "pattern",
                "material"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ipak",
            "RightAnswer": "silk",
            "options": [
                "shape",
                "pile",
                "pattern"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yeng",
            "RightAnswer": "sleeve",
            "options": [
                "silk",
                "shape",
                "pile"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "silliq",
            "RightAnswer": "smooth",
            "options": [
                "rough",
                "practical",
                "loose"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "cho‘zilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "stretch",
            "options": [
                "match",
                "maintain",
                "fold"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chiziqli",
            "RightAnswer": "striped",
            "options": [
                "smooth",
                "rough",
                "practical"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uslub",
            "RightAnswer": "style",
            "options": [
                "sleeve",
                "silk",
                "shape"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mos kelmoq; kostyum",
            "RightAnswer": "suit",
            "options": [
                "notice",
                "design",
                "taste"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mos",
            "RightAnswer": "suitable",
            "options": [
                "striped",
                "smooth",
                "rough"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yirtmoq; yirtiq",
            "RightAnswer": "tear",
            "options": [
                "suit",
                "notice",
                "design"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tor",
            "RightAnswer": "tight",
            "options": [
                "suitable",
                "striped",
                "smooth"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "asbob",
            "RightAnswer": "tool",
            "options": [
                "style",
                "sleeve",
                "silk"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kesib olib tashlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "cut off",
            "options": [
                "stand up",
                "sit down",
                "put on"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tugmachani yopmoq, fermuarni tortmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "do up",
            "options": [
                "cut off",
                "stand up",
                "sit down"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "to‘ldirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "fill up",
            "options": [
                "do up",
                "cut off",
                "stand up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kiymoq (kiyim)",
            "RightAnswer": "have on",
            "options": [
                "fill up",
                "do up",
                "cut off"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tashlab ketmoq, qoldirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "leave out",
            "options": [
                "have on",
                "fill up",
                "do up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kiyib olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "put on",
            "options": [
                "leave out",
                "have on",
                "fill up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yechmoq (kiyim)",
            "RightAnswer": "take off",
            "options": [
                "put on",
                "leave out",
                "have on"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kiyib ko‘rmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "try on",
            "options": [
                "take off",
                "put on",
                "leave out"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "orqasida",
            "RightAnswer": "at the back",
            "options": [
                "on a diet",
                "in shape",
                "in comparison to"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oxirida",
            "RightAnswer": "at the end",
            "options": [
                "at the back",
                "on a diet",
                "in shape"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "modada",
            "RightAnswer": "in fashion/style",
            "options": [
                "at the end",
                "at the back",
                "on a diet"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oldida",
            "RightAnswer": "in front",
            "options": [
                "in fashion/style",
                "at the end",
                "at the back"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "burchagida",
            "RightAnswer": "in the corner",
            "options": [
                "in front",
                "in fashion/style",
                "at the end"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "modadan chiqqan",
            "RightAnswer": "out of fashion/style",
            "options": [
                "in the corner",
                "in front",
                "in fashion/style"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "san’at",
            "RightAnswer": "art",
            "options": [
                "tool",
                "style",
                "sleeve"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rassom",
            "RightAnswer": "artist",
            "options": [
                "art",
                "tool",
                "style"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "san’atkorona",
            "RightAnswer": "artistic",
            "options": [
                "tight",
                "suitable",
                "striped"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sindirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "break",
            "options": [
                "stretch",
                "match",
                "maintain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "siniq",
            "RightAnswer": "broke, broken",
            "options": [
                "peaceful(ly)",
                "noisy, noisily",
                "online"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "(sinmaydigan) sinadigan",
            "RightAnswer": "(un)breakable",
            "options": [
                "artistic",
                "tight",
                "suitable"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yaratmoq (asar)",
            "RightAnswer": "compose",
            "options": [
                "break",
                "stretch",
                "match"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kompozitsiya",
            "RightAnswer": "composition",
            "options": [
                "artist",
                "art",
                "tool"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bastakor",
            "RightAnswer": "composer",
            "options": [
                "composition",
                "artist",
                "art"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko‘rsatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "exhibit",
            "options": [
                "compose",
                "break",
                "stretch"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko‘rgazma",
            "RightAnswer": "exhibition",
            "options": [
                "composer",
                "composition",
                "artist"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ozod",
            "RightAnswer": "free",
            "options": [
                "(un)breakable",
                "artistic",
                "tight"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "erkinlik",
            "RightAnswer": "freedom",
            "options": [
                "exhibition",
                "composer",
                "composition"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo‘l",
            "RightAnswer": "hand",
            "options": [
                "freedom",
                "exhibition",
                "composer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bir chimdim (kichik miqdor)",
            "RightAnswer": "handful",
            "options": [
                "hand",
                "freedom",
                "exhibition"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tutqich, boshqarmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "handle",
            "options": [
                "routine",
                "criminal",
                "plastic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tasavvur qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "imagine",
            "options": [
                "exhibit",
                "compose",
                "break"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tasavvur",
            "RightAnswer": "imagination",
            "options": [
                "handful",
                "hand",
                "freedom"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tasavvurga boy",
            "RightAnswer": "imaginative",
            "options": [
                "free",
                "(un)breakable",
                "artistic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aqlli",
            "RightAnswer": "intelligent",
            "options": [
                "imaginative",
                "free",
                "(un)breakable"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "aql-idrok",
            "RightAnswer": "intelligence",
            "options": [
                "imagination",
                "handful",
                "hand"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mukammal",
            "RightAnswer": "perfect",
            "options": [
                "intelligent",
                "imaginative",
                "free"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mukammallik",
            "RightAnswer": "perfection",
            "options": [
                "intelligence",
                "imagination",
                "handful"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nomukammal",
            "RightAnswer": "imperfect",
            "options": [
                "perfect",
                "intelligent",
                "imaginative"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tayyorlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "prepare",
            "options": [
                "imagine",
                "exhibit",
                "compose"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tayyorlov",
            "RightAnswer": "preparation",
            "options": [
                "perfection",
                "intelligence",
                "imagination"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hayron qolgan",
            "RightAnswer": "amazed at/by",
            "options": [
                "pleased with",
                "covered in",
                "allergic to"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko‘ngli qolgani",
            "RightAnswer": "disappointed with",
            "options": [
                "amazed at/by",
                "pleased with",
                "covered in"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tanish",
            "RightAnswer": "familiar with",
            "options": [
                "disappointed with",
                "amazed at/by",
                "pleased with"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jalb qilingan",
            "RightAnswer": "involved in",
            "options": [
                "familiar with",
                "disappointed with",
                "amazed at/by"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o‘xshash",
            "RightAnswer": "similar to",
            "options": [
                "involved in",
                "familiar with",
                "disappointed with"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...dan ...ga aylantirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "change sth (from sth) into",
            "options": [
                "complain (to sb) about",
                "combine sth with",
                "smell of"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "... sifatida tasvirlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "describe sth as",
            "options": [
                "change sth (from sth) into",
                "complain (to sb) about",
                "combine sth with"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tushuntirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "explain sth to",
            "options": [
                "describe sth as",
                "change sth (from sth) into",
                "complain (to sb) about"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kimnidir eslatmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "remind sb of",
            "options": [
                "explain sth to",
                "describe sth as",
                "change sth (from sth) into"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "olib tashlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "remove sth from",
            "options": [
                "remind sb of",
                "explain sth to",
                "describe sth as"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ta’sir",
            "RightAnswer": "an influence on",
            "options": [
                "a recipe for",
                "a cure for",
                "a kind of"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...ning rasmi",
            "RightAnswer": "a picture of",
            "options": [
                "an influence on",
                "a recipe for",
                "a cure for"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 12": [
        {
            "Question": "ajoyib",
            "RightAnswer": "amazing",
            "options": [
                "imperfect",
                "perfect",
                "intelligent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "iqlim",
            "RightAnswer": "climate",
            "options": [
                "preparation",
                "perfection",
                "intelligence"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qishloq hududi",
            "RightAnswer": "countryside",
            "options": [
                "climate",
                "preparation",
                "perfection"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "atrof-muhit",
            "RightAnswer": "environment",
            "options": [
                "countryside",
                "climate",
                "preparation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yo‘q bo‘lib ketgan",
            "RightAnswer": "extinct",
            "options": [
                "amazing",
                "imperfect",
                "perfect"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bashorat qilmoq; ob-havo bashorati",
            "RightAnswer": "forecast",
            "options": [
                "tear",
                "suit",
                "notice"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muzdek",
            "RightAnswer": "freezing",
            "options": [
                "extinct",
                "amazing",
                "imperfect"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "global",
            "RightAnswer": "global",
            "options": [
                "freezing",
                "extinct",
                "amazing"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "issiq to‘lqini",
            "RightAnswer": "heatwave",
            "options": [
                "environment",
                "countryside",
                "climate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hasharot",
            "RightAnswer": "insect",
            "options": [
                "heatwave",
                "environment",
                "countryside"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chaqmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "lightning",
            "options": [
                "insect",
                "heatwave",
                "environment"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "axlat tashlamoq; axlat",
            "RightAnswer": "litter",
            "options": [
                "forecast",
                "tear",
                "suit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mahalliy",
            "RightAnswer": "local",
            "options": [
                "global",
                "freezing",
                "extinct"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "joylashmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "locate",
            "options": [
                "prepare",
                "imagine",
                "exhibit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sut emizuvchi hayvon",
            "RightAnswer": "mammal",
            "options": [
                "lightning",
                "insect",
                "heatwave"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yumshoq (ob-havo)",
            "RightAnswer": "mild",
            "options": [
                "local",
                "global",
                "freezing"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nomlamoq; ism",
            "RightAnswer": "name",
            "options": [
                "litter",
                "forecast",
                "tear"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kelib chiqish",
            "RightAnswer": "origin",
            "options": [
                "mammal",
                "lightning",
                "insect"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sayyora",
            "RightAnswer": "planet",
            "options": [
                "origin",
                "mammal",
                "lightning"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "saqlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "preserve",
            "options": [
                "locate",
                "prepare",
                "imagine"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qayta ishlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "recycle",
            "options": [
                "preserve",
                "locate",
                "prepare"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sudralib yuruvchi",
            "RightAnswer": "reptile",
            "options": [
                "planet",
                "origin",
                "mammal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qutqarmoq; qutqarish",
            "RightAnswer": "rescue",
            "options": [
                "name",
                "litter",
                "forecast"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sun’iy yo‘ldosh",
            "RightAnswer": "satellite",
            "options": [
                "reptile",
                "planet",
                "origin"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qisqa yomg‘ir",
            "RightAnswer": "shower",
            "options": [
                "satellite",
                "reptile",
                "planet"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "Quyosh tizimi",
            "RightAnswer": "solar system",
            "options": [
                "bank account",
                "youth club",
                "identity card"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tur (biologik)",
            "RightAnswer": "species",
            "options": [
                "shower",
                "satellite",
                "reptile"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "momaqaldiroq",
            "RightAnswer": "thunder",
            "options": [
                "species",
                "shower",
                "satellite"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yovvoyi",
            "RightAnswer": "wild",
            "options": [
                "mild",
                "local",
                "global"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yovvoyi tabiat",
            "RightAnswer": "wildlife",
            "options": [
                "thunder",
                "species",
                "shower"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "portlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "blow up",
            "options": [
                "try on",
                "take off",
                "put on"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko‘paymoq, ortmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "build up",
            "options": [
                "blow up",
                "try on",
                "take off"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tozalamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "clear up",
            "options": [
                "build up",
                "blow up",
                "try on"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o‘chib qolmoq (olov)",
            "RightAnswer": "go out",
            "options": [
                "clear up",
                "build up",
                "blow up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kirishni oldini olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "keep out",
            "options": [
                "go out",
                "clear up",
                "build up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo‘yib yubormoq",
            "RightAnswer": "put down",
            "options": [
                "keep out",
                "go out",
                "clear up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o‘chirmoq (olov)",
            "RightAnswer": "put out",
            "options": [
                "put down",
                "keep out",
                "go out"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "devorga osmoq (masalan, rasm)",
            "RightAnswer": "put up",
            "options": [
                "put out",
                "put down",
                "keep out"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "eng ko‘pi bilan",
            "RightAnswer": "at most",
            "options": [
                "out of fashion/style",
                "in the corner",
                "in front"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tepasida/pastida",
            "RightAnswer": "at the top/bottom",
            "options": [
                "at most",
                "out of fashion/style",
                "in the corner"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "boshida",
            "RightAnswer": "in the beginning",
            "options": [
                "at the top/bottom",
                "at most",
                "out of fashion/style"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uzoqda",
            "RightAnswer": "in the distance",
            "options": [
                "in the beginning",
                "at the top/bottom",
                "at most"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jami",
            "RightAnswer": "in total",
            "options": [
                "in the distance",
                "in the beginning",
                "at the top/bottom"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tepasida",
            "RightAnswer": "on top",
            "options": [
                "in total",
                "in the distance",
                "in the beginning"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "markaz",
            "RightAnswer": "centre",
            "options": [
                "wildlife",
                "thunder",
                "species"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "markaziy",
            "RightAnswer": "central",
            "options": [
                "wild",
                "mild",
                "local"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "doira",
            "RightAnswer": "circle",
            "options": [
                "centre",
                "wildlife",
                "thunder"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "doirasimon",
            "RightAnswer": "circular",
            "options": [
                "central",
                "wild",
                "mild"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xavf",
            "RightAnswer": "danger",
            "options": [
                "circle",
                "centre",
                "wildlife"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xavfli",
            "RightAnswer": "dangerous",
            "options": [
                "circular",
                "central",
                "wild"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chuqur",
            "RightAnswer": "deep",
            "options": [
                "dangerous",
                "circular",
                "central"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chuqur tarzda",
            "RightAnswer": "deeply",
            "options": [
                "secretly",
                "certainly",
                "identically"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chuqurlik",
            "RightAnswer": "depth",
            "options": [
                "danger",
                "circle",
                "centre"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yo‘q qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "destroy",
            "options": [
                "recycle",
                "preserve",
                "locate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yo‘q qilish",
            "RightAnswer": "destruction",
            "options": [
                "depth",
                "danger",
                "circle"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "vayron qiluvchi",
            "RightAnswer": "destructive",
            "options": [
                "deep",
                "dangerous",
                "circular"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tuman",
            "RightAnswer": "fog",
            "options": [
                "destruction",
                "depth",
                "danger"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tumanga to‘la",
            "RightAnswer": "foggy",
            "options": [
                "destructive",
                "deep",
                "dangerous"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bog‘",
            "RightAnswer": "garden",
            "options": [
                "fog",
                "destruction",
                "depth"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bog‘bon",
            "RightAnswer": "gardener",
            "options": [
                "garden",
                "fog",
                "destruction"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bog‘dorchilik",
            "RightAnswer": "gardening",
            "options": [
                "gardener",
                "garden",
                "fog"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bostirib kirish",
            "RightAnswer": "invade",
            "options": [
                "destroy",
                "recycle",
                "preserve"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bosqin",
            "RightAnswer": "invasion",
            "options": [
                "gardening",
                "gardener",
                "garden"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bosqinchilar",
            "RightAnswer": "invader",
            "options": [
                "invasion",
                "gardening",
                "gardener"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tabiat",
            "RightAnswer": "nature",
            "options": [
                "invader",
                "invasion",
                "gardening"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tabiiy",
            "RightAnswer": "natural",
            "options": [
                "foggy",
                "destructive",
                "deep"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tabiiy ravishda",
            "RightAnswer": "naturally",
            "options": [
                "deeply",
                "secretly",
                "certainly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ifloslantirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "pollute",
            "options": [
                "invade",
                "destroy",
                "recycle"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ifloslanish",
            "RightAnswer": "pollution",
            "options": [
                "nature",
                "invader",
                "invasion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ifloslangan",
            "RightAnswer": "polluted",
            "options": [
                "natural",
                "foggy",
                "destructive"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo‘rqadigan",
            "RightAnswer": "afraid of",
            "options": [
                "similar to",
                "involved in",
                "familiar with"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xabardor",
            "RightAnswer": "aware of",
            "options": [
                "afraid of",
                "similar to",
                "involved in"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qiziqqan",
            "RightAnswer": "enthusiastic about",
            "options": [
                "aware of",
                "afraid of",
                "similar to"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jiddiy",
            "RightAnswer": "serious about",
            "options": [
                "enthusiastic about",
                "aware of",
                "afraid of"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yetishmovchilik",
            "RightAnswer": "short of",
            "options": [
                "serious about",
                "enthusiastic about",
                "aware of"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qochib qutulmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "escape from",
            "options": [
                "remove sth from",
                "remind sb of",
                "explain sth to"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kimnidir ...dan saqlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "prevent sb from",
            "options": [
                "escape from",
                "remove sth from",
                "remind sb of"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...ni ...dan qutqarmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "save sth from",
            "options": [
                "prevent sb from",
                "escape from",
                "remove sth from"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "haqida o‘ylamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "think about",
            "options": [
                "save sth from",
                "prevent sb from",
                "escape from"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xavotirlanmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "worry about",
            "options": [
                "think about",
                "save sth from",
                "prevent sb from"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...ga zarar",
            "RightAnswer": "damage to",
            "options": [
                "a picture of",
                "an influence on",
                "a recipe for"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...ning ko‘payishi",
            "RightAnswer": "an increase in",
            "options": [
                "damage to",
                "a picture of",
                "an influence on"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 13": [
        {
            "Question": "kulgili",
            "RightAnswer": "amusing",
            "options": [
                "polluted",
                "natural",
                "foggy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jahli chiqarmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "annoy",
            "options": [
                "pollute",
                "invade",
                "destroy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "munosabat",
            "RightAnswer": "attitude",
            "options": [
                "pollution",
                "nature",
                "invader"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jahlil, badjahl",
            "RightAnswer": "bad-tempered",
            "options": [
                "amusing",
                "polluted",
                "natural"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "o‘zini tutmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "behave",
            "options": [
                "annoy",
                "pollute",
                "invade"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bezorilik qilmoq; bezori",
            "RightAnswer": "bully",
            "options": [
                "rescue",
                "name",
                "litter"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sokin",
            "RightAnswer": "calm",
            "options": [
                "bad-tempered",
                "amusing",
                "polluted"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nishonlamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "celebrate",
            "options": [
                "behave",
                "annoy",
                "pollute"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xarakter",
            "RightAnswer": "character",
            "options": [
                "attitude",
                "pollution",
                "nature"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tushkun",
            "RightAnswer": "depressed",
            "options": [
                "calm",
                "bad-tempered",
                "amusing"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "noqulay vaziyat",
            "RightAnswer": "embarrassing",
            "options": [
                "character",
                "attitude",
                "pollution"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hissiyot",
            "RightAnswer": "emotion",
            "options": [
                "embarrassing",
                "character",
                "attitude"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qiziqqan, ishtiyoqmand",
            "RightAnswer": "enthusiastic",
            "options": [
                "depressed",
                "calm",
                "bad-tempered"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "his",
            "RightAnswer": "feeling",
            "options": [
                "emotion",
                "embarrassing",
                "character"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xursand",
            "RightAnswer": "glad",
            "options": [
                "enthusiastic",
                "depressed",
                "calm"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jarohat yetkazmoq; og‘riqli",
            "RightAnswer": "hurt",
            "options": [
                "get rid of",
                "tell a joke",
                "have an operation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "baxtsiz, g‘amgin",
            "RightAnswer": "miserable",
            "options": [
                "glad",
                "enthusiastic",
                "depressed"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sho‘x, quvnoq (yomon ahloqli bolalar uchun)",
            "RightAnswer": "naughty",
            "options": [
                "miserable",
                "glad",
                "enthusiastic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shovqinli",
            "RightAnswer": "noisy",
            "options": [
                "naughty",
                "miserable",
                "glad"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "odobli",
            "RightAnswer": "polite",
            "options": [
                "noisy",
                "naughty",
                "miserable"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "javob bermoq (reaktsiya qilmoq)",
            "RightAnswer": "react",
            "options": [
                "celebrate",
                "behave",
                "annoy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "afsuslanmoq; afsus",
            "RightAnswer": "regret",
            "options": [
                "bully",
                "rescue",
                "name"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kulgili, bema’ni",
            "RightAnswer": "ridiculous",
            "options": [
                "polite",
                "noisy",
                "naughty"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "romantik",
            "RightAnswer": "romantic",
            "options": [
                "ridiculous",
                "polite",
                "noisy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo‘pol",
            "RightAnswer": "rude",
            "options": [
                "romantic",
                "ridiculous",
                "polite"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hazil tuyg‘usi",
            "RightAnswer": "sense of humour",
            "options": [
                "solar system",
                "bank account",
                "youth club"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uyatchan",
            "RightAnswer": "shy",
            "options": [
                "rude",
                "romantic",
                "ridiculous"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "stress",
            "RightAnswer": "stress",
            "options": [
                "feeling",
                "emotion",
                "embarrassing"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "latifa aytmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "tell a joke",
            "options": [
                "have an operation",
                "take an exam",
                "make sure"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xafa qilmoq; xafa",
            "RightAnswer": "upset",
            "options": [
                "hurt",
                "get rid of",
                "tell a joke"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tinchlanmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "calm down",
            "options": [
                "put up",
                "put out",
                "put down"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xursand bo‘lmoq, kayfiyatini ko‘tarmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "cheer up",
            "options": [
                "calm down",
                "put up",
                "put out"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shoshilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "come on",
            "options": [
                "cheer up",
                "calm down",
                "put up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "davom ettirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "go on",
            "options": [
                "come on",
                "cheer up",
                "calm down"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kutib turmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "hang on",
            "options": [
                "go on",
                "come on",
                "cheer up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qochib ketmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "run away (from)",
            "options": [
                "hang on",
                "go on",
                "come on"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jim bo‘lmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "shut up",
            "options": [
                "run away (from)",
                "hang on",
                "go on"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "balandroq gapirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "speak up",
            "options": [
                "shut up",
                "run away (from)",
                "hang on"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "avval",
            "RightAnswer": "at first",
            "options": [
                "on top",
                "in total",
                "in the distance"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hech bo‘lmaganda",
            "RightAnswer": "at least",
            "options": [
                "at first",
                "on top",
                "in total"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ba’zida",
            "RightAnswer": "at times",
            "options": [
                "at least",
                "at first",
                "on top"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yashirincha",
            "RightAnswer": "in secret",
            "options": [
                "at times",
                "at least",
                "at first"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...ga qaramasdan",
            "RightAnswer": "in spite of",
            "options": [
                "in secret",
                "at times",
                "at least"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko‘z yosh bilan",
            "RightAnswer": "in tears",
            "options": [
                "in spite of",
                "in secret",
                "at times"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zeriktirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "bore",
            "options": [
                "react",
                "celebrate",
                "behave"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zerikarli, zerikkan",
            "RightAnswer": "boring, bored",
            "options": [
                "shy",
                "rude",
                "romantic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "komediya",
            "RightAnswer": "comedy",
            "options": [
                "stress",
                "feeling",
                "emotion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "komik (kulgi ustasi)",
            "RightAnswer": "comedian",
            "options": [
                "comedy",
                "stress",
                "feeling"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "his-tuyg‘u",
            "RightAnswer": "emotion",
            "options": [
                "comedian",
                "comedy",
                "stress"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hissiy",
            "RightAnswer": "emotional",
            "options": [
                "boring, bored",
                "shy",
                "rude"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "energiya",
            "RightAnswer": "energy",
            "options": [
                "emotion",
                "comedian",
                "comedy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "energiyaga boy",
            "RightAnswer": "energetic",
            "options": [
                "emotional",
                "boring, bored",
                "shy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hayajonlantirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "excite",
            "options": [
                "bore",
                "react",
                "celebrate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hayajon",
            "RightAnswer": "excitement",
            "options": [
                "energy",
                "emotion",
                "comedian"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hayajonli, hayajonlangan",
            "RightAnswer": "exciting, excited",
            "options": [
                "energetic",
                "emotional",
                "boring, bored"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sezmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "feel",
            "options": [
                "excite",
                "bore",
                "react"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sezdi",
            "RightAnswer": "felt",
            "options": [
                "spoke",
                "forgave",
                "flew"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "his-tuyg‘ular",
            "RightAnswer": "feeling",
            "options": [
                "excitement",
                "energy",
                "emotion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "baxtli",
            "RightAnswer": "happy",
            "options": [
                "exciting, excited",
                "energetic",
                "emotional"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "baxtsiz",
            "RightAnswer": "unhappy",
            "options": [
                "happy",
                "exciting, excited",
                "energetic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "baxt",
            "RightAnswer": "happiness",
            "options": [
                "feeling",
                "excitement",
                "energy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yomon ko‘rmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "hate",
            "options": [
                "feel",
                "excite",
                "bore"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nafrat",
            "RightAnswer": "hatred",
            "options": [
                "happiness",
                "feeling",
                "excitement"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shovqin",
            "RightAnswer": "noise",
            "options": [
                "hatred",
                "happiness",
                "feeling"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shovqinli, shovqin bilan",
            "RightAnswer": "noisy, noisily",
            "options": [
                "online",
                "nearby",
                "sure about/of"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hamdardlik",
            "RightAnswer": "sympathy",
            "options": [
                "noise",
                "hatred",
                "happiness"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hamdard bo‘lmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "sympathise",
            "options": [
                "hate",
                "feel",
                "excite"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hamdard",
            "RightAnswer": "sympathetic",
            "options": [
                "unhappy",
                "happy",
                "exciting, excited"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "uyalgan",
            "RightAnswer": "ashamed of",
            "options": [
                "short of",
                "serious about",
                "enthusiastic about"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "noqulay holatda",
            "RightAnswer": "embarrassed about",
            "options": [
                "ashamed of",
                "short of",
                "serious about"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qo‘rqadigan",
            "RightAnswer": "scared of",
            "options": [
                "embarrassed about",
                "ashamed of",
                "short of"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...dan xursand",
            "RightAnswer": "happy about",
            "options": [
                "scared of",
                "embarrassed about",
                "ashamed of"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "asabi qitiqlangan",
            "RightAnswer": "nervous about",
            "options": [
                "happy about",
                "scared of",
                "embarrassed about"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "afsuslangan",
            "RightAnswer": "sorry about/for",
            "options": [
                "nervous about",
                "happy about",
                "scared of"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "hayron qolgan",
            "RightAnswer": "surprised at/by",
            "options": [
                "sorry about/for",
                "nervous about",
                "happy about"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "charchagan",
            "RightAnswer": "tired of",
            "options": [
                "surprised at/by",
                "sorry about/for",
                "nervous about"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kimnidir tabriklamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "congratulate sb on",
            "options": [
                "worry about",
                "think about",
                "save sth from"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ustidan kulmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "laugh at",
            "options": [
                "congratulate sb on",
                "worry about",
                "think about"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "... haqidagi latifa",
            "RightAnswer": "a joke about",
            "options": [
                "an increase in",
                "damage to",
                "a picture of"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 14": [
        {
            "Question": "baxtsiz hodisa",
            "RightAnswer": "accident",
            "options": [
                "sympathy",
                "noise",
                "hatred"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taxmin qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "assume",
            "options": [
                "sympathise",
                "hate",
                "feel"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "sabab bo‘lmoq; sabab",
            "RightAnswer": "cause",
            "options": [
                "regret",
                "bully",
                "rescue"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "da’vo qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "claim",
            "options": [
                "assume",
                "sympathise",
                "hate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shikoyat qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "complain",
            "options": [
                "claim",
                "assume",
                "sympathise"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishontirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "convince",
            "options": [
                "complain",
                "claim",
                "assume"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tanqid qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "criticise",
            "options": [
                "convince",
                "complain",
                "claim"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "inkor qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "deny",
            "options": [
                "criticise",
                "convince",
                "complain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muhokama",
            "RightAnswer": "discussion",
            "options": [
                "accident",
                "sympathy",
                "noise"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "shubha qilmoq; shubha",
            "RightAnswer": "doubt",
            "options": [
                "cause",
                "regret",
                "bully"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ruhlantirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "encourage",
            "options": [
                "deny",
                "criticise",
                "convince"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qutulmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "get rid of",
            "options": [
                "tell a joke",
                "have an operation",
                "take an exam"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "g‘iybat qilmoq; g‘iybat",
            "RightAnswer": "gossip",
            "options": [
                "doubt",
                "cause",
                "regret"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ideal",
            "RightAnswer": "ideal",
            "options": [
                "sympathetic",
                "unhappy",
                "happy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "haqorat qilmoq; haqorat",
            "RightAnswer": "insult",
            "options": [
                "gossip",
                "doubt",
                "cause"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tergov qilmoq, o‘rganmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "investigate",
            "options": [
                "encourage",
                "deny",
                "criticise"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "salbiy",
            "RightAnswer": "negative",
            "options": [
                "ideal",
                "sympathetic",
                "unhappy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ijobiy",
            "RightAnswer": "positive",
            "options": [
                "negative",
                "ideal",
                "sympathetic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maqtamoq; maqtov",
            "RightAnswer": "praise",
            "options": [
                "insult",
                "gossip",
                "doubt"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ko‘rsatmoq (go‘yoki qilyapti)",
            "RightAnswer": "pretend",
            "options": [
                "investigate",
                "encourage",
                "deny"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maqsad",
            "RightAnswer": "purpose",
            "options": [
                "discussion",
                "accident",
                "sympathy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rad etmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "refuse",
            "options": [
                "pretend",
                "investigate",
                "encourage"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "natija bermoq; natija",
            "RightAnswer": "result",
            "options": [
                "praise",
                "insult",
                "gossip"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mish-mish",
            "RightAnswer": "rumour",
            "options": [
                "purpose",
                "discussion",
                "accident"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "oqilona",
            "RightAnswer": "sensible",
            "options": [
                "positive",
                "negative",
                "ideal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "jiddiy",
            "RightAnswer": "serious",
            "options": [
                "sensible",
                "positive",
                "negative"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "zaxira",
            "RightAnswer": "spare",
            "options": [
                "serious",
                "sensible",
                "positive"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "nazariya",
            "RightAnswer": "theory",
            "options": [
                "rumour",
                "purpose",
                "discussion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "fikr",
            "RightAnswer": "thought",
            "options": [
                "theory",
                "rumour",
                "purpose"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ogohlantirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "warn",
            "options": [
                "refuse",
                "pretend",
                "investigate"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "kiyimlarni shkafga ilib qo‘ymoq",
            "RightAnswer": "hang up",
            "options": [
                "speak up",
                "shut up",
                "run away (from)"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yerda/tanadan ko‘tarib olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "pick up",
            "options": [
                "hang up",
                "speak up",
                "shut up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "joyiga qaytarmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "put back",
            "options": [
                "pick up",
                "hang up",
                "speak up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tugamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "run out",
            "options": [
                "put back",
                "pick up",
                "hang up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bo‘lib bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "share out",
            "options": [
                "run out",
                "put back",
                "pick up"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muammoni hal qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "sort out",
            "options": [
                "share out",
                "run out",
                "put back"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ehtiyot bo‘lmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "watch out",
            "options": [
                "sort out",
                "share out",
                "run out"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yechim topmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "work out",
            "options": [
                "watch out",
                "sort out",
                "share out"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tasodifan/xato bilan",
            "RightAnswer": "by accident/mistake",
            "options": [
                "in tears",
                "in spite of",
                "in secret"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tartibsizlikda",
            "RightAnswer": "in a mess",
            "options": [
                "by accident/mistake",
                "in tears",
                "in spite of"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "xavf ostida",
            "RightAnswer": "in danger",
            "options": [
                "in a mess",
                "by accident/mistake",
                "in tears"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mening fikrimcha",
            "RightAnswer": "in my view",
            "options": [
                "in danger",
                "in a mess",
                "by accident/mistake"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muammo ichida",
            "RightAnswer": "in trouble",
            "options": [
                "in my view",
                "in danger",
                "in a mess"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "bosim ostida",
            "RightAnswer": "under pressure",
            "options": [
                "in trouble",
                "in my view",
                "in danger"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maslahat",
            "RightAnswer": "advice",
            "options": [
                "thought",
                "theory",
                "rumour"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maslahat bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "advise",
            "options": [
                "warn",
                "refuse",
                "pretend"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "maslahatchi",
            "RightAnswer": "adviser",
            "options": [
                "advice",
                "thought",
                "theory"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chalkashtirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "confuse",
            "options": [
                "advise",
                "warn",
                "refuse"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chalkashgan",
            "RightAnswer": "confused",
            "options": [
                "spare",
                "serious",
                "sensible"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "chalkashlik",
            "RightAnswer": "confusion",
            "options": [
                "adviser",
                "advice",
                "thought"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "mustasno qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "except",
            "options": [
                "confuse",
                "advise",
                "warn"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "istisno",
            "RightAnswer": "exception",
            "options": [
                "confusion",
                "adviser",
                "advice"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yordam bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "help",
            "options": [
                "except",
                "confuse",
                "advise"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "foydali",
            "RightAnswer": "helpful",
            "options": [
                "confused",
                "spare",
                "serious"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ojiz",
            "RightAnswer": "helpless",
            "options": [
                "helpful",
                "confused",
                "spare"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "omad",
            "RightAnswer": "luck",
            "options": [
                "exception",
                "confusion",
                "adviser"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "omadli",
            "RightAnswer": "lucky",
            "options": [
                "helpless",
                "helpful",
                "confused"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "omadsiz",
            "RightAnswer": "unlucky",
            "options": [
                "lucky",
                "helpless",
                "helpful"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "baxtga qarshi",
            "RightAnswer": "luckily",
            "options": [
                "naturally",
                "deeply",
                "secretly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "afzal ko‘rmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "prefer",
            "options": [
                "help",
                "except",
                "confuse"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "afzallik",
            "RightAnswer": "preference",
            "options": [
                "luck",
                "exception",
                "confusion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "afzalroq",
            "RightAnswer": "preferable",
            "options": [
                "unlucky",
                "lucky",
                "helpless"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tavsiya qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "recommend",
            "options": [
                "prefer",
                "help",
                "except"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tavsiya",
            "RightAnswer": "recommendation",
            "options": [
                "preference",
                "luck",
                "exception"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rad qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "refuse",
            "options": [
                "recommend",
                "prefer",
                "help"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "rad etish",
            "RightAnswer": "refusal",
            "options": [
                "recommendation",
                "preference",
                "luck"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yechmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "solve",
            "options": [
                "refuse",
                "recommend",
                "prefer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "yechim",
            "RightAnswer": "solution",
            "options": [
                "refusal",
                "recommendation",
                "preference"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taklif qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "suggest",
            "options": [
                "solve",
                "refuse",
                "recommend"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "taklif",
            "RightAnswer": "suggestion",
            "options": [
                "solution",
                "refusal",
                "recommendation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishonchli",
            "RightAnswer": "sure about/of",
            "options": [
                "tired of",
                "surprised at/by",
                "sorry about/for"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "tasodifan yuz bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "happen to",
            "options": [
                "laugh at",
                "congratulate sb on",
                "worry about"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "qarshi maslahat bermoq",
            "RightAnswer": "advise against",
            "options": [
                "happen to",
                "laugh at",
                "congratulate sb on"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "... bilan haqida kelishmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "agree (with sb) about",
            "options": [
                "advise against",
                "happen to",
                "laugh at"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ma’qullamoq",
            "RightAnswer": "approve of",
            "options": [
                "agree (with sb) about",
                "advise against",
                "happen to"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "ishonmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "believe in",
            "options": [
                "approve of",
                "agree (with sb) about",
                "advise against"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "muomala qilmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "deal with",
            "options": [
                "believe in",
                "approve of",
                "agree (with sb) about"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...ni ...dan yashirmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "hide sth from sb",
            "options": [
                "deal with",
                "believe in",
                "approve of"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "turib olmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "insist on",
            "options": [
                "hide sth from sb",
                "deal with",
                "believe in"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "suyanmoq",
            "RightAnswer": "rely on",
            "options": [
                "insist on",
                "hide sth from sb",
                "deal with"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...ning afzalligi",
            "RightAnswer": "an advantage of",
            "options": [
                "a joke about",
                "an increase in",
                "damage to"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "...ga yechim",
            "RightAnswer": "a solution to",
            "options": [
                "an advantage of",
                "a joke about",
                "an increase in"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "level 15" : [
{ Question: "dengiz sayohati", RightAnswer: "voyage", options: ["make yourself at home", "steal the show", "under the weather"]},
{ Question: "safar", RightAnswer: "journey", options: ["voyage", "make yourself at home", "steal the show"]},
{ Question: "sayohat", RightAnswer: "trip", options: ["journey", "voyage", "make yourself at home"]},
{ Question: "sayohat qilish", RightAnswer: "travel", options: ["grown-up", "vegan", "vegetarian"]},
{ Question: "ekskursiya", RightAnswer: "excursion", options: ["trip", "journey", "voyage"]},
{ Question: "yo‘l haqi", RightAnswer: "fare", options: ["excursion", "trip", "journey"]},
{ Question: "chipta", RightAnswer: "ticket", options: ["fare", "excursion", "trip"]},
{ Question: "to‘lov", RightAnswer: "fee", options: ["ticket", "fare", "excursion"]},
{ Question: "yashamoq", RightAnswer: "live", options: ["out of work", "on duty", "in business"]},
{ Question: "turmoq", RightAnswer: "stay", options: ["live", "out of work", "on duty"]},
{ Question: "manzara", RightAnswer: "view", options: ["fee", "ticket", "fare"]},
{ Question: "ko‘rish joyi", RightAnswer: "sight", options: ["view", "fee", "ticket"]},
{ Question: "o‘tib yubormoq", RightAnswer: "miss", options: ["stay", "live", "out of work"]},
{ Question: "yo‘qotmoq", RightAnswer: "lose", options: ["miss", "stay", "live"]},
{ Question: "chegara", RightAnswer: "border", options: ["sight", "view", "fee"]},
{ Question: "chekka", RightAnswer: "edge", options: ["border", "sight", "view"]},
{ Question: "chiziq", RightAnswer: "line", options: ["edge", "border", "sight"]},
{ Question: "dunyo", RightAnswer: "world", options: ["line", "edge", "border"]},
{ Question: "Yer", RightAnswer: "earth", options: ["world", "line", "edge"]},
{ Question: "olmoq", RightAnswer: "take", options: ["lose", "miss", "stay"]},
{ Question: "olib kelmoq", RightAnswer: "bring", options: ["take", "lose", "miss"]},
{ Question: "bormoq", RightAnswer: "go", options: ["bring", "take", "lose"]},
{ Question: "uzunlik", RightAnswer: "length", options: ["earth", "world", "line"]},
{ Question: "masofa", RightAnswer: "distance", options: ["length", "earth", "world"]},
{ Question: "hudud", RightAnswer: "area", options: ["distance", "length", "earth"]},
{ Question: "yer maydoni", RightAnswer: "territory", options: ["area", "distance", "length"]},
{ Question: "band qilmoq", RightAnswer: "book", options: ["go", "bring", "take"]},
{ Question: "saqlamoq", RightAnswer: "keep", options: ["book", "go", "bring"]},
{ Question: "gid", RightAnswer: "guide", options: ["territory", "area", "distance"]},
{ Question: "yetaklamoq", RightAnswer: "lead", options: ["keep", "book", "go"]},
{ Question: "fasl", RightAnswer: "season", options: ["guide", "territory", "area"]},
{ Question: "davr", RightAnswer: "period", options: ["season", "guide", "territory"]},
{ Question: "yetib kelmoq", RightAnswer: "arrive", options: ["lead", "keep", "book"]},
{ Question: "yetib bormoq", RightAnswer: "reach", options: ["arrive", "lead", "keep"]},
{ Question: "vatandosh", RightAnswer: "native", options: ["place of work", "job advert", "job offer"]},
{ Question: "uy", RightAnswer: "home", options: ["period", "season", "guide"]},
{ Question: "yetib olmoq", RightAnswer: "catch up with", options: ["work as", "train to do", "specialise in st"]},
{ Question: "ro‘yxatdan o‘tmoq (mehmonxona/aeroportda)", RightAnswer: "check in", options: ["catch up with", "work as", "train to do"]},
{ Question: "chiqib ketmoq; tekshirmoq", RightAnswer: "check out", options: ["check in", "catch up with", "work as"]},
{ Question: "tushirib qo‘ymoq; uxlab qolmoq", RightAnswer: "drop off", options: ["check out", "check in", "catch up with"]},
{ Question: "qaytib kelmoq", RightAnswer: "get back", options: ["drop off", "check out", "check in"]},
{ Question: "ta’tilga chiqmoq", RightAnswer: "go away", options: ["get back", "drop off", "check out"]},
{ Question: "tezlikka yetishmoq", RightAnswer: "keep up with", options: ["go away", "get back", "drop off"]},
{ Question: "yo‘l olmoq", RightAnswer: "make for", options: ["keep up with", "go away", "get back"]},
{ Question: "olib ketmoq", RightAnswer: "pick up", options: ["make for", "keep up with", "go away"]},
{ Question: "chetga to‘xtamoq", RightAnswer: "pull in", options: ["pick up", "make for", "keep up with"]},
{ Question: "mashina urib yubormoq", RightAnswer: "run over", options: ["pull in", "pick up", "make for"]},
{ Question: "kuzatib qo‘ymoq", RightAnswer: "see off", options: ["run over", "pull in", "pick up"]},
{ Question: "sayohat boshlamoq", RightAnswer: "set out", options: ["see off", "run over", "pull in"]},
{ Question: "havoga ko‘tarilmoq", RightAnswer: "take off", options: ["set out", "see off", "run over"]},
{ Question: "orqaga qaytmoq", RightAnswer: "turn round", options: ["take off", "set out", "see off"]},
{ Question: "avariyaga uchramoq", RightAnswer: "have an accident", options: ["wrote", "supervise", "qualify"]},
{ Question: "avariyada qatnashmoq", RightAnswer: "be (involved) in an accident", options: ["have an accident", "wrote", "supervise"]},
{ Question: "tasodifan qilmoq", RightAnswer: "do sth by accident", options: ["be (involved) in an accident", "have an accident", "wrote"]},
{ Question: "oldindan", RightAnswer: "in advance", options: ["make redundant", "turn down", "take over"]},
{ Question: "tomon harakatlanmoq", RightAnswer: "advance to", options: ["do sth by accident", "be (involved) in an accident", "have an accident"]},
{ Question: "to‘g‘ridan-to‘g‘ri oldinga yurmoq", RightAnswer: "go straight ahead", options: ["advance to", "do sth by accident", "be (involved) in an accident"]},
{ Question: "boshlamoq, davom ettirmoq", RightAnswer: "go ahead", options: ["go straight ahead", "advance to", "do sth by accident"]},
{ Question: "kimdandir oldinda bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "be ahead", options: ["go ahead", "go straight ahead", "advance to"]},
{ Question: "yo‘nalishning o‘zgarishi", RightAnswer: "a change of direction", options: ["reason why", "be sb’s view that", "works"]},
{ Question: "...ning yo‘nalishida", RightAnswer: "in the direction of sth", options: ["in advance", "make redundant", "turn down"]},
{ Question: "shu tomonga", RightAnswer: "in this direction", options: ["in the direction of sth", "in advance", "make redundant"]},
{ Question: "birdan (aniq bilmasdan)", RightAnswer: "off the top of your head", options: ["in your interest to do", "last but not least", "enough is enough"]},
 { Question: "tomon yo‘l olmoq", RightAnswer: "head for", options: ["be ahead", "go ahead", "go straight ahead"]},
{ Question: "boshdan oyoq sevib qolmoq", RightAnswer: "head over heels (in love)", options: ["off the top of your head", "in your interest to do", "last but not least"]},
{ Question: "ta’tilga chiqmoq", RightAnswer: "go on holiday", options: ["head for", "be ahead", "go ahead"]},
{ Question: "ta’til qilmoq", RightAnswer: "take a holiday", options: ["go on holiday", "head for", "be ahead"]},
{ Question: "davlat bayrami", RightAnswer: "bank holiday", options: ["a change of direction", "reason why", "be sb’s view that"]},
{ Question: "chapga burilmoq", RightAnswer: "turn left", options: ["take a holiday", "go on holiday", "head for"]},
{ Question: "chap tomonda", RightAnswer: "on the left", options: ["in this direction", "in the direction of sth", "in advance"]},
{ Question: "chap tomonda", RightAnswer: "on the left-hand side", options: ["on the left", "in this direction", "in the direction of sth"]},
{ Question: "chap burchakda", RightAnswer: "in the left-hand corner", options: ["on the left-hand side", "on the left", "in this direction"]},
{ Question: "chap qo‘l bilan ishlovchi ", RightAnswer: "left-handed", options: ["necessary to do", "workable", "irresponsible"]},
{ Question: "marshrutni rejalashtirmoq", RightAnswer: "plan a route", options: ["turn left", "take a holiday", "go on holiday"]},
{ Question: "yo‘l tutmoq", RightAnswer: "take a route", options: ["plan a route", "turn left", "take a holiday"]},
{ Question: "diqqatga sazovor joylarni ko‘rmoq", RightAnswer: "see the sights", options: ["take a route", "plan a route", "turn left"]},
{ Question: "sayohatga chiqib ko‘rmoq", RightAnswer: "go sightseeing", options: ["see the sights", "take a route", "plan a route"]},
{ Question: "yuqori tezlikda", RightAnswer: "at high speed", options: ["in the left-hand corner", "on the left-hand side", "on the left"]},
{ Question: "keskin tezlashish", RightAnswer: "a burst of speed", options: ["bank holiday", "a change of direction", "reason why"]},
{ Question: "tezlik cheklovi", RightAnswer: "speed limit", options: ["a burst of speed", "bank holiday", "a change of direction"]},
{ Question: "(biror joyga) ekskursiyaga chiqmoq", RightAnswer: "take a tour around somewhere", options: ["go sightseeing", "see the sights", "take a route"]},
{ Question: "joyni aylanib chiqmoq", RightAnswer: "tour a place", options: ["take a tour around somewhere", "go sightseeing", "see the sights"]},
{ Question: "yo‘lboshlovchi", RightAnswer: "tour guide", options: ["speed limit", "a burst of speed", "bank holiday"]},
{ Question: "xizmat safari", RightAnswer: "business trip", options: ["tour guide", "speed limit", "a burst of speed"]},
{ Question: "maktab safari", RightAnswer: "school trip", options: ["business trip", "tour guide", "speed limit"]},
{ Question: "sayohatga chiqmoq", RightAnswer: "go on a trip", options: ["tour a place", "take a tour around somewhere", "go sightseeing"]},
{ Question: "sayohat qilmoq", RightAnswer: "take a trip", options: ["go on a trip", "tour a place", "take a tour around somewhere"]},
{ Question: "yo‘lni topmoq", RightAnswer: "find your way", options: ["take a trip", "go on a trip", "tour a place"]},
{ Question: "bir tomondan", RightAnswer: "in a way", options: ["at high speed", "in the left-hand corner", "on the left-hand side"]},
{ Question: "yo‘lda", RightAnswer: "on the way", options: ["in a way", "at high speed", "in the left-hand corner"]},
{ Question: "oxirigacha yetib bormoq", RightAnswer: "go all the way", options: ["find your way", "take a trip", "go on a trip"]},
{ Question: "qo‘rqmoq", RightAnswer: "afraid", options: ["rise", "raise", "work"]},
{ Question: "qilishdan qo‘rqmoq", RightAnswer: "afraid to do", options: ["afraid", "rise", "raise"]},
{ Question: "ko‘rinmoq", RightAnswer: "appear to be", options: ["afraid to do", "afraid", "rise"]},
{ Question: "uyushtirmoq", RightAnswer: "arrange sth", options: ["appear to be", "afraid to do", "afraid"]},
{ Question: "kimdir uchun tayyorlamoq", RightAnswer: "arrange for sb to do", options: ["arrange sth", "appear to be", "afraid to do"]},
{ Question: "yetib bormoq", RightAnswer: "arrive in", options: ["arrange for sb to do", "arrange sth", "appear to be"]},
{ Question: "davom ettirmoq", RightAnswer: "continue st", options: ["arrive in ", "arrange for sb to do", "arrange sth"]},
{ Question: "qilishni davom ettirmoq", RightAnswer: "continue to do", options: ["continue st", "arrive in ", "arrange for sb to do"]},
{ Question: "... bilan davom ettirmoq", RightAnswer: "continue with sth", options: ["continue to do", "continue st", "arrive in "]},
{ Question: "farq qilmoq", RightAnswer: "differ from", options: ["continue with sth", "continue to do", "continue st"]},
{ Question: "orzu qilmoq", RightAnswer: "dream about", options: ["differ from", "continue with sth", "continue to do"]},
{ Question: "taklif qilmoq", RightAnswer: "invite sb to do", options: ["dream about", "differ from", "continue with sth"]},
{ Question: "qiziqmoq", RightAnswer: "keen to do", options: ["invite sb to do", "dream about", "differ from"]},
{ Question: "...ga qiziqmoq", RightAnswer: "keen on", options: ["keen to do", "invite sb to do", "dream about"]},
{ Question: "yashamoq", RightAnswer: "live in ", options: ["keen on", "keen to do", "invite sb to do"]},
{ Question: "... bilan kun kechirmoq", RightAnswer: "live on sth", options: ["live in ", "keen on", "keen to do"]},
{ Question: "...dan afsuslanmoq", RightAnswer: "regret  doing", options: ["live on sth", "live in ", "keen on"]},
{ Question: "nimadir uchun afsuslanmoq", RightAnswer: "regret sth", options: ["regret  doing", "live on sth", "live in "]},
{ Question: "aytishga afsuslanmoq", RightAnswer: "regret to tell/inform", options: ["regret sth", "regret  doing", "live on sth"]},
{ Question: "o‘ylamoq", RightAnswer: "think of/about", options: ["regret to tell/inform", "regret sth", "regret  doing"]},
{ Question: "... haqida yozmoq", RightAnswer: "write about", options: ["think of/about", "regret to tell/inform", "regret sth"]},
{ Question: "...ga yozmoq", RightAnswer: "write to", options: ["write about", "think of/about", "regret to tell/inform"]},
{ Question: "yozib qo‘ymoq", RightAnswer: "write sth down", options: ["write to", "write about", "think of/about"]},
{ Question: "uyushtirmoq", RightAnswer: "arrange", options: ["reach", "arrive", "lead"]},
{ Question: "qayta uyushtirmoq", RightAnswer: "rearrange", options: ["arrange", "reach", "arrive"]},
{ Question: "kelishuv", RightAnswer: "arrangement", options: ["home", "period", "season"]},
{ Question: "yetib kelmoq", RightAnswer: "arrive", options: ["rearrange", "arrange", "reach"]},
{ Question: "kelish", RightAnswer: "arrival", options: ["arrangement", "home", "period"]},
{ Question: "keng", RightAnswer: "broad", options: ["natural", "false", "artificial"]},
{ Question: "kengaytirmoq", RightAnswer: "broaden", options: ["arrive", "rearrange", "arrange"]},
{ Question: "madaniyat", RightAnswer: "culture", options: ["arrival", "arrangement", "home"]},
{ Question: "madaniy", RightAnswer: "culturally", options: ["hard at work", "experienced in st", "short of money"]},
{ Question: "madaniyatli", RightAnswer: "cultured", options: ["broad", "natural", "false"]},
{ Question: "farq qilmoq", RightAnswer: "differ", options: ["broaden", "arrive", "rearrange"]},
{ Question: "farqli", RightAnswer: "different", options: ["cultured", "broad", "natural"]},
{ Question: "farq", RightAnswer: "difference", options: ["culture", "arrival", "arrangement"]},
{ Question: "yo‘naltirmoq", RightAnswer: "direct", options: ["differ", "broaden", "arrive"]},
{ Question: "bilvosita", RightAnswer: "indirect", options: ["different", "cultured", "broad"]},
{ Question: "yo‘nalish", RightAnswer: "direction", options: ["difference", "culture", "arrival"]},
{ Question: "direktor", RightAnswer: "director", options: ["direction", "difference", "culture"]},
{ Question: "to‘g‘ridan-to‘g‘ri", RightAnswer: "directly", options: ["culturally", "hard at work", "experienced in st"]},
{ Question: "uzoq", RightAnswer: "distant", options: ["indirect", "different", "cultured"]},
{ Question: "uzoqdan", RightAnswer: "distantly", options: ["directly", "culturally", "hard at work"]},
{ Question: "masofa", RightAnswer: "distance", options: ["director", "direction", "difference"]},
{ Question: "kirib bormoq", RightAnswer: "enter", options: ["direct", "differ", "broaden"]},
{ Question: "kirish joyi", RightAnswer: "entrance", options: ["distance", "director", "direction"]},
{ Question: "yashamoq", RightAnswer: "inhabit", options: ["enter", "direct", "differ"]},
{ Question: "yashovchi", RightAnswer: "inhabitant", options: ["entrance", "distance", "director"]},
{ Question: "suratga olmoq", RightAnswer: "photograph", options: ["inhabit", "enter", "direct"]},
{ Question: "fotografiya", RightAnswer: "photography", options: ["inhabitant", "entrance", "distance"]},
{ Question: "fotograf", RightAnswer: "photographer", options: ["photography", "inhabitant", "entrance"]},
{ Question: "fotografik", RightAnswer: "photographic", options: ["distant", "indirect", "different"]},
{ Question: "tanimoq", RightAnswer: "recognise", options: ["photograph", "inhabit", "enter"]},
{ Question: "taniladigan", RightAnswer: "recognisable", options: ["photographic", "distant", "indirect"]},
{ Question: "tan olish", RightAnswer: "recognition", options: ["photographer", "photography", "inhabitant"]},
{ Question: "vaqt", RightAnswer: "time", options: ["recognition", "photographer", "photography"]},
{ Question: "jadval", RightAnswer: "timetable", options: ["time", "recognition", "photographer"]},
{ Question: "tur", RightAnswer: "tour", options: ["timetable", "time", "recognition"]},
{ Question: "turizm", RightAnswer: "tourism", options: ["tour", "timetable", "time"]},
{ Question: "sayyoh", RightAnswer: "tourist", options: ["tourism", "tour", "timetable"]},
{ Question: "dunyo", RightAnswer: "world", options: ["tourist", "tourism", "tour"]},
{ Question: "butun dunyo bo‘ylab", RightAnswer: "worldwide", options: ["responsibly", "helpless", "useless"]}],
"level 16" : [
{ Question: "futbol maydoni", RightAnswer: "pitch", options: ["world", "tourist", "tourism"]},
{ Question: "yugurish yo‘lagi", RightAnswer: "track", options: ["pitch", "world", "tourist"]},
{ Question: "sport maydoni (tennis/basketbol)", RightAnswer: "court", options: ["track", "pitch", "world"]},
{ Question: "golf maydoni", RightAnswer: "course", options: ["court", "track", "pitch"]},
{ Question: "boks maydoni", RightAnswer: "ring", options: ["course", "court", "track"]},
{ Question: "muz maydoni", RightAnswer: "rink", options: ["ring", "course", "court"]},
{ Question: "hakam (tennis/beysbol)", RightAnswer: "umpire", options: ["rink", "ring", "course"]},
{ Question: "hakam (futbol)", RightAnswer: "referee", options: ["umpire", "rink", "ring"]},
{ Question: "sport", RightAnswer: "sport", options: ["referee", "umpire", "rink"]},
{ Question: "yengil atletika", RightAnswer: "athletics", options: ["sport", "referee", "umpire"]},
{ Question: "yutmoq", RightAnswer: "win", options: ["recognise", "photograph", "inhabit"]},
{ Question: "yengmoq", RightAnswer: "beat", options: ["win", "recognise", "photograph"]},
{ Question: "hisob qilmoq", RightAnswer: "score", options: ["beat", "win", "recognise"]},
{ Question: "final", RightAnswer: "final", options: ["athletics", "sport", "referee"]},
{ Question: "yakuniy sahna (tomosha)", RightAnswer: "finale", options: ["final", "athletics", "sport"]},
{ Question: "oxir", RightAnswer: "end", options: ["finale", "final", "athletics"]},
{ Question: "yakun", RightAnswer: "ending", options: ["end", "finale", "final"]},
{ Question: "tanaffus", RightAnswer: "interval", options: ["ending", "end", "finale"]},
{ Question: "o‘yin o‘rtasidagi tanaffus", RightAnswer: "half time", options: ["interval", "ending", "end"]},
{ Question: "o‘yin", RightAnswer: "play", options: ["travel", "grown-up", "vegan"]},
{ Question: "o‘yin", RightAnswer: "game", options: ["half time", "interval", "ending"]},
{ Question: "tayoq (kriket)", RightAnswer: "bat", options: ["game", "half time", "interval"]},
{ Question: "tayoq (xokkey)", RightAnswer: "stick", options: ["bat", "game", "half time"]},
{ Question: "tayoq (qarmoqli baliq ovlash)", RightAnswer: "rod", options: ["stick", "bat", "game"]},
{ Question: "raketka", RightAnswer: "racket", options: ["rod", "stick", "bat"]},
{ Question: "durang", RightAnswer: "draw", options: ["play", "travel", "grown-up"]},
{ Question: "teng", RightAnswer: "equal", options: ["recognisable", "photographic", "distant"]},
{ Question: "tomoshabin (stadion)", RightAnswer: "spectator", options: ["racket", "rod", "stick"]},
{ Question: "tomoshabin", RightAnswer: "viewer", options: ["spectator", "racket", "rod"]},
{ Question: "havaskor", RightAnswer: "amateur", options: ["native", "place of work", "job advert"]},
{ Question: "professional", RightAnswer: "professional", options: ["amateur", "native", "place of work"]},
{ Question: "raqib", RightAnswer: "competitor", options: ["viewer", "spectator", "racket"]},
{ Question: "raqib", RightAnswer: "opponent", options: ["competitor", "viewer", "spectator"]},
{ Question: "vaqtini oldinga surmoq", RightAnswer: "bring forward", options: ["turn round", "take off", "set out"]},
{ Question: "davom ettirmoq", RightAnswer: "carry on", options: ["bring forward", "turn round", "take off"]},
{ Question: "nihoyat boshlamoq", RightAnswer: "get round to", options: ["carry on", "bring forward", "turn round"]},
{ Question: "yomon ish qilmoq", RightAnswer: "get up to", options: ["get round to", "carry on", "bring forward"]},
{ Question: "qatnashmoq (musobaqa); yoqtirmoq", RightAnswer: "go in for", options: ["get up to", "get round to", "carry on"]},
{ Question: "yoqtirmay qolmoq", RightAnswer: "go off", options: ["go in for", "get up to", "get round to"]},
{ Question: "qatnashmoq", RightAnswer: "join in", options: ["go off", "go in for", "get up to"]},
{ Question: "musobaqadan chiqarib yubormoq; hushidan ketkazmoq", RightAnswer: "knock out", options: ["join in", "go off", "go in for"]},
{ Question: "ehtiyot bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "look out", options: ["knock out", "join in", "go off"]},
{ Question: "chiqib ketmoq (ishtirokni to‘xtatmoq)", RightAnswer: "pull out", options: ["look out", "knock out", "join in"]},
{ Question: "kechiktirmoq", RightAnswer: "put off", options: ["pull out", "look out", "knock out"]},
{ Question: "chidamoq", RightAnswer: "put up with", options: ["put off", "pull out", "look out"]},
{ Question: "odatlanib qolmoq", RightAnswer: "take to", options: ["put up with", "put off", "pull out"]},
{ Question: "boshlamoq (hobbi, sport); vaqtni egallamoq", RightAnswer: "take up", options: ["take to", "put up with", "put off"]},
{ Question: "imkoniyatdan to‘liq foydalanmoq", RightAnswer: "make the best of sth", options: ["go all the way", "find your way", "take a trip (to a place)"]},
{ Question: "qo‘ldan kelgancha harakat qilmoq", RightAnswer: "do your best", options: ["make the best of sth", "go all the way", "find your way"]},
{ Question: "biror narsada eng yaxshisi", RightAnswer: "the best at st", options: ["school trip", "business trip", "tour guide"]},
{ Question: "imkoniyatga ega bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "have a chance to do", options: ["do your best", "make the best of sth", "go all the way"]},
{ Question: "qilish imkoniyatiga ega bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "have a chance of doing", options: ["have a chance to do", "do your best", "make the best of sth"]},
{ Question: "oz imkoniyat", RightAnswer: "little chance of", options: ["the best at st", "school trip", "business trip"]},
{ Question: "imkoniyatlari", RightAnswer: "the chances of", options: ["little chance of", "the best at st", "school trip"]},
{ Question: "xavf ostiga qo‘yib urinib ko‘rmoq", RightAnswer: "take a chance (on sth)", options: ["have a chance of doing", "have a chance to do", "do your best"]},
{ Question: "hayotdagi eng katta imkoniyat", RightAnswer: "chance of a lifetime", options: ["the chances of", "little chance of", "the best at st"]},
{ Question: "navbat", RightAnswer: "your go", options: ["chance of a lifetime", "the chances of", "little chance of"]},
{ Question: "urinib ko‘rmoq", RightAnswer: "have a go", options: ["take a chance (on sth)", "have a chance of doing", "have a chance to do"]},
{ Question: "balandlikda", RightAnswer: "in height", options: ["on the way", "in a way", "at high speed"]},
{ Question: "balandlikdan qo‘rqadigan ", RightAnswer: "afraid of heights", options: ["left-handed", "necessary (for sb) to do", "workable"]},
{ Question: "...ning balandligi", RightAnswer: "height of sth", options: ["your go", "chance of a lifetime", "the chances of"]},
{ Question: "nimagadir qiziqib ketgan ", RightAnswer: "mad about", options: ["afraid of heights", "left-handed", "necessary (for sb) to do"]},
{ Question: "jinni bo‘lib qolmoq", RightAnswer: "become mad", options: ["have a go", "take a chance (on sth)", "have a chance of doing"]},
{ Question: "(narsadan/qilishdan) zavqlanmoq", RightAnswer: "take pleasure in st", options: ["become mad", "have a go", "take a chance (on sth)"]},
{ Question: "zavq olmoq", RightAnswer: "get pleasure from st", options: ["take pleasure in st", "become mad", "have a go"]},
{ Question: "orasida mashhur ", RightAnswer: "popular with/among", options: ["mad about", "afraid of heights", "left-handed"]},
{ Question: "qarama-qarshi tomon", RightAnswer: " the opposite side", options: ["in height", "on the way", "in a way"]},
{ Question: "uzoq tomonda", RightAnswer: " the far side", options: [" the opposite side", "in height", "on the way"]},
{ Question: "kimningdir tarafini olmoq", RightAnswer: "side with sb", options: ["get pleasure from st", "take pleasure in st", "become mad"]},
{ Question: "g‘olib/mag‘lub tomon(da)", RightAnswer: "on the winning/losing side", options: [" the far side", " the opposite side", "in height"]},
{ Question: "qobiliyatga ega bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "have a talent", options: ["side with sb", "get pleasure from st", "take pleasure in st"]},
{ Question: "qobiliyat tanlovi", RightAnswer: "talent contest", options: ["height of sth", "your go", "chance of a lifetime"]},
{ Question: "vaqtida", RightAnswer: "on time", options: ["on the winning/losing side", " the far side", " the opposite side"]},
{ Question: "ayni vaqtida", RightAnswer: " in time", options: ["on time", "on the winning/losing side", " the far side"]},
{ Question: "butun vaqt davomida", RightAnswer: "the whole time", options: ["talent contest", "height of sth", "your go"]},
{ Question: "vaqti keldi", RightAnswer: "high time", options: ["head over heels (in love)", "off the top of your head", "in your interest to do"]},
{ Question: "shoshilmasdan qilmoq", RightAnswer: "take your time (doing)", options: ["have a talent", "side with sb", "get pleasure from st"]},
{ Question: "qilish uchun vaqt sarflamoq", RightAnswer: "take time to do", options: ["take your time (doing)", "have a talent", "side with sb"]},
{ Question: "(narsa) vaqtni oladi", RightAnswer: "sth takes up time", options: ["take time to do", "take your time (doing)", "have a talent"]},
{ Question: "vaqtni (biror ishga) sarflash", RightAnswer: "spend time doing", options: ["sth takes up time", "take time to do", "take your time (doing)"]},
{ Question: "(biror narsaga) vaqt ajratmoq", RightAnswer: "spend time on", options: ["spend time doing", "sth takes up time", "take time to do"]},
{ Question: "belgilangan vaqtda", RightAnswer: "at/for a certain time", options: [" in time", "on time", "on the winning/losing side"]},
{ Question: "vaqt o‘tadi", RightAnswer: "time passes", options: ["spend time on", "spend time doing", "sth takes up time"]},
{ Question: "vaqt topmoq", RightAnswer: "find time", options: ["time passes", "spend time on", "spend time doing"]},
{ Question: "uchun vaqt ajratmoq", RightAnswer: "make/find time for", options: ["find time", "time passes", "spend time on"]},
{ Question: "hozircha", RightAnswer: "for the time being", options: ["high time", "head over heels (in love)", "off the top of your head"]},
{ Question: "yaxshi vaqt o‘tkazmoq", RightAnswer: "have a good/nice time (doing)", options: ["make/find time for", "find time", "time passes"]},
{ Question: "soatni aytmoq", RightAnswer: "tell the time", options: ["have a good/nice time (doing)", "make/find time for", "find time"]},
{ Question: "bo‘sh vaqt", RightAnswer: "spare time", options: ["the whole time", "talent contest", "height of sth"]},
{ Question: "burilmoq", RightAnswer: "turn around", options: ["tell the time", "have a good/nice time (doing)", "make/find time for"]},
{ Question: "ag‘darib qo‘ymoq", RightAnswer: "turn sth over", options: ["turn around", "tell the time", "have a good/nice time (doing)"]},
{ Question: "navbatma-navbat", RightAnswer: "in turn", options: ["for the time being", "high time", "head over heels (in love)"]},
{ Question: "almashinib qilmoq", RightAnswer: "take turns", options: ["turn sth over", "turn around", "tell the time"]},
{ Question: "navbati bilan qilmoq", RightAnswer: "take it in turns", options: ["take turns", "turn sth over", "turn around"]},
{ Question: "sizning navbatingiz", RightAnswer: "your turn", options: ["spare time", "the whole time", "talent contest"]},
{ Question: "bilan bellashmoq", RightAnswer: "compete against sb", options: ["write sth down", "write to", "write about"]},
{ Question: "...da raqobat qilmoq", RightAnswer: "compete for/in sth", options: ["compete against sb", "write sth down", "write to"]},
{ Question: "diqqatini jamlamoq", RightAnswer: "concentrate on st", options: ["compete for/in sth", "compete against sb", "write sth down"]},
{ Question: "qilish qiyin", RightAnswer: "difficult to do", options: ["concentrate on st", "compete for/in sth", "compete against sb"]},
{ Question: "qiyin deb bilmoq", RightAnswer: "find sth difficult", options: ["difficult to do", "concentrate on st", "compete for/in sth"]},
{ Question: "qilish qiyin deb topmoq", RightAnswer: "find it difficult to do", options: ["find sth difficult", "difficult to do", "concentrate on st"]},
{ Question: "...ga mehr qo‘ygan", RightAnswer: "fond", options: ["find it difficult to do", "find sth difficult", "difficult to do"]},
{ Question: "qilishga erkin", RightAnswer: "free to do", options: ["fond", "find it difficult to do", "find sth difficult"]},
{ Question: "...dan ozod", RightAnswer: "free from/of sth", options: ["free to do", "fond", "find it difficult to do"]},
{ Question: "...uchun bo‘sh", RightAnswer: "free for sth", options: ["free from/of sth", "free to do", "fond"]},
{ Question: "qiziqmoq", RightAnswer: "interested in st", options: ["free for sth", "free from/of sth", "free to do"]},
{ Question: "o‘z ichiga olmoq", RightAnswer: "involve st", options: ["interested in st", "free for sth", "free from/of sth"]},
{ Question: "ishtirok etayotgan", RightAnswer: "involved in st", options: ["involve st", "interested in st", "free for sth"]},
{ Question: "eshitmoq", RightAnswer: "listen to", options: ["involved in st", "involve st", "interested in st"]},
{ Question: "yaxshi ko‘rmoq", RightAnswer: "love", options: ["listen to", "involved in st", "involve st"]},
{ Question: "qilishni yaxshi ko‘rmoq", RightAnswer: "love to do", options: ["love", "listen to", "involved in st"]},
{ Question: "qilmoqchi bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "mean to do", options: ["love to do", "love", "listen to"]},
{ Question: "degani", RightAnswer: "mean that", options: ["mean to do", "love to do", "love"]},
{ Question: "bu degani", RightAnswer: "it/this means that", options: ["mean that", "mean to do", "love to do"]},
{ Question: "ma’nosida bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "mean st", options: ["it/this means that", "mean that", "mean to do"]},
{ Question: "afzal ko‘rmoq", RightAnswer: "prefer to do ", options: ["mean st", "it/this means that", "mean that"]},
{ Question: "...ni afzal ko‘rmoq", RightAnswer: "prefer sth", options: ["prefer to do ", "mean st", "it/this means that"]},
{ Question: "...ni ...ga nisbatan afzal ko‘rmoq", RightAnswer: "prefer to", options: ["prefer sth", "prefer to do ", "mean st"]},
{ Question: "to‘xtatmoq", RightAnswer: "stop st", options: ["prefer to", "prefer sth", "prefer to do "]},
{ Question: "qilish uchun to‘xtamoq", RightAnswer: "stop to do", options: ["stop st", "prefer to", "prefer sth"]},
{ Question: "kimnidir ...dan to‘xtatmoq", RightAnswer: "stop sb from doing", options: ["stop to do", "stop st", "prefer to"]},
{ Question: "qilishi aniq", RightAnswer: "certain to do", options: ["stop sb from doing", "stop to do", "stop st"]},
{ Question: "aniq biladi", RightAnswer: "certain of sth", options: ["certain to do", "stop sb from doing", "stop to do"]},
{ Question: "ishonchi komil bo'lmoq", RightAnswer: "be certain that", options: ["certain of sth", "certain to do", "stop sb from doing"]},
{ Question: "ruxsat bermoq", RightAnswer: "allow", options: ["score", "beat", "win"]},
{ Question: "rad etmoq", RightAnswer: "disallow", options: ["allow", "score", "beat"]},
{ Question: "nafaqa/pul ajratish", RightAnswer: "allowance", options: ["opponent", "competitor", "viewer"]},
{ Question: "ruxsat etilgan", RightAnswer: "allowable", options: ["equal", "recognisable", "photographic"]},
{ Question: "bog‘lamoq", RightAnswer: "associate", options: ["disallow", "allow", "score"]},
{ Question: "aloqani uzmoq", RightAnswer: "disassociate", options: ["associate", "disallow", "allow"]},
{ Question: "uyushma", RightAnswer: "association", options: ["allowance", "opponent", "competitor"]},
{ Question: "bog‘langan", RightAnswer: "associated", options: ["allowable", "equal", "recognisable"]},
{ Question: "raqobat qilmoq", RightAnswer: "compete", options: ["disassociate", "associate", "disallow"]},
{ Question: "musobaqa", RightAnswer: "competition", options: ["association", "allowance", "opponent"]},
{ Question: "raqobatchi", RightAnswer: "competitor", options: ["competition", "association", "allowance"]},
{ Question: "raqobatbardosh", RightAnswer: "competitive", options: ["associated", "allowable", "equal"]},
{ Question: "zavqlanmoq", RightAnswer: "enjoy", options: ["compete", "disassociate", "associate"]},
{ Question: "zavq", RightAnswer: "enjoyment", options: ["competitor", "competition", "association"]},
{ Question: "maroqli", RightAnswer: "enjoyable", options: ["competitive", "associated", "allowable"]},
{ Question: "jihozlamoq", RightAnswer: "equip", options: ["enjoy", "compete", "disassociate"]},
{ Question: "jihozlar", RightAnswer: "equipment", options: ["enjoyment", "competitor", "competition"]},
{ Question: "jihozlangan", RightAnswer: "equipped", options: ["enjoyable", "competitive", "associated"]},
{ Question: "omad", RightAnswer: "fortune", options: ["equipment", "enjoyment", "competitor"]},
{ Question: "baxtsizlik", RightAnswer: "misfortune", options: ["fortune", "equipment", "enjoyment"]},
 { Question: "baxtli ", RightAnswer: "fortunate", options: ["equipped", "enjoyable", "competitive"]},
{ Question: "qiziqish", RightAnswer: "interest", options: ["misfortune", "fortune", "equipment"]},
 { Question: "qiziqarli ", RightAnswer: "interesting", options: ["fortunate", "equipped", "enjoyable"]},
{ Question: "bilmoq", RightAnswer: "know", options: ["equip", "enjoy", "compete"]},
{ Question: "bilim", RightAnswer: "knowledge", options: ["interest", "misfortune", "fortune"]},
 { Question: "bilimdon", RightAnswer: "knowledgeable", options: ["interesting", "fortunate", "equipped"]},
{ Question: "yo‘qotmoq", RightAnswer: "lose", options: ["know", "equip", "enjoy"]},
{ Question: "yo‘qotish", RightAnswer: "loss", options: ["knowledge", "interest", "misfortune"]},
{ Question: "yo‘qolgan", RightAnswer: "lost", options: ["knowledgeable", "interesting", "fortunate"]},
{ Question: "sevmoq", RightAnswer: "love", options: ["lose", "know", "equip"]},
{ Question: "medal", RightAnswer: "medal", options: ["loss", "knowledge", "interest"]},
{ Question: "medal sovrindori", RightAnswer: "medallist", options: ["medal", "loss", "knowledge"]},
{ Question: "medalon", RightAnswer: "medallion", options: ["medallist", "medal", "loss"]},
{ Question: "qarshi chiqmoq", RightAnswer: "oppose", options: ["love", "lose", "know"]},
{ Question: "qarshilik", RightAnswer: "opposition", options: ["medallion", "medallist", "medal"]},
{ Question: "raqib", RightAnswer: "opponent", options: ["opposition", "medallion", "medallist"]},
{ Question: "qarama-qarshi", RightAnswer: "opposite", options: ["lost", "knowledgeable", "interesting"]},
{ Question: "mashq qilmoq", RightAnswer: "practice", options: ["oppose", "love", "lose"]},
{ Question: "mashq qilmoq", RightAnswer: "practise", options: ["practice", "oppose", "love"]},
{ Question: "amaliy ", RightAnswer: "practical", options: ["opposite", "lost", "knowledgeable"]},
{ Question: "tayyorlamoq", RightAnswer: "train", options: ["practise", "practice", "oppose"]},
{ Question: "qayta tayyorlamoq", RightAnswer: "retrain", options: ["train", "practise", "practice"]},
{ Question: "murabbiy", RightAnswer: "trainer", options: ["opponent", "opposition", "medallion"]},
{ Question: "saqlamoq", RightAnswer: "maintain", options: ["retrain", "train", "practise"]},
{ Question: "texnik xizmat", RightAnswer: "maintenance", options: ["trainer", "opponent", "opposition"]}],
"level 17" : [
{ Question: "sun’iy", RightAnswer: "artificial", options: ["practical", "opposite", "lost"]},
{ Question: "yolg‘on, soxta", RightAnswer: "false", options: ["artificial", "practical", "opposite"]},
{ Question: "tabiiy", RightAnswer: "natural", options: ["false", "artificial", "practical"]},
{ Question: "jismoniy", RightAnswer: "physical", options: ["natural", "false", "artificial"]},
{ Question: "rost", RightAnswer: "true", options: ["physical", "natural", "false"]},
{ Question: "aniq", RightAnswer: "accurate", options: ["true", "physical", "natural"]},
{ Question: "usul", RightAnswer: "method", options: ["maintenance", "trainer", "opponent"]},
{ Question: "yo‘l, usul", RightAnswer: "way", options: ["method", "maintenance", "trainer"]},
{ Question: "dvigatel", RightAnswer: "engine", options: ["way", "method", "maintenance"]},
{ Question: "mashina", RightAnswer: "machine", options: ["engine", "way", "method"]},
{ Question: "motor", RightAnswer: "motor", options: ["machine", "engine", "way"]},
{ Question: "maqsad", RightAnswer: "aim", options: ["motor", "machine", "engine"]},
{ Question: "sabab", RightAnswer: "cause", options: ["aim", "motor", "machine"]},
{ Question: "sabab", RightAnswer: "reason", options: ["cause", "aim", "motor"]},
{ Question: "baholamoq", RightAnswer: "estimate", options: ["maintain", "retrain", "train"]},
{ Question: "hisoblamoq", RightAnswer: "calculate", options: ["estimate", "maintain", "retrain"]},
{ Question: "elektr", RightAnswer: "electric", options: ["accurate", "true", "physical"]},
{ Question: "elektron", RightAnswer: "electronic", options: ["electric", "accurate", "true"]},
{ Question: "ixtiro qilmoq", RightAnswer: "invent", options: ["calculate", "estimate", "maintain"]},
{ Question: "kashf qilmoq", RightAnswer: "discover", options: ["invent", "calculate", "estimate"]},
{ Question: "tadqiqot", RightAnswer: "research", options: ["reason", "cause", "aim"]},
{ Question: "tajriba", RightAnswer: "experiment", options: ["research", "reason", "cause"]},
{ Question: "taraqqiyot", RightAnswer: "progress", options: ["experiment", "research", "reason"]},
{ Question: "rivojlanish", RightAnswer: "development", options: ["progress", "experiment", "research"]},
{ Question: "zamonaviy", RightAnswer: "modern", options: ["electronic", "electric", "accurate"]},
{ Question: "yangi", RightAnswer: "new", options: ["modern", "electronic", "electric"]},
{ Question: "sanoat", RightAnswer: "industry", options: ["development", "progress", "experiment"]},
{ Question: "fabrika", RightAnswer: "factory", options: ["industry", "development", "progress"]},
{ Question: "mukofot", RightAnswer: "award", options: ["factory", "industry", "development"]},
{ Question: "mukofot", RightAnswer: "reward", options: ["award", "factory", "industry"]},
{ Question: "bo‘lib o‘tmoq", RightAnswer: "take place", options: ["worldwide", "responsibly", "helpless"]},
{ Question: "yuz bermoq", RightAnswer: "occur", options: ["discover", "invent", "calculate"]},
{ Question: "buzilmoq, ishlashdan to‘xtamoq", RightAnswer: "break down", options: ["take up", "take to", "put up with"]},
{ Question: "bajarish (tajriba, reja)", RightAnswer: "carry out", options: ["break down", "take up", "take to"]},
{ Question: "muvaffaqiyatli chiqmoq", RightAnswer: "come off", options: ["carry out", "break down", "take up"]},
{ Question: "rivojlanmoq, ishlay boshlamoq", RightAnswer: "come on", options: ["come off", "carry out", "break down"]},
{ Question: "(g‘oya, rejani) o‘ylab topmoq", RightAnswer: "come up with", options: ["come on", "come off", "carry out"]},
{ Question: "uzmoq (elektr ta’minoti)", RightAnswer: "cut off", options: ["come up with", "come on", "come off"]},
{ Question: "aniqlamoq, bilib olmoq", RightAnswer: "find out", options: ["cut off", "come up with", "come on"]},
{ Question: "(issiqlik, hid) chiqarmoq", RightAnswer: "give off", options: ["find out", "cut off", "come up with"]},
{ Question: "imkoniyatlarni kamaytirmoq", RightAnswer: "narrow down", options: ["give off", "find out", "cut off"]},
{ Question: "elektrga ulamoq", RightAnswer: "plug in", options: ["narrow down", "give off", "find out"]},
{ Question: "telefon orqali ulamoq", RightAnswer: "put through", options: ["plug in", "narrow down", "give off"]},
{ Question: "ga aylantirmoq", RightAnswer: "turn into", options: ["put through", "plug in", "narrow down"]},
{ Question: "o‘chirib qo‘ymoq", RightAnswer: "turn off", options: ["turn into", "put through", "plug in"]},
{ Question: "yechim topmoq", RightAnswer: "work out", options: ["turn off", "turn into", "put through"]},
{ Question: "urinib ko‘rmoq", RightAnswer: "make an attempt", options: ["take it in turns", "take turns", "turn sth over"]},
{ Question: "urinib ko‘rmoq", RightAnswer: "attempt to do", options: ["make an attempt", "take it in turns", "take turns"]},
{ Question: "o‘rtacha", RightAnswer: "on average", options: ["at/for a certain time", " in time", "on time"]},
{ Question: "boshida", RightAnswer: "in the beginning", options: ["on average", "at/for a certain time", " in time"]},
{ Question: "...ning boshida", RightAnswer: "at the beginning", options: ["in the beginning", "on average", "at/for a certain time"]},
{ Question: "…dan boshlanib", RightAnswer: "beginning with", options: ["at the beginning", "in the beginning", "on average"]},
{ Question: "...ning tagida", RightAnswer: "at the bottom", options: ["beginning with", "at the beginning", "in the beginning"]},
{ Question: "nimanidir sababi ", RightAnswer: " the cause of sth", options: ["your turn", "spare time", "the whole time"]},
{ Question: "xulosaga kelmoq", RightAnswer: "reach the conclusion", options: ["attempt to do", "make an attempt", "take it in turns"]},
{ Question: "yakunida", RightAnswer: "in conclusion", options: ["at the bottom", "beginning with", "at the beginning"]},
{ Question: "tajriba o‘tkazmoq", RightAnswer: "carry out an experiment", options: ["reach the conclusion", "attempt to do", "make an attempt"]},
{ Question: "(biror narsa bilan) tajriba qilmoq", RightAnswer: "experiment with st", options: ["carry out an experiment", "reach the conclusion", "attempt to do"]},
{ Question: "aslida", RightAnswer: "in fact", options: ["in conclusion", "at the bottom", "beginning with"]},
{ Question: "aslida, rostini aytganda", RightAnswer: "as a matter of fact", options: ["in turn", "for the time being", "high time"]},
{ Question: "gap shundaki", RightAnswer: "the fact is ", options: ["as a matter of fact", "in turn", "for the time being"]},
{ Question: "haqiqatga yuzlanmoq", RightAnswer: "face the facts", options: ["experiment with st", "carry out an experiment", "reach the conclusion"]},
{ Question: "(biror narsa) joriy qilinishi bilan", RightAnswer: "with the introduction of sth", options: ["in fact", "in conclusion", "at the bottom"]},
{ Question: "tanishtirish", RightAnswer: "an introduction to", options: [" the cause of sth", "your turn", "spare time"]},
{ Question: "telefon qilmoq", RightAnswer: "make a phone call", options: ["face the facts", "experiment with st", "carry out an experiment"]},
{ Question: "suratga tushirmoq", RightAnswer: "take a photo", options: ["make a phone call", "face the facts", "experiment with st"]},
{ Question: "tadqiqot o‘tkazmoq", RightAnswer: "do research", options: ["take a photo", "make a phone call", "face the facts"]},
{ Question: "sabab bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "cause sth", options: ["be certain that", "certain of sth", "certain to do"]},
{ Question: "deb hisoblamoq", RightAnswer: "consider st", options: ["cause sth", "be certain that", "certain of sth"]},
{ Question: "o‘ylamoq (agar)", RightAnswer: "consider if/whether", options: ["consider st", "cause sth", "be certain that"]},
{ Question: "kimnidir uchun ko‘rib chiqmoq", RightAnswer: "consider sb for sth", options: ["consider if/whether", "consider st", "cause sth"]},
{ Question: "...ga g‘alati deb hisoblamoq", RightAnswer: "consider it strange, etc (for sb to do)", options: ["consider sb for sth", "consider if/whether", "consider st"]},
{ Question: "muhokama qilmoq", RightAnswer: "discuss st", options: ["consider it strange, etc (for sb to do)", "consider sb for sth", "consider if/whether"]},
{ Question: "tushuntirmoq", RightAnswer: "explain that", options: ["discuss st", "consider it strange, etc (for sb to do)", "consider sb for sth"]},
{ Question: "...ni tushuntirmoq", RightAnswer: "explain sth", options: ["explain that", "discuss st", "consider it strange, etc (for sb to do)"]},
{ Question: "qilishni niyat qilmoq", RightAnswer: "intend to d", options: ["explain sth", "explain that", "discuss st"]},
{ Question: "bilmoq", RightAnswer: "know (about) st", options: ["intend to d", "explain sth", "explain that"]},
{ Question: "kimnidir bilmoq", RightAnswer: "know of sb", options: ["know (about) st", "intend to d", "explain sth"]},
{ Question: "sifatida tanilgan", RightAnswer: "be known as sth", options: ["know of sb", "know (about) st", "intend to d"]},
{ Question: "qidirmoq", RightAnswer: "look for", options: ["be known as sth", "know of sb", "know (about) st"]},
{ Question: "intiqlik bilan kutmoq", RightAnswer: "look forward to st", options: ["look for", "be known as sth", "know of sb"]},
{ Question: "uddalamoq", RightAnswer: "manage to do", options: ["look forward to st", "look for", "be known as sth"]},
{ Question: "rejalashtirmoq", RightAnswer: "plan sth", options: ["manage to do", "look forward to st", "look for"]},
{ Question: "qilishni rejalashtirmoq", RightAnswer: "plan to do", options: ["plan sth", "manage to do", "look forward to st"]},
{ Question: "mumkin deb topmoq", RightAnswer: "find sth possible", options: ["plan to do", "plan sth", "manage to do"]},
{ Question: "qila olmaydigan deb topmoq", RightAnswer: "find it impossible to do", options: ["find sth possible", "plan to do", "plan sth"]},
{ Question: "qilish mumkin", RightAnswer: "possible (for sb) to do", options: ["find it impossible to do", "find sth possible", "plan to do"]},
{ Question: "natija", RightAnswer: "result of st", options: ["possible (for sb) to do", "find it impossible to do", "find sth possible"]},
{ Question: "...ga olib kelmoq", RightAnswer: "result in sth", options: ["result of st", "possible (for sb) to do", "find it impossible to do"]},
{ Question: "qilishga olib kelmoq", RightAnswer: "result in", options: ["result in sth", "result of st", "possible (for sb) to do"]},
{ Question: "...dan kelib chiqmoq", RightAnswer: "result from st", options: ["result in", "result in sth", "result of st"]},
{ Question: "... natijasida", RightAnswer: "as a result of sth", options: ["result from st", "result in", "result in sth"]},
{ Question: "qiziqmoq", RightAnswer: "wonder about st", options: ["as a result of sth", "result from st", "result in"]},
{ Question: "hayron bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "wonder if", options: ["wonder about st", "as a result of sth", "result from st"]},
{ Question: "ko‘rinmoq", RightAnswer: "appear", options: ["occur", "discover", "invent"]},
{ Question: "tashqi ko‘rinish", RightAnswer: "appearance", options: ["reward", "award", "factory"]},
{ Question: "ko‘rinishidan", RightAnswer: "apparently", options: ["distantly", "directly", "culturally"]},
{ Question: "qurmoq", RightAnswer: "build", options: ["appear", "occur", "discover"]},
{ Question: "quruvchi", RightAnswer: "builder", options: ["appearance", "reward", "award"]},
{ Question: "bino", RightAnswer: "building", options: ["builder", "appearance", "reward"]},
{ Question: "kashf qilmoq", RightAnswer: "discover", options: ["build", "appear", "occur"]},
{ Question: "kashfiyot", RightAnswer: "discovery", options: ["building", "builder", "appearance"]},
{ Question: "tushuntirmoq", RightAnswer: "explain", options: ["discover", "build", "appear"]},
{ Question: "tushuntirish", RightAnswer: "explanation", options: ["discovery", "building", "builder"]},
{ Question: "muhim", RightAnswer: "important", options: ["new", "modern", "electronic"]},
{ Question: "muhim emas", RightAnswer: "unimportant", options: ["important", "new", "modern"]},
{ Question: "ahamiyat", RightAnswer: "importance", options: ["explanation", "discovery", "building"]},
{ Question: "ahamiyatli tarzda", RightAnswer: "importantly", options: ["apparently", "distantly", "directly"]},
{ Question: "joriy qilmoq", RightAnswer: "introduce", options: ["explain", "discover", "build"]},
{ Question: "kirish", RightAnswer: "introduction", options: ["importance", "explanation", "discovery"]},
{ Question: "kirish qismi", RightAnswer: "introductory", options: ["unimportant", "important", "new"]},
{ Question: "ixtiro qilmoq", RightAnswer: "invent", options: ["introduce", "explain", "discover"]},
{ Question: "ixtirochi", RightAnswer: "inventor", options: ["introduction", "importance", "explanation"]},
{ Question: "ixtiro", RightAnswer: "invention", options: ["inventor", "introduction", "importance"]},
{ Question: "kuzatmoq", RightAnswer: "observe", options: ["invent", "introduce", "explain"]},
{ Question: "kuzatuvchi", RightAnswer: "observer", options: ["invention", "inventor", "introduction"]},
{ Question: "kuzatish", RightAnswer: "observation", options: ["observer", "invention", "inventor"]},
{ Question: "mumkin", RightAnswer: "possible", options: ["introductory", "unimportant", "important"]},
{ Question: "mumkin emas", RightAnswer: "impossible", options: ["possible", "introductory", "unimportant"]},
{ Question: "imkoniyat", RightAnswer: "possibility", options: ["observation", "observer", "invention"]},
{ Question: "imkoniyatli tarzda", RightAnswer: "possibly", options: ["importantly", "apparently", "distantly"]},
{ Question: "psixologiya", RightAnswer: "psychology", options: ["possibility", "observation", "observer"]},
{ Question: "psixolog", RightAnswer: "psychologist", options: ["psychology", "possibility", "observation"]},
{ Question: "psixologik", RightAnswer: "psychological", options: ["impossible", "possible", "introductory"]},
{ Question: "tadqiqot qilmoq", RightAnswer: "research", options: ["observe", "invent", "introduce"]},
{ Question: "tadqiqotchi", RightAnswer: "researcher", options: ["psychologist", "psychology", "possibility"]},
{ Question: "inqilob", RightAnswer: "revolution", options: ["researcher", "psychologist", "psychology"]},
{ Question: "inqilobiy", RightAnswer: "revolutionary", options: ["psychological", "impossible", "possible"]},
{ Question: "ilm", RightAnswer: "science", options: ["revolution", "researcher", "psychologist"]},
{ Question: "olim", RightAnswer: "scientist", options: ["science", "revolution", "researcher"]},
{ Question: "ilmi ", RightAnswer: "scientific", options: ["revolutionary", "psychological", "impossible"]},
{ Question: "texnologiya", RightAnswer: "technology", options: ["scientist", "science", "revolution"]},
{ Question: "texnologik", RightAnswer: "technological", options: ["scientific", "revolutionary", "psychological"]},
{ Question: "texnik", RightAnswer: "technical", options: ["technological", "scientific", "revolutionary"]},
{ Question: "texnik", RightAnswer: "technician", options: ["technology", "scientist", "science"]},
{ Question: "usul, metod", RightAnswer: "technique", options: ["technician", "technology", "scientist"]},
{ Question: "yog‘och", RightAnswer: "wood", options: ["technique", "technician", "technology"]},
{ Question: "yog‘ochdan yasalgan", RightAnswer: "wooden", options: ["technical", "technological", "scientific"]}],
"level 18" : [
{ Question: "inkor qilmoq", RightAnswer: "deny", options: ["research", "observe", "invent"]},
{ Question: "rad etmoq", RightAnswer: "refuse", options: ["deny", "research", "observe"]},
{ Question: "rozi bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "agree", options: ["refuse", "deny", "research"]},
{ Question: "qabul qilmoq", RightAnswer: "accept", options: ["agree", "refuse", "deny"]},
{ Question: "sarlavha", RightAnswer: "headline", options: ["wood", "technique", "technician"]},
{ Question: "sarlavha (matnda)", RightAnswer: "heading", options: ["headline", "wood", "technique"]},
{ Question: "maxsus maqola", RightAnswer: "feature", options: ["heading", "headline", "wood"]},
{ Question: "maqola", RightAnswer: "article", options: ["feature", "heading", "headline"]},
{ Question: "tok-shou", RightAnswer: "talk show", options: ["an introduction to", " the cause of sth", "your turn"]},
{ Question: "viktorina shousi", RightAnswer: "quiz show", options: ["talk show", "an introduction to", " the cause of sth"]},
{ Question: "o‘yin shousi", RightAnswer: "game show", options: ["quiz show", "talk show", "an introduction to"]},
{ Question: "diktor", RightAnswer: "announcer", options: ["article", "feature", "heading"]},
{ Question: "sharhlovchi", RightAnswer: "commentator", options: ["announcer", "article", "feature"]},
{ Question: "ommabop gazeta", RightAnswer: "tabloid", options: ["commentator", "announcer", "article"]},
{ Question: "jiddiy gazeta", RightAnswer: "broadsheet", options: ["tabloid", "commentator", "announcer"]},
{ Question: "jurnalist", RightAnswer: "journalist", options: ["broadsheet", "tabloid", "commentator"]},
{ Question: "kolumnist (gazeta sharhlovchisi)", RightAnswer: "columnist", options: ["journalist", "broadsheet", "tabloid"]},
{ Question: "matbuot", RightAnswer: "press", options: ["columnist", "journalist", "broadsheet"]},
{ Question: "ommaviy axborot vositalari", RightAnswer: "media", options: ["press", "columnist", "journalist"]},
{ Question: "dastur", RightAnswer: "programme", options: ["media", "press", "columnist"]},
{ Question: "dastur", RightAnswer: "program", options: ["programme", "media", "press"]},
{ Question: "telekanal", RightAnswer: "channel", options: ["program", "programme", "media"]},
{ Question: "eshittirish, ko‘rsatuv", RightAnswer: "broadcast", options: ["draw", "play", "travel"]},
{ Question: "axborot dasturi", RightAnswer: "bulletin", options: ["channel", "program", "programme"]},
{ Question: "shoshilinch xabar", RightAnswer: "newsflash", options: ["bulletin", "channel", "program"]},
{ Question: "gap ochmoq", RightAnswer: "bring up", options: ["work out", "turn off", "turn into"]},
{ Question: "efirga chiqmoq", RightAnswer: "come on", options: ["bring up", "work out", "turn off"]},
{ Question: "chop etilmoq", RightAnswer: "come out", options: ["come on", "bring up", "work out"]},
{ Question: "to‘ldirmoq (hujjat)", RightAnswer: "fill in", options: ["come out", "come on", "bring up"]},
{ Question: "varaqlamoq", RightAnswer: "flick through", options: ["fill in", "come out", "come on"]},
{ Question: "batafsil ko‘rib chiqmoq", RightAnswer: "go into", options: ["flick through", "fill in", "come out"]},
{ Question: "tarqatmoq", RightAnswer: "hand out", options: ["go into", "flick through", "fill in"]},
{ Question: "ma’lumot qidirmoq (lug‘at, kitob)", RightAnswer: "look up", options: ["hand out", "go into", "flick through"]},
{ Question: "tushunishga harakat qilmoq; o‘zini qilib ko‘rsatmoq", RightAnswer: "make out", options: ["look up", "hand out", "go into"]},
{ Question: "bahona/voqea o‘ylab topmoq", RightAnswer: "make up", options: ["make out", "look up", "hand out"]},
{ Question: "taklif bermoq", RightAnswer: "put forward", options: ["make up", "make out", "look up"]},
{ Question: "aldovga tushmaslik", RightAnswer: "see through", options: ["put forward", "make up", "make out"]},
{ Question: "ajralib turmoq", RightAnswer: "stand out", options: ["see through", "put forward", "make up"]},
{ Question: "sahifa ochmoq", RightAnswer: "turn over", options: ["stand out", "see through", "put forward"]},
{ Question: "boshqaruvda", RightAnswer: "in control", options: ["with the introduction of sth", "in fact", "in conclusion"]},
{ Question: "boshqaruvni qo‘lga olmoq", RightAnswer: "take control", options: ["do research", "take a photo", "make a phone call"]},
{ Question: "boshqaruv ostida", RightAnswer: "under control", options: ["in control", "with the introduction of sth", "in fact"]},
{ Question: "kimningdir nazorati ostida", RightAnswer: "under the control of sb", options: ["under control", "in control", "with the introduction of sth"]},
{ Question: "boshqaruvdan chiqib ketgan ", RightAnswer: "out of control", options: ["popular with/among", "mad about", "afraid of heights"]},
{ Question: "...ga ta’rif bermoq", RightAnswer: "give a description", options: ["take control", "do research", "take a photo"]},
{ Question: "ta’sir ko‘rsatmoq", RightAnswer: "make a difference", options: ["give a description", "take control", "do research"]},
{ Question: "farqini aytib bermoq", RightAnswer: "tell the difference (between)", options: ["make a difference", "give a description", "take control"]},
{ Question: "hech qanday farq yo'q", RightAnswer: "there’s no difference between", options: ["game show", "quiz show", "talk show"]},
{ Question: "qadrlamaslik", RightAnswer: "take for granted", options: ["tell the difference (between)", "make a difference", "give a description"]},
{ Question: "ta’sir qilmoq", RightAnswer: "influence", options: ["take for granted", "tell the difference (between)", "make a difference"]},
{ Question: "ta’siri bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "have/be an influence on", options: ["there’s no difference between", "game show", "quiz show"]},
{ Question: "internetda", RightAnswer: "on the Internet", options: ["under the control of sb", "under control", "in control"]},
{ Question: "internet orqali", RightAnswer: "over the Internet", options: ["on the Internet", "under the control of sb", "under control"]},
{ Question: "internetda sayr qilmoq", RightAnswer: "surf the Internet", options: ["influence", "take for granted", "tell the difference (between)"]},
{ Question: "yangiliklarda", RightAnswer: "in the news", options: ["over the Internet", "on the Internet", "under the control of sb"]},
{ Question: "yangiliklarda", RightAnswer: "on the news", options: ["in the news", "over the Internet", "on the Internet"]},
{ Question: "yangilikni eshitmoq", RightAnswer: "hear the news", options: ["surf the Internet", "influence", "take for granted"]},
{ Question: "tezkor yangilik", RightAnswer: "newsflash", options: ["have/be an influence on", "there’s no difference between", "game show"]},
{ Question: "gazeta ", RightAnswer: "newspaper", options: ["newsflash", "bulletin", "channel"]},
{ Question: "sodir bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "take place", options: ["hear the news", "surf the Internet", "influence"]},
{ Question: "o‘rniga", RightAnswer: "in place of", options: ["on the news", "in the news", "over the Internet"]},
{ Question: "bir joyda", RightAnswer: "at a place", options: ["in place of", "on the news", "in the news"]},
{ Question: "savol bermoq", RightAnswer: "ask a Question", options: ["take place", "hear the news", "surf the Internet"]},
{ Question: "so‘roq qilmoq", RightAnswer: "Question", options: ["ask a Question", "take place", "hear the news"]},
{ Question: "muhokamada", RightAnswer: "in Question", options: ["at a place", "in place of", "on the news"]},
{ Question: "savol belgisi", RightAnswer: "Question mark", options: ["newsflash", "have/be an influence on", "there’s no difference between"]},
{ Question: "fikrga ega bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "hold a view", options: ["Question", "ask a Question", "take place"]},
{ Question: "kimningdir qarashi ", RightAnswer: "be sb’s view that", options: ["works", "worker", "work"]},
{ Question: "mening nazarimda", RightAnswer: "in my view", options: ["in Question", "at a place", "in place of"]},
{ Question: "... sababli", RightAnswer: "in view of", options: ["in my view", "in Question", "at a place"]},
{ Question: "manzarani tomosha qilmoq", RightAnswer: "see the view", options: ["hold a view", "Question", "ask a Question"]},
{ Question: "nimaningdir manzarasi", RightAnswer: "view of sth", options: ["Question mark", "newsflash", "have/be an influence on"]},
{ Question: "(biror narsa/kishni) kuzatmoq", RightAnswer: "watch", options: ["see the view", "hold a view", "Question"]},
{ Question: "ehtiyot bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "watch (out) for", options: ["watch", "see the view", "hold a view"]},
{ Question: "qorovullik qilmoq", RightAnswer: "keep watch", options: ["watch (out) for", "watch", "see the view"]},
{ Question: "kimningdir fikricha", RightAnswer: "according to sb", options: ["wonder if", "wonder about st", "as a result of sth"]},
{ Question: "e’lon qilmoq", RightAnswer: "announce sth", options: ["according to sb", "wonder if", "wonder about st"]},
{ Question: "deb e’lon qilmoq", RightAnswer: "announce that", options: ["announce sth", "according to sb", "wonder if"]},
{ Question: "ishontirmoq", RightAnswer: "believe sth", options: ["announce that", "announce sth", "according to sb"]},
{ Question: "ishontirmoq (nimagadir)", RightAnswer: "believe in sth", options: ["believe sth", "announce that", "announce sth"]},
{ Question: "deb hisoblamoq", RightAnswer: "believe that", options: ["believe in sth", "believe sth", "announce that"]},
{ Question: "kimnidir deb hisoblamoq", RightAnswer: "believe sb to be", options: ["believe that", "believe in sth", "believe sth"]},
{ Question: "fikr bildirmoq", RightAnswer: "comment on sth", options: ["believe sb to be", "believe that", "believe in sth"]},
{ Question: "fikr bildirmoq", RightAnswer: "make a comment about sth", options: ["comment on sth", "believe sb to be", "believe that"]},
{ Question: "aralashtirib yubormoq", RightAnswer: "confuse with", options: ["make a comment about sth", "comment on sth", "believe sb to be"]},
{ Question: "adashgan", RightAnswer: "confused about/by sth", options: ["confuse with", "make a comment about sth", "comment on sth"]},
{ Question: "yozishmoq, mos kelmoq", RightAnswer: "correspond with", options: ["confused about/by sth", "confuse with", "make a comment about sth"]},
{ Question: "sifatida ta’riflamoq", RightAnswer: "describe as", options: ["correspond with", "confused about/by sth", "confuse with"]},
{ Question: "kimga nimanidir ta’riflab bermoq", RightAnswer: "describe sth to sb", options: ["describe as", "correspond with", "confused about/by sth"]},
{ Question: "eshitmoq", RightAnswer: "hear", options: ["describe sth to sb", "describe as", "correspond with"]},
{ Question: "haqida eshitmoq", RightAnswer: "hear about", options: ["hear", "describe sth to sb", "describe as"]},
{ Question: "kimdandir xabar olmoq", RightAnswer: "hear from sb", options: ["hear about", "hear", "describe sth to sb"]},
{ Question: "kimga deb xabar bermoq", RightAnswer: "inform sb that", options: ["hear from sb", "hear about", "hear"]},
{ Question: "xabar bermoq", RightAnswer: "inform sb about/of sth", options: ["inform sb that", "hear from sb", "hear about"]},
{ Question: "ehtimoli bor", RightAnswer: "likely to do", options: ["inform sb about/of sth", "inform sb that", "hear from sb"]},
{ Question: "ehtimolki", RightAnswer: "likely that", options: ["likely to do", "inform sb about/of sth", "inform sb that"]},
{ Question: "ko‘ndirmoq", RightAnswer: "persuade sb to do", options: ["likely that", "likely to do", "inform sb about/of sth"]},
{ Question: "deb ishontirmoq", RightAnswer: "persuade sb that", options: ["persuade sb to do", "likely that", "likely to do"]},
{ Question: "...ga ishontirmoq", RightAnswer: "persuade sb of sth", options: ["persuade sb that", "persuade sb to do", "likely that"]},
{ Question: "...da ma’no ", RightAnswer: "point (in) doing", options: ["persuade sb of sth", "persuade sb that", "persuade sb to do"]},
{ Question: "kimga nimanidir yubormoq", RightAnswer: "send sb sth", options: ["point (in) doing", "persuade sb of sth", "persuade sb that"]},
{ Question: "nimanidir kimga yubormoq", RightAnswer: "send sth to sb", options: ["send sb sth", "point (in) doing", "persuade sb of sth"]},
{ Question: "hayron qoldirmoq", RightAnswer: "by surprise", options: ["send sth to sb", "send sb sth", "point (in) doing"]},
{ Question: "hayron qolgan", RightAnswer: "surprised at/by sth", options: ["by surprise", "send sth to sb", "send sb sth"]},
{ Question: "aytmoq", RightAnswer: "tell sb sth", options: ["surprised at/by sth", "by surprise", "send sth to sb"]},
{ Question: "deb aytmoq", RightAnswer: "tell sb that", options: ["tell sb sth", "surprised at/by sth", "by surprise"]},
{ Question: "nimadir haqida aytmoq", RightAnswer: "tell sb about st", options: ["tell sb that", "tell sb sth", "surprised at/by sth"]},
{ Question: "qilmaslikka aytmoq", RightAnswer: "tell sb (not) to do", options: ["tell sb about st", "tell sb that", "tell sb sth"]},
{ Question: "e’lon qilmoq", RightAnswer: "announce", options: ["accept", "agree", "refuse"]},
{ Question: "e’lon", RightAnswer: "announcement", options: ["newspaper", "newsflash", "bulletin"]},
 { Question: "e’lon qilingan", RightAnswer: "announced", options: ["wooden", "technical", "technological"]},
{ Question: "ishonch", RightAnswer: "belief", options: ["announcement", "newspaper", "newsflash"]},
{ Question: "ishonchsizlik", RightAnswer: "disbelief", options: ["belief", "announcement", "newspaper"]},
{ Question: "ishonmoq", RightAnswer: "believe", options: ["announce", "accept", "agree"]},
 { Question: "ishonchli", RightAnswer: "believable", options: ["announced", "wooden", "technical"]},
 { Question: "ishonchli tarzda", RightAnswer: "believably", options: ["possibly", "importantly", "apparently"]},
{ Question: "muloqot qilmoq", RightAnswer: "communicate", options: ["believe", "announce", "accept"]},
{ Question: "aloqa", RightAnswer: "communication", options: ["disbelief", "belief", "announcement"]},
 { Question: "muloqot qiladigan", RightAnswer: "communicative", options: ["believable", "announced", "wooden"]},
{ Question: "muloqotchi", RightAnswer: "communicator", options: ["communication", "disbelief", "belief"]},
{ Question: "ishontirmoq", RightAnswer: "convince", options: ["communicate", "believe", "announce"]},
{ Question: "ishongan", RightAnswer: "convinced", options: ["communicative", "believable", "announced"]},
 { Question: "ishonarli", RightAnswer: "convincing", options: ["convinced", "communicative", "believable"]},
{ Question: "muhokama qilmoq", RightAnswer: "discuss", options: ["convince", "communicate", "believe"]},
{ Question: "muhokama", RightAnswer: "discussion", options: ["communicator", "communication", "disbelief"]},
{ Question: "tahrir qilmoq", RightAnswer: "edit", options: ["discuss", "convince", "communicate"]},
{ Question: "muharrir", RightAnswer: "editor", options: ["discussion", "communicator", "communication"]},
{ Question: "bosh maqola", RightAnswer: "editorial", options: ["professional", "amateur", "native"]},
{ Question: "tahrirlangan", RightAnswer: "edited", options: ["convincing", "convinced", "communicative"]},
{ Question: "hazil", RightAnswer: "humour", options: ["editor", "discussion", "communicator"]},
{ Question: "hazilkash", RightAnswer: "humorous", options: ["edited", "convincing", "convinced"]},
{ Question: "hazilsiz", RightAnswer: "humourless", options: ["humorous", "edited", "convincing"]},
{ Question: "xabar bermoq", RightAnswer: "inform", options: ["edit", "discuss", "convince"]},
{ Question: "ma’lumot", RightAnswer: "information", options: ["humour", "editor", "discussion"]},
 { Question: "xabardor", RightAnswer: "informed", options: ["humourless", "humorous", "edited"]},
 { Question: "ma’lumotli", RightAnswer: "informative", options: ["informed", "humourless", "humorous"]},
{ Question: "jurnal", RightAnswer: "journal", options: ["information", "humour", "editor"]},
{ Question: "jurnalist", RightAnswer: "journalist", options: ["journal", "information", "humour"]},
{ Question: "jurnalistika", RightAnswer: "journalism", options: ["journalist", "journal", "information"]},
{ Question: "jurnalistik", RightAnswer: "journalistic", options: ["informative", "informed", "humourless"]},
{ Question: "siyosat", RightAnswer: "politics", options: ["journalism", "journalist", "journal"]},
{ Question: "siyosiy ", RightAnswer: "", options: ["journalistic", "informative", "informed"]},
{ Question: "siyosatchi", RightAnswer: "politician", options: ["politics", "journalism", "journalist"]},
{ Question: "kuch", RightAnswer: "power", options: ["politician", "politics", "journalism"]},
{ Question: "kuchli", RightAnswer: "powerful", options: ["", "journalistic", "informative"]},
{ Question: "kuchsiz", RightAnswer: "powerless", options: ["powerful", "", "journalistic"]},
{ Question: "kuch bermoq", RightAnswer: "empower", options: ["inform", "edit", "discuss"]},
{ Question: "masxara qilmoq", RightAnswer: "ridicule", options: ["empower", "inform", "edit"]},
{ Question: "kulgili", RightAnswer: "ridiculous", options: ["powerless", "powerful", ""]},
{ Question: "kulgililik", RightAnswer: "ridiculousness", options: ["power", "politician", "politics"]},
{ Question: "ikkinchi", RightAnswer: "second", options: ["ridiculous", "powerless", "powerful"]},
{ Question: "ikkinchidan", RightAnswer: "secondly", options: ["believably", "possibly", "importantly"]},
{ Question: "ikkinchi darajali", RightAnswer: "secondary", options: ["second", "ridiculous", "powerless"]},
{ Question: "yozmoq", RightAnswer: "write", options: ["ridicule", "empower", "inform"]},
{ Question: "yozuvchi", RightAnswer: "writer", options: ["ridiculousness", "power", "politician"]},
{ Question: "yozuv", RightAnswer: "writing", options: ["writer", "ridiculousness", "power"]},
{ Question: "yozdi", RightAnswer: "wrote", options: ["supervise", "qualify", "meet"]},
 { Question: "yozilgan", RightAnswer: "written", options: ["secondary", "second", "ridiculous"]}],
"level 19" : [
{ Question: "munosabat", RightAnswer: "relationship", options: ["writing", "writer", "ridiculousness"]},
{ Question: "aloqa", RightAnswer: "connection", options: ["relationship", "writing", "writer"]},
{ Question: "qo‘llab-quvvatlash", RightAnswer: "support", options: ["broadcast", "draw", "play"]},
{ Question: "yordam bermoq", RightAnswer: "assist", options: ["write", "ridicule", "empower"]},
{ Question: "kompaniya", RightAnswer: "company", options: ["connection", "relationship", "writing"]},
{ Question: "guruh", RightAnswer: "group", options: ["company", "connection", "relationship"]},
{ Question: "ayblash", RightAnswer: "blame", options: ["support", "broadcast", "draw"]},
{ Question: "ayb", RightAnswer: "fault", options: ["group", "company", "connection"]},
{ Question: "mehribon", RightAnswer: "kind", options: ["written", "secondary", "second"]},
{ Question: "xushmuomala", RightAnswer: "polite", options: ["kind", "written", "secondary"]},
{ Question: "mashhur", RightAnswer: "popular", options: ["polite", "kind", "written"]},
{ Question: "taniqli", RightAnswer: "famous", options: ["popular", "polite", "kind"]},
{ Question: "qari/eski", RightAnswer: "old", options: ["famous", "popular", "polite"]},
{ Question: "qadimgi", RightAnswer: "ancient", options: ["old", "famous", "popular"]},
{ Question: "achinish his qiluvchi", RightAnswer: "sympathetic", options: ["ancient", "old", "famous"]},
{ Question: "yoqimli", RightAnswer: "likeable", options: ["sympathetic", "ancient", "old"]},
{ Question: "odatdagi", RightAnswer: "typical", options: ["likeable", "sympathetic", "ancient"]},
{ Question: "doimiy", RightAnswer: "usual", options: ["typical", "likeable", "sympathetic"]},
{ Question: "oddiy", RightAnswer: "ordinary", options: ["usual", "typical", "likeable"]},
{ Question: "olomon", RightAnswer: "crowd", options: ["fault", "group", "company"]},
{ Question: "tomoshabinlar", RightAnswer: "audience", options: ["crowd", "fault", "group"]},
{ Question: "asabiy", RightAnswer: "nervous", options: ["ordinary", "usual", "typical"]},
{ Question: "jahl", RightAnswer: "bad-tempered", options: ["nervous", "ordinary", "usual"]},
{ Question: "yaqin", RightAnswer: "close", options: ["bad-tempered", "nervous", "ordinary"]},
{ Question: "yaqin", RightAnswer: "near", options: ["close", "bad-tempered", "nervous"]},
{ Question: "zavqlanmoq", RightAnswer: "enjoy", options: ["assist", "write", "ridicule"]},
{ Question: "rozi qilmoq", RightAnswer: "please", options: ["enjoy", "assist", "write"]},
{ Question: "sezgir", RightAnswer: "sensitive", options: ["near", "close", "bad-tempered"]},
{ Question: "aqlli", RightAnswer: "sensible", options: ["sensitive", "near", "close"]},
{ Question: "noma’lum", RightAnswer: "unknown", options: ["sensible", "sensitive", "near"]},
{ Question: "yomon nom chiqargan", RightAnswer: "infamous", options: ["unknown", "sensible", "sensitive"]},
{ Question: "hol-ahvol so‘ramoq", RightAnswer: "ask after", options: ["turn over", "stand out", "see through"]},
{ Question: "bolani tarbiyalamoq", RightAnswer: "bring up", options: ["ask after", "turn over", "stand out"]},
{ Question: "sevib qolmoq / aldanganini tushunmaslik", RightAnswer: "fall for", options: ["bring up", "ask after", "turn over"]},
{ Question: "janjallashib, do‘stlikni to‘xtatmoq", RightAnswer: "fall out (with)", options: ["fall for", "bring up", "ask after"]},
{ Question: "yaxshi munosabatda bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "get on (with)", options: ["fall out (with)", "fall for", "bring up"]},
{ Question: "voyaga yetmoq", RightAnswer: "grow up", options: ["get on (with)", "fall out (with)", "fall for"]},
{ Question: "o‘zini balandroq tutmoq", RightAnswer: "look down on", options: ["grow up", "get on (with)", "fall out (with)"]},
{ Question: "hurmat qilmoq", RightAnswer: "look up to", options: ["look down on", "grow up", "get on (with)"]},
{ Question: "yarashmoq", RightAnswer: "make up", options: ["look up to", "look down on", "grow up"]},
{ Question: "vafot etmoq", RightAnswer: "pass away", options: ["make up", "look up to", "look down on"]},
{ Question: "kamsitmoq, yomon muomala qilmoq", RightAnswer: "pick on", options: ["pass away", "make up", "look up to"]},
{ Question: "tanqid qilmoq, ustidan kulmoq", RightAnswer: "put down", options: ["pick on", "pass away", "make up"]},
{ Question: "tinchlanmoq / uy qurib joylashmoq", RightAnswer: "settle down", options: ["put down", "pick on", "pass away"]},
{ Question: "himoya qilmoq", RightAnswer: "stand up for", options: ["settle down", "put down", "pick on"]},
{ Question: "hayratda qoldirmoq", RightAnswer: "take aback", options: ["stand up for", "settle down", "put down"]},
{ Question: "ma’qullamoq", RightAnswer: "give approval of/for sth", options: ["keep watch", "watch (out) for", "watch"]},
{ Question: "kimningdir roziligiga sazovor bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "meet with sb’s approval", options: ["give approval of/for sth", "keep watch", "watch (out) for"]},
{ Question: "(kim bilandir) bahslashmoq", RightAnswer: "have an argument", options: ["meet with sb’s approval", "give approval of/for sth", "keep watch"]},
{ Question: "bahsni yutmoq/yutqazmoq", RightAnswer: "win/lose an argument", options: ["have an argument", "meet with sb’s approval", "give approval of/for sth"]},
{ Question: "(biror narsa/kishga) g‘amxo‘rlik qilmoq", RightAnswer: "take care", options: ["win/lose an argument", "have an argument", "meet with sb’s approval"]},
{ Question: "...ga qiziqish/mehr qo‘ymoq", RightAnswer: "care for/about", options: ["take care", "win/lose an argument", "have an argument"]},
{ Question: "qilishga jur’at qilmoq", RightAnswer: "have the courage to do", options: ["care for/about", "take care", "win/lose an argument"]},
{ Question: "qilish uchun jasorat talab qilinadi ", RightAnswer: "it takes courage to do", options: ["take place", "worldwide", "responsibly"]},
{ Question: "niqoblangan", RightAnswer: "in disguise", options: ["in view of", "in my view", "in Question"]},
{ Question: "niqob taqmoq", RightAnswer: "wear a disguise", options: ["have the courage to do", "care for/about", "take care"]},
{ Question: "niqoblanmoq", RightAnswer: "disguise yourself", options: ["wear a disguise", "have the courage to do", "care for/about"]},
{ Question: "... sifatida niqoblangan ", RightAnswer: "disguised as", options: ["out of control", "popular with/among", "mad about"]},
{ Question: "oila qurmoq", RightAnswer: "start a family", options: ["disguise yourself", "wear a disguise", "have the courage to do"]},
{ Question: "kichik oila", RightAnswer: "nuclear family", options: ["view of sth", "Question mark", "newsflash"]},
{ Question: "katta oila", RightAnswer: "extended family", options: ["nuclear family", "view of sth", "Question mark"]},
{ Question: "yaxshilik qilmoq", RightAnswer: "do a favour", options: ["start a family", "disguise yourself", "wear a disguise"]},
{ Question: "tarafida bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "be in favour of", options: ["in disguise", "in view of", "in my view"]},
 { Question: "do‘st bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "make friends", options: ["do a favour", "start a family", "disguise yourself"]},
{ Question: "eng yaqin do‘st", RightAnswer: "best friend", options: ["extended family", "nuclear family", "view of sth"]},
{ Question: "kimnidir sevib qolmoq", RightAnswer: "fall in love with sb", options: ["make friends", "do a favour", "start a family"]},
{ Question: "yaxshi kayfiyatda", RightAnswer: "in a good mood", options: ["be in favour of", "in disguise", "in view of"]},
{ Question: "to‘g‘ri kayfiyatda", RightAnswer: "in the right mood", options: ["in a good mood", "be in favour of", "in disguise"]},
{ Question: "nimagadir kayfiyati bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "in the mood for sth", options: ["in the right mood", "in a good mood", "be in favour of"]},
{ Question: "kimga achinmoq", RightAnswer: "pity sb", options: ["fall in love with sb", "make friends", "do a favour"]},
{ Question: "kimga rahmi kelmoq", RightAnswer: "take pity on sb", options: ["pity sb", "fall in love with sb", "make friends"]},
{ Question: "kimga achinish", RightAnswer: "feel pity for sb", options: ["take pity on sb", "pity sb", "fall in love with sb"]},
{ Question: "afsuski ", RightAnswer: "it’s a pity (that)", options: ["it takes courage to do", "take place", "worldwide"]},
{ Question: "qilishga va’da bermoq", RightAnswer: "promise to do", options: ["feel pity for sb", "take pity on sb", "pity sb"]},
{ Question: "va’da bermoq", RightAnswer: "make sb a promise", options: ["promise to do", "feel pity for sb", "take pity on sb"]},
{ Question: "va’dasidan qaytmoq", RightAnswer: "break a promise", options: ["make sb a promise", "promise to do", "feel pity for sb"]},
{ Question: "rozilik bildirmoq", RightAnswer: "agree with", options: ["tell sb (not) to do", "tell sb about st", "tell sb that"]},
{ Question: "ruxsat bermoq", RightAnswer: "allow sb to do", options: ["agree with", "tell sb (not) to do", "tell sb about st"]},
{ Question: "ma’qullamoq", RightAnswer: "approve of st", options: ["allow sb to do", "agree with", "tell sb (not) to do"]},
{ Question: "kimdandir narsa so‘ramoq", RightAnswer: "ask sb sth", options: ["approve of st", "allow sb to do", "agree with"]},
{ Question: "hujum qilmoq", RightAnswer: "attack", options: ["ask sb sth", "approve of st", "allow sb to do"]},
{ Question: "taqiqlamoq", RightAnswer: "ban sb from st", options: ["attack", "ask sb sth", "approve of st"]},
{ Question: "ishontirmoq", RightAnswer: "convince sb of sth", options: ["ban sb from st", "attack", "ask sb sth"]},
{ Question: "majbur qilmoq", RightAnswer: "force sb to do sth", options: ["convince sb of sth", "ban sb from st", "attack"]},
{ Question: "mustaqil", RightAnswer: "independent", options: ["force sb to do sth", "convince sb of sth", "ban sb from st"]},
{ Question: "imkon bermoq", RightAnswer: "let sb do sth", options: ["independent", "force sb to do sth", "convince sb of sth"]},
{ Question: "e’tiroz bildirmoq", RightAnswer: "object to st", options: ["let sb do sth", "independent", "force sb to do sth"]},
{ Question: "o‘zini qilib ko‘rsatmoq", RightAnswer: "pretend to do", options: ["object to st", "let sb do sth", "independent"]},
{ Question: "ishonmoq", RightAnswer: "rely on", options: ["pretend to do", "object to st", "let sb do sth"]},
{ Question: "qodir", RightAnswer: "able", options: ["infamous", "unknown", "sensible"]},
{ Question: "qodir emas", RightAnswer: "unable", options: ["able", "infamous", "unknown"]},
{ Question: "qobiliyat", RightAnswer: "ability", options: ["audience", "crowd", "fault"]},
{ Question: "nogiron", RightAnswer: "disabled", options: ["unable", "able", "infamous"]},
{ Question: "nogironlik", RightAnswer: "disability", options: ["ability", "audience", "crowd"]},
{ Question: "erishmoq", RightAnswer: "achieve", options: ["please", "enjoy", "assist"]},
{ Question: "yutuq", RightAnswer: "achievement", options: ["disability", "ability", "audience"]},
{ Question: "bahslashmoq", RightAnswer: "argue", options: ["achieve", "please", "enjoy"]},
{ Question: "bahs", RightAnswer: "argument", options: ["achievement", "disability", "ability"]},
{ Question: "bahsga moyil", RightAnswer: "argumentative", options: ["disabled", "unable", "able"]},
{ Question: "parvarish qilmoq", RightAnswer: "care", options: ["argue", "achieve", "please"]},
{ Question: "ehtiyotkor(ona)", RightAnswer: "careful", options: ["argumentative", "disabled", "unable"]},
{ Question: "beparvo", RightAnswer: "careless", options: ["careful", "argumentative", "disabled"]},
{ Question: "", RightAnswer: "caring", options: ["careless", "careful", "argumentative"]},
{ Question: "yozishmoq", RightAnswer: "correspond", options: ["care", "argue", "achieve"]},
{ Question: "yozishmalar", RightAnswer: "correspondence", options: ["argument", "achievement", "disability"]},
{ Question: "do‘st", RightAnswer: "friend", options: ["correspondence", "argument", "achievement"]},
{ Question: "do‘stlik", RightAnswer: "friendship", options: ["friend", "correspondence", "argument"]},
{ Question: "do‘stona", RightAnswer: "friendly", options: ["caring", "careless", "careful"]},
{ Question: "baxtli", RightAnswer: "happy", options: ["friendly", "caring", "careless"]},
{ Question: "baxtsiz", RightAnswer: "unhappy", options: ["happy", "friendly", "caring"]},
{ Question: "baxt", RightAnswer: "happiness", options: ["friendship", "friend", "correspondence"]},
{ Question: "baxtli tarzda", RightAnswer: "happily", options: ["secondly", "believably", "possibly"]},
{ Question: "rashkchi", RightAnswer: "jealous", options: ["unhappy", "happy", "friendly"]},
{ Question: "rashk", RightAnswer: "jealousy", options: ["happiness", "friendship", "friend"]},
{ Question: "mehribon", RightAnswer: "kind", options: ["jealous", "unhappy", "happy"]},
{ Question: "qo‘pol", RightAnswer: "unkind", options: ["kind", "jealous", "unhappy"]},
{ Question: "mehribonlik", RightAnswer: "kindness", options: ["jealousy", "happiness", "friendship"]},
{ Question: "mehribon tarzda", RightAnswer: "kindly", options: ["happily", "secondly", "believably"]},
{ Question: "turmush qurmoq", RightAnswer: "marry", options: ["correspond", "care", "argue"]},
{ Question: "turmush", RightAnswer: "marriage", options: ["kindness", "jealousy", "happiness"]},
{ Question: "", RightAnswer: "married", options: ["unkind", "kind", "jealous"]},
{ Question: "asab", RightAnswer: "nerve", options: ["marriage", "kindness", "jealousy"]},
{ Question: "asabiy", RightAnswer: "nervous", options: ["married", "unkind", "kind"]},
{ Question: "asabiylik", RightAnswer: "nervousness", options: ["nerve", "marriage", "kindness"]},
{ Question: "bo‘ysunmoq", RightAnswer: "obey", options: ["marry", "correspond", "care"]},
{ Question: "bo‘ysunmaslik", RightAnswer: "disobey", options: ["obey", "marry", "correspond"]},
{ Question: "itoatkor", RightAnswer: "obedient", options: ["nervous", "married", "unkind"]},
{ Question: "itoat", RightAnswer: "obedience", options: ["nervousness", "nerve", "marriage"]},
{ Question: "shaxs", RightAnswer: "person", options: ["obedience", "nervousness", "nerve"]},
{ Question: "shaxsiy", RightAnswer: "personal", options: ["obedient", "nervous", "married"]},
{ Question: "shaxsiyat", RightAnswer: "personality", options: ["person", "obedience", "nervousness"]},
{ Question: "xushmuomala", RightAnswer: "polite", options: ["personal", "obedient", "nervous"]},
{ Question: "qo‘pol", RightAnswer: "impolite", options: ["polite", "personal", "obedient"]},
{ Question: "xushmuomala tarzda", RightAnswer: "politely", options: ["kindly", "happily", "secondly"]},
{ Question: "xushmuomalalik", RightAnswer: "politeness", options: ["personality", "person", "obedience"]},
{ Question: "aloqasi bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "relate", options: ["disobey", "obey", "marry"]},
{ Question: "nisbatan", RightAnswer: "relative", options: ["politely", "kindly", "happily"]},
{ Question: "aloqa", RightAnswer: "relation", options: ["politeness", "personality", "person"]},
{ Question: "munosabat", RightAnswer: "relationship", options: ["relation", "politeness", "personality"]}],
"level 20" : [
{ Question: "dalil", RightAnswer: "proof", options: ["relationship", "relation", "politeness"]},
{ Question: "dalil-isbot", RightAnswer: "evidence", options: ["proof", "relationship", "relation"]},
{ Question: "qoida", RightAnswer: "rule", options: ["evidence", "proof", "relationship"]},
{ Question: "qonun", RightAnswer: "law", options: ["rule", "evidence", "proof"]},
{ Question: "adolat", RightAnswer: "justice", options: ["law", "rule", "evidence"]},
{ Question: "huquq", RightAnswer: "right", options: ["justice", "law", "rule"]},
{ Question: "gumondor", RightAnswer: "suspect", options: ["right", "justice", "law"]},
{ Question: "hibsga olmoq", RightAnswer: "arrest", options: ["relate", "disobey", "obey"]},
{ Question: "ayblamoq", RightAnswer: "charge", options: ["arrest", "relate", "disobey"]},
{ Question: "sudya", RightAnswer: "judge", options: ["suspect", "right", "justice"]},
{ Question: "hakamlar hay’ati", RightAnswer: "jury", options: ["judge", "suspect", "right"]},
{ Question: "gumondor", RightAnswer: "suspect", options: ["jury", "judge", "suspect"]},
{ Question: "ayblanuvchi", RightAnswer: "accused", options: ["suspect", "jury", "judge"]},
{ Question: "javobgarlikka tortmoq", RightAnswer: "prosecute", options: ["charge", "arrest", "relate"]},
{ Question: "ta’qib qilmoq", RightAnswer: "persecute", options: ["prosecute", "charge", "arrest"]},
{ Question: "aybsiz", RightAnswer: "innocent", options: ["impolite", "polite", "personal"]},
{ Question: "aybdor", RightAnswer: "guilty", options: ["innocent", "impolite", "polite"]},
{ Question: "qaror", RightAnswer: "decision", options: ["accused", "suspect", "jury"]},
{ Question: "hukm", RightAnswer: "verdict", options: ["decision", "accused", "suspect"]},
{ Question: "o‘lim jazosi", RightAnswer: "capital punishment", options: ["best friend", "extended family", "nuclear family"]},
{ Question: "jismoniy jazo", RightAnswer: "corporal punishment", options: ["capital punishment", "best friend", "extended family"]},
{ Question: "talonchi", RightAnswer: "robber", options: ["verdict", "decision", "accused"]},
{ Question: "uyni buzib kiruvchi o‘g‘ri", RightAnswer: "burglar", options: ["robber", "verdict", "decision"]},
{ Question: "o‘g‘ri", RightAnswer: "thief", options: ["burglar", "robber", "verdict"]},
{ Question: "buzuvchi (mol-mulkni)", RightAnswer: "vandal", options: ["thief", "burglar", "robber"]},
{ Question: "bezorilik qiluvchi", RightAnswer: "hooligan", options: ["vandal", "thief", "burglar"]},
{ Question: "hukm chiqarmoq", RightAnswer: "sentence", options: ["persecute", "prosecute", "charge"]},
{ Question: "qamoqqa olmoq", RightAnswer: "imprison", options: ["sentence", "persecute", "prosecute"]},
{ Question: "guvoh", RightAnswer: "witness", options: ["hooligan", "vandal", "thief"]},
{ Question: "guvoh (tasodifiy kuzatuvchi)", RightAnswer: "bystander", options: ["witness", "hooligan", "vandal"]},
{ Question: "advokat", RightAnswer: "lawyer", options: ["bystander", "witness", "hooligan"]},
{ Question: "yurist", RightAnswer: "solicitor", options: ["lawyer", "bystander", "witness"]},
{ Question: "orqaga qaytmoq (talabdan)", RightAnswer: "back down", options: ["take aback", "stand up for", "settle down"]},
{ Question: "qochib ketmoq (qamoqdan)", RightAnswer: "break out", options: ["back down", "take aback", "stand up for"]},
{ Question: "yangi qonun joriy qilmoq", RightAnswer: "bring in", options: ["break out", "back down", "take aback"]},
{ Question: "ortidan quvmoq", RightAnswer: "chase after", options: ["bring in", "break out", "back down"]},
{ Question: "ma’lumot bermoq", RightAnswer: "come forward", options: ["chase after", "bring in", "break out"]},
{ Question: "jazodan qochmoq", RightAnswer: "get away with", options: ["come forward", "chase after", "bring in"]},
{ Question: "portlamoq, o‘q uzilmoq", RightAnswer: "go off", options: ["get away with", "come forward", "chase after"]},
{ Question: "topshirmoq (hokimiyatga)", RightAnswer: "hand in", options: ["go off", "get away with", "come forward"]},
{ Question: "qurolli talonchilik qilmoq; kechiktirmoq", RightAnswer: "hold up", options: ["hand in", "go off", "get away with"]},
{ Question: "jazolamaslik, ozod qilmoq", RightAnswer: "let off", options: ["hold up", "hand in", "go off"]},
{ Question: "surishtirmoq", RightAnswer: "look into", options: ["let off", "hold up", "hand in"]},
{ Question: "qochib ketmoq", RightAnswer: "make off", options: ["look into", "let off", "hold up"]},
{ Question: "yozib olmoq", RightAnswer: "take down", options: ["make off", "look into", "let off"]},
{ Question: "aldamoq", RightAnswer: "take in", options: ["take down", "make off", "look into"]},
{ Question: "hisobga olmoq", RightAnswer: "take into account", options: ["break a promise", "make sb a promise", "promise to do"]},
{ Question: "izoh bermoq", RightAnswer: "account for sth", options: ["take into account", "break a promise", "make sb a promise"]},
{ Question: "ustunlikka ega bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "have an advantage", options: ["account for sth", "take into account", "break a promise"]},
{ Question: "...dan foydalanib qolmoq", RightAnswer: "take advantage", options: ["have an advantage", "account for sth", "take into account"]},
{ Question: "ustun holatda", RightAnswer: "at an advantage", options: ["in the mood for sth", "in the right mood", "in a good mood"]},
{ Question: "aybdor bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "be to blame", options: ["take advantage", "have an advantage", "account for sth"]},
{ Question: "aybni o‘z zimmasiga olmoq", RightAnswer: "take the blame", options: ["be to blame", "take advantage", "have an advantage"]},
{ Question: "ayblamoq", RightAnswer: "put the blame on sb", options: ["take the blame", "be to blame", "take advantage"]},
{ Question: "(biror narsaga) zarar yetkazmoq", RightAnswer: "cause damage (to sth)", options: ["put the blame on sb", "take the blame", "be to blame"]},
{ Question: "aybdor", RightAnswer: "at fault", options: ["at an advantage", "in the mood for sth", "in the right mood"]},
{ Question: "kamchilik qidirmoq", RightAnswer: "find fault with", options: ["cause damage (to sth)", "put the blame on sb", "take the blame"]},
{ Question: "qilish niyati yo'q ", RightAnswer: "have no intention of doing", options: ["find fault with", "cause damage (to sth)", "put the blame on sb"]},
{ Question: "xato qilmoq", RightAnswer: "make a mistake", options: ["have no intention of doing", "find fault with", "cause damage (to sth)"]},
{ Question: "xato qilish", RightAnswer: "a mistake", options: ["corporal punishment", "capital punishment", "best friend"]},
{ Question: "kimnidir boshqa birov deb adashmoq", RightAnswer: "mistake sb for sb", options: ["make a mistake", "have no intention of doing", "find fault with"]},
{ Question: "kim uchun kerak bo‘lmoq ", RightAnswer: "necessary (for sb) to do", options: ["workable", "irresponsible", "responsible"]},
{ Question: "tartibda", RightAnswer: "in order", options: ["at fault", "at an advantage", "in the mood for sth"]},
{ Question: "tartibga keltirmoq", RightAnswer: "put sth in order", options: ["mistake sb for sb", "make a mistake", "have no intention of doing"]},
{ Question: "... qilish uchun", RightAnswer: "in order to do", options: ["in order", "at fault", "at an advantage"]},
{ Question: "buyruq bermoq", RightAnswer: "give an order", options: ["put sth in order", "mistake sb for sb", "make a mistake"]},
{ Question: "buyruq asosida (qilmoq)", RightAnswer: "under orders", options: ["in order to do", "in order", "at fault"]},
{ Question: "ruxsat bermoq", RightAnswer: "give sb permission to do", options: ["give an order", "put sth in order", "mistake sb for sb"]},
{ Question: "ruxsat so‘ramoq", RightAnswer: "ask for permission to do", options: ["give sb permission to do", "give an order", "put sth in order"]},
{ Question: "ruxsatga so‘ramoq", RightAnswer: "ask for permission  to do", options: ["ask for permission to do", "give sb permission to do", "give an order"]},
{ Question: "ataylab qilmoq", RightAnswer: "do sth on purpose", options: ["ask for permission  to do", "ask for permission to do", "give sb permission to do"]},
{ Question: "...ning maqsadi", RightAnswer: "purpose of sth", options: ["a mistake", "corporal punishment", "capital punishment"]},
{ Question: "sabab ", RightAnswer: "reason why", options: ["be sb’s view that", "works", "worker"]},
{ Question: "nimaningdir sababi", RightAnswer: "reason for sth", options: ["purpose of sth", "a mistake", "corporal punishment"]},
{ Question: "kimnidir ishontirishga harakat qilmoq", RightAnswer: "reason with sb", options: ["do sth on purpose", "ask for permission  to do", "ask for permission to do"]},
{ Question: "noto‘g‘ri ish qilmoq", RightAnswer: "do wrong", options: ["reason with sb", "do sth on purpose", "ask for permission  to do"]},
{ Question: "noto‘g‘ri ish", RightAnswer: "the wrong thing to do", options: ["reason for sth", "purpose of sth", "a mistake"]},
{ Question: "xato qilmoq", RightAnswer: "go wrong", options: ["do wrong", "reason with sb", "do sth on purpose"]},
{ Question: "noto‘g‘ri joylashtirilgan", RightAnswer: "the wrong way up", options: ["under orders", "in order to do", "in order"]},
{ Question: "ayblamoq", RightAnswer: "accuse sb of st", options: ["rely on", "pretend to do", "object to st"]},
{ Question: "hibsga olmoq", RightAnswer: "arrest sb for st", options: ["accuse sb of st", "rely on", "pretend to do"]},
{ Question: "ayblamoq", RightAnswer: "charge sb with sth", options: ["arrest sb for st", "accuse sb of st", "rely on"]},
{ Question: "da’vo qilmoq", RightAnswer: "claim to be/do", options: ["charge sb with sth", "arrest sb for st", "accuse sb of st"]},
{ Question: "inkor qilmoq", RightAnswer: "deny st", options: ["claim to be/do", "charge sb with sth", "arrest sb for st"]},
{ Question: "shubhalanmoq", RightAnswer: "doubt sth", options: ["deny st", "claim to be/do", "charge sb with sth"]},
{ Question: "kechirmoq", RightAnswer: "forgive sb for st", options: ["doubt sth", "deny st", "claim to be/do"]},
{ Question: "ko‘z yugurtirmoq", RightAnswer: "glimpse sth", options: ["forgive sb for st", "doubt sth", "deny st"]},
{ Question: "aybdor", RightAnswer: "guilty of st", options: ["glimpse sth", "forgive sb for st", "doubt sth"]},
{ Question: "qonuniy", RightAnswer: "legal (for sb) to do", options: ["guilty of st", "glimpse sth", "forgive sb for st"]},
{ Question: "kimnidir majbur qilmoq", RightAnswer: "make sb do", options: ["legal (for sb) to do", "guilty of st", "glimpse sth"]},
{ Question: "rad etmoq", RightAnswer: "refuse to do sth", options: ["make sb do", "legal (for sb) to do", "guilty of st"]},
{ Question: "hurmat qilmoq", RightAnswer: "respect sth; respect sb for st", options: ["refuse to do sth", "make sb do", "legal (for sb) to do"]},
{ Question: "tahdid qilmoq", RightAnswer: "threaten to do; threaten sb with sth", options: ["respect sth; respect sb for st", "refuse to do sth", "make sb do"]},
{ Question: "ayblamoq", RightAnswer: "accuse", options: ["imprison", "sentence", "persecute"]},
{ Question: "ayblanuvchi", RightAnswer: "accused", options: ["solicitor", "lawyer", "bystander"]},
{ Question: "ayblov", RightAnswer: "accusation", options: ["accused", "solicitor", "lawyer"]},
{ Question: "qaram bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "addict", options: ["accuse", "imprison", "sentence"]},
{ Question: "qaram", RightAnswer: "addicted", options: ["guilty", "innocent", "impolite"]},
{ Question: "qaram qiladigan", RightAnswer: "addictive", options: ["addicted", "guilty", "innocent"]},
{ Question: "qaramlik", RightAnswer: "addiction", options: ["accusation", "accused", "solicitor"]},
{ Question: "mahkum qilmoq", RightAnswer: "convict", options: ["addict", "accuse", "imprison"]},
{ Question: "mahkum qilingan", RightAnswer: "convicted", options: ["addictive", "addicted", "guilty"]},
{ Question: "hukm", RightAnswer: "conviction", options: ["addiction", "accusation", "accused"]},
{ Question: "jinoyat", RightAnswer: "crime", options: ["conviction", "addiction", "accusation"]},
{ Question: "jinoyatchi", RightAnswer: "criminal", options: ["editorial", "professional", "amateur"]},
{ Question: "ravshan", RightAnswer: "evident", options: ["convicted", "addictive", "addicted"]},
{ Question: "dalil", RightAnswer: "evidence", options: ["crime", "conviction", "addiction"]},
{ Question: "ravshan tarzda", RightAnswer: "evidently", options: ["relative", "politely", "kindly"]},
{ Question: "qalbakilashtirmoq", RightAnswer: "forge", options: ["convict", "addict", "accuse"]},
{ Question: "qalbakilashtirish", RightAnswer: "forgery", options: ["evidence", "crime", "conviction"]},
{ Question: "qalbakilashtiruvchi", RightAnswer: "forger", options: ["forgery", "evidence", "crime"]},
{ Question: "halol", RightAnswer: "honest", options: ["evident", "convicted", "addictive"]},
{ Question: "halol bo‘lmagan", RightAnswer: "dishonest", options: ["honest", "evident", "convicted"]},
{ Question: "halollik", RightAnswer: "honesty", options: ["forger", "forgery", "evidence"]},
{ Question: "halol tarzda", RightAnswer: "honestly", options: ["evidently", "relative", "politely"]},
{ Question: "tergov qilmoq", RightAnswer: "investigate", options: ["forge", "convict", "addict"]},
{ Question: "tergovchi", RightAnswer: "investigative", options: ["dishonest", "honest", "evident"]},
{ Question: "tergov", RightAnswer: "investigation", options: ["honesty", "forger", "forgery"]},
{ Question: "tergovchi", RightAnswer: "investigator", options: ["investigation", "honesty", "forger"]},
{ Question: "qonun", RightAnswer: "law", options: ["investigator", "investigation", "honesty"]},
{ Question: "advokat", RightAnswer: "lawyer", options: ["law", "investigator", "investigation"]},
{ Question: "qonuniy", RightAnswer: "lawful", options: ["investigative", "dishonest", "honest"]},
{ Question: "qotillik", RightAnswer: "murder", options: ["blame", "support", "broadcast"]},
{ Question: "qotil", RightAnswer: "murderer", options: ["lawyer", "law", "investigator"]},
{ Question: "jinoyat", RightAnswer: "offence", options: ["murderer", "lawyer", "law"]},
{ Question: "haqoratli", RightAnswer: "offensive", options: ["lawful", "investigative", "dishonest"]},
{ Question: "xafa qilmoq", RightAnswer: "offend", options: ["investigate", "forge", "convict"]},
{ Question: "jinoyatchi", RightAnswer: "offender", options: ["offence", "murderer", "lawyer"]},
{ Question: "qamoqxona", RightAnswer: "prison", options: ["offender", "offence", "murderer"]},
{ Question: "mahkum", RightAnswer: "prisoner", options: ["prison", "offender", "offence"]},
{ Question: "qamoqqa olingan", RightAnswer: "imprison(ed)", options: ["offensive", "lawful", "investigative"]},
{ Question: "qamoq", RightAnswer: "imprisonment", options: ["prisoner", "prison", "offender"]},
{ Question: "isbotlamoq", RightAnswer: "prove", options: ["offend", "investigate", "forge"]},
{ Question: "dalil", RightAnswer: "proof", options: ["imprisonment", "prisoner", "prison"]},
 { Question: "isbotlangan", RightAnswer: "proven", options: ["imprison(ed)", "offensive", "lawful"]},
{ Question: "inkor qilmoq", RightAnswer: "disprove", options: ["prove", "offend", "investigate"]},
{ Question: "o‘g‘irlash", RightAnswer: "rob", options: ["disprove", "prove", "offend"]},
{ Question: "talonchilik", RightAnswer: "robbery", options: ["proof", "imprisonment", "prisoner"]},
{ Question: "o‘g‘ri", RightAnswer: "robber", options: ["robbery", "proof", "imprisonment"]},
{ Question: "xavfsiz qilmoq", RightAnswer: "secure", options: ["rob", "disprove", "prove"]},
{ Question: "xavfsiz emas", RightAnswer: "insecure", options: ["proven", "imprison(ed)", "offensive"]},
{ Question: "xavfsizlik", RightAnswer: "security", options: ["robber", "robbery", "proof"]},
{ Question: "o‘g‘irlik", RightAnswer: "theft", options: ["security", "robber", "robbery"]},
{ Question: "o‘g‘ri", RightAnswer: "thief", options: ["theft", "security", "robber"]}],
"level 21" : [
{ Question: "retsept", RightAnswer: "prescription", options: ["thief", "theft", "security"]},
{ Question: "retsept (ovqatga)", RightAnswer: "recipe", options: ["prescription", "thief", "theft"]},
{ Question: "ozg‘in", RightAnswer: "thin", options: ["insecure", "proven", "imprison(ed)"]},
{ Question: "kelishgan", RightAnswer: "slim", options: ["thin", "insecure", "proven"]},
{ Question: "infeksiya", RightAnswer: "infection", options: ["recipe", "prescription", "thief"]},
{ Question: "ifloslanish", RightAnswer: "pollution", options: ["infection", "recipe", "prescription"]},
{ Question: "operatsiya", RightAnswer: "operation", options: ["pollution", "infection", "recipe"]},
{ Question: "jarrohlik", RightAnswer: "surgery", options: ["operation", "pollution", "infection"]},
{ Question: "vosita", RightAnswer: "remedy", options: ["surgery", "operation", "pollution"]},
{ Question: "davolash", RightAnswer: "cure", options: ["remedy", "surgery", "operation"]},
{ Question: "terapiya", RightAnswer: "therapy", options: ["cure", "remedy", "surgery"]},
{ Question: "bint, gips", RightAnswer: "plaster", options: ["therapy", "cure", "remedy"]},
{ Question: "bint", RightAnswer: "bandage", options: ["plaster", "therapy", "cure"]},
{ Question: "yara", RightAnswer: "sore", options: ["bandage", "plaster", "therapy"]},
{ Question: "jarohat, og‘riq", RightAnswer: "hurt", options: ["murder", "blame", "support"]},
{ Question: "og‘riq", RightAnswer: "pain", options: ["sore", "bandage", "plaster"]},
{ Question: "ta’sir", RightAnswer: "effect", options: ["pain", "sore", "bandage"]},
{ Question: "natija", RightAnswer: "result", options: ["effect", "pain", "sore"]},
{ Question: "bo‘lim (kasalxonada)", RightAnswer: "ward", options: ["result", "effect", "pain"]},
{ Question: "klinika", RightAnswer: "clinic", options: ["ward", "result", "effect"]},
{ Question: "kasallik", RightAnswer: "illness", options: ["clinic", "ward", "result"]},
{ Question: "kasallik (jiddiyroq)", RightAnswer: "disease", options: ["illness", "clinic", "ward"]},
{ Question: "sog‘lom", RightAnswer: "healthy", options: ["slim", "thin", "insecure"]},
{ Question: "jismonan sog‘lom", RightAnswer: "fit", options: ["healthy", "slim", "thin"]},
{ Question: "doza", RightAnswer: "dose", options: ["disease", "illness", "clinic"]},
{ Question: "doza (slangda)", RightAnswer: "fix", options: ["dose", "disease", "illness"]},
{ Question: "jarohatlangan", RightAnswer: "injured", options: ["fit", "healthy", "slim"]},
{ Question: "shikastlangan", RightAnswer: "damaged", options: ["injured", "fit", "healthy"]},
{ Question: "tekshirmoq", RightAnswer: "examine", options: ["secure", "rob", "disprove"]},
{ Question: "tergov qilmoq", RightAnswer: "investigate", options: ["examine", "secure", "rob"]},
{ Question: "isitma", RightAnswer: "fever", options: ["fix", "dose", "disease"]},
{ Question: "toshma", RightAnswer: "rash", options: ["fever", "fix", "dose"]},
{ Question: "boshlanmoq (urush, yong‘in va h.k.)", RightAnswer: "break out", options: ["take in", "take down", "make off"]},
{ Question: "sabab bo‘lmoq (kasallikka)", RightAnswer: "bring on", options: ["break out", "take in", "take down"]},
{ Question: "yengil kasallikka chalinmoq", RightAnswer: "come down with", options: ["bring on", "break out", "take in"]},
{ Question: "hushiga kelmoq", RightAnswer: "come round/to", options: ["come down with", "bring on", "break out"]},
{ Question: "kamaytirmoq (masalan, chekishni)", RightAnswer: "cut down (on)", options: ["come round/to", "come down with", "bring on"]},
{ Question: "o‘zini qila oladigan darajada sezmoq", RightAnswer: "feel up to", options: ["cut down (on)", "come round/to", "come down with"]},
{ Question: "tuzalmoq", RightAnswer: "get over", options: ["feel up to", "cut down (on)", "come round/to"]},
{ Question: "tashlamoq (odatni)", RightAnswer: "give up", options: ["get over", "feel up to", "cut down (on)"]},
{ Question: "qaramoq", RightAnswer: "look after", options: ["give up", "get over", "feel up to"]},
{ Question: "hushidan ketmoq", RightAnswer: "pass out", options: ["look after", "give up", "get over"]},
{ Question: "omon qolmoq", RightAnswer: "pull through", options: ["pass out", "look after", "give up"]},
{ Question: "o‘ldirmoq (kasal hayvonni)", RightAnswer: "put down", options: ["pull through", "pass out", "look after"]},
{ Question: "semirmoq", RightAnswer: "put on", options: ["put down", "pull through", "pass out"]},
{ Question: "ta’siri o‘tib ketmoq (dori)", RightAnswer: "wear off", options: ["put on", "put down", "pull through"]},
{ Question: "(biror narsaga) muqobil topmoq", RightAnswer: "find an alternative (to sth)", options: ["go wrong", "do wrong", "reason with sb"]},
{ Question: "muqobilga ega bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "have an alternative", options: ["find an alternative (to sth)", "go wrong", "do wrong"]},
{ Question: "muqobil tibbiyot", RightAnswer: "alternative medicine", options: ["the wrong thing to do", "reason for sth", "purpose of sth"]},
{ Question: "uchrashuv tayinlamoq", RightAnswer: "make an appointment", options: ["have an alternative", "find an alternative (to sth)", "go wrong"]},
{ Question: "urinib ko‘rmoq", RightAnswer: "make an attempt", options: ["make an appointment", "have an alternative", "find an alternative (to sth)"]},
{ Question: "urinmoq", RightAnswer: "attempt to do", options: ["make an attempt", "make an appointment", "have an alternative"]},
{ Question: "...dan foyda ko‘rmoq", RightAnswer: "benefit from sth", options: ["attempt to do", "make an attempt", "make an appointment"]},
{ Question: "...ning foydasi", RightAnswer: "a benefit of sth", options: ["alternative medicine", "the wrong thing to do", "reason for sth"]},
{ Question: "shikoyat qilmoq", RightAnswer: "complain (about doing)", options: ["benefit from sth", "attempt to do", "make an attempt"]},
{ Question: "(biror narsadan) shikoyat qilmoq", RightAnswer: "complain of sth", options: ["complain (about doing)", "benefit from sth", "attempt to do"]},
{ Question: "mashq qilmoq", RightAnswer: "get exercise", options: ["complain of sth", "complain (about doing)", "benefit from sth"]},
{ Question: "mashq bajarmoq", RightAnswer: "do exercise", options: ["get exercise", "complain of sth", "complain (about doing)"]},
{ Question: "sog‘lom bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "get fit", options: ["do exercise", "get exercise", "complain of sth"]},
{ Question: "(kim uchun) foydali ", RightAnswer: "good for sb", options: ["disguised as", "out of control", "popular with/among"]},
{ Question: "...da yaxshi bo‘lmoq ", RightAnswer: "good at st", options: ["good for sb", "disguised as", "out of control"]},
{ Question: "(kimga) mehribon ", RightAnswer: "good to sb", options: ["good at st", "good for sb", "disguised as"]},
{ Question: "sog‘lig'i yaxshi ", RightAnswer: "in good health", options: ["the wrong way up", "under orders", "in order to do"]},
{ Question: "sog‘liq markazi", RightAnswer: "health centre", options: ["a benefit of sth", "alternative medicine", "the wrong thing to do"]},
{ Question: "sog‘liqni saqlash", RightAnswer: "health care", options: ["health centre", "a benefit of sth", "alternative medicine"]},
{ Question: "ukol olmoq", RightAnswer: "have an injection", options: ["get fit", "do exercise", "get exercise"]},
{ Question: "ukol qilmoq", RightAnswer: "give sb an injection", options: ["have an injection", "get fit", "do exercise"]},
{ Question: "dori ichmoq/ yozib bermoq", RightAnswer: "take medicine", options: ["give sb an injection", "have an injection", "get fit"]},
{ Question: "tibbiyot o‘qimoq / amaliyot qilmoq", RightAnswer: "practise medicine", options: ["take medicine", "give sb an injection", "have an injection"]},
{ Question: "eng yaxshi davo", RightAnswer: "the best medicine", options: ["health care", "health centre", "a benefit of sth"]},
{ Question: "sport formasiga kirish", RightAnswer: "get in shape", options: ["practise medicine", "take medicine", "give sb an injection"]},
{ Question: "formani saqlash", RightAnswer: "stay in shape", options: ["get in shape", "practise medicine", "take medicine"]},
{ Question: "...ning shakli", RightAnswer: "the shape of sth", options: ["the best medicine", "health care", "health centre"]},
{ Question: "... shaklida", RightAnswer: "in the shape of", options: ["in good health", "the wrong way up", "under orders"]},
{ Question: "narsa yoymoq", RightAnswer: "spread sth", options: ["stay in shape", "get in shape", "practise medicine"]},
{ Question: "(joyga) tarqalmoq", RightAnswer: "spread to a place", options: ["spread sth", "stay in shape", "get in shape"]},
{ Question: "qaram", RightAnswer: "addicted to sth", options: ["threaten to do; threaten sb with sth", "respect sth; respect sb for st", "refuse to do sth"]},
{ Question: "harakat qilmoq", RightAnswer: "attempt to do", options: ["addicted to sth", "threaten to do; threaten sb with sth", "respect sth; respect sb for st"]},
{ Question: "foyda olmoq", RightAnswer: "benefit from sth", options: ["attempt to do", "addicted to sth", "threaten to do; threaten sb with sth"]},
{ Question: "...ning foydasi", RightAnswer: "a benefit of sth", options: ["benefit from sth", "attempt to do", "addicted to sth"]},
{ Question: "shikoyat qilmoq", RightAnswer: "complain (about doing)", options: ["a benefit of sth", "benefit from sth", "attempt to do"]},
{ Question: "shikoyat qilmoq", RightAnswer: "complain of sth", options: ["complain (about doing)", "a benefit of sth", "benefit from sth"]},
{ Question: "uddalamoq", RightAnswer: "cope with st", options: ["complain of sth", "complain (about doing)", "a benefit of sth"]},
{ Question: "ukol qilmoq", RightAnswer: "inject sth into", options: ["cope with st", "complain of sth", "complain (about doing)"]},
{ Question: "olib kelmoq", RightAnswer: "lead to sth", options: ["inject sth into", "cope with st", "complain of sth"]},
{ Question: "ehtimol", RightAnswer: "likely to do", options: ["lead to sth", "inject sth into", "cope with st"]},
{ Question: "(no)ehtimolki", RightAnswer: "it is (un)likely that", options: ["likely to do", "lead to sth", "inject sth into"]},
{ Question: "qilish kerak", RightAnswer: "need to do", options: ["it is (un)likely that", "likely to do", "lead to sth"]},
{ Question: "qilinishi kerak", RightAnswer: "need doing", options: ["need to do", "it is (un)likely that", "likely to do"]},
{ Question: "muhtoj", RightAnswer: "in need of", options: ["need doing", "need to do", "it is (un)likely that"]},
{ Question: "kerak emas", RightAnswer: "no need for", options: ["in need of", "need doing", "need to do"]},
{ Question: "operatsiya qilmoq", RightAnswer: "operate on", options: ["no need for", "in need of", "need doing"]},
{ Question: "azob chekmoq", RightAnswer: "suffer from sth", options: ["operate on", "no need for", "in need of"]},
{ Question: "charchagan", RightAnswer: "tired of st", options: ["suffer from sth", "operate on", "no need for"]},
{ Question: "harakat qilmoq", RightAnswer: "try to do", options: ["tired of st", "suffer from sth", "operate on"]},
{ Question: "sinab ko‘rmoq", RightAnswer: "try", options: ["try to do", "tired of st", "suffer from sth"]},
{ Question: "xavotirlanmoq", RightAnswer: "worry about doing", options: ["try", "try to do", "tired of st"]},
{ Question: "xavotirga tushgan", RightAnswer: "worried about", options: ["worry about doing", "try", "try to do"]},
{ Question: "arziydi", RightAnswer: "worth st", options: ["worried about", "worry about doing", "try"]},
{ Question: "allergiya", RightAnswer: "allergy", options: ["rash", "fever", "fix"]},
{ Question: "allergiyali", RightAnswer: "allergic", options: ["damaged", "injured", "fit"]},
{ Question: "xabardor", RightAnswer: "aware", options: ["allergic", "damaged", "injured"]},
{ Question: "bexabar", RightAnswer: "unaware", options: ["aware", "allergic", "damaged"]},
{ Question: "xabardorlik", RightAnswer: "awareness", options: ["allergy", "rash", "fever"]},
{ Question: "foyda", RightAnswer: "benefit", options: ["awareness", "allergy", "rash"]},
{ Question: "foydali", RightAnswer: "beneficial", options: ["unaware", "aware", "allergic"]},
{ Question: "qulaylik", RightAnswer: "comfort", options: ["benefit", "awareness", "allergy"]},
{ Question: "noqulaylik", RightAnswer: "discomfort", options: ["comfort", "benefit", "awareness"]},
{ Question: "qulay", RightAnswer: "comfortable", options: ["beneficial", "unaware", "aware"]},
{ Question: "qulay tarzda", RightAnswer: "comfortably", options: ["honestly", "evidently", "relative"]},
{ Question: "urg‘u", RightAnswer: "emphasis", options: ["discomfort", "comfort", "benefit"]},
{ Question: "urg‘u bermoq", RightAnswer: "emphasise", options: ["investigate", "examine", "secure"]},
{ Question: "qat’iy", RightAnswer: "emphatic", options: ["comfortable", "beneficial", "unaware"]},
{ Question: "sog‘lom", RightAnswer: "fit", options: ["emphatic", "comfortable", "beneficial"]},
{ Question: "sog‘ligi yomon", RightAnswer: "unfit", options: ["fit", "emphatic", "comfortable"]},
{ Question: "jismoniy holat", RightAnswer: "fitness", options: ["emphasis", "discomfort", "comfort"]},
{ Question: "kasal", RightAnswer: "ill", options: ["unfit", "fit", "emphatic"]},
{ Question: "kasallik", RightAnswer: "illness", options: ["fitness", "emphasis", "discomfort"]},
{ Question: "ukol qilmoq", RightAnswer: "inject", options: ["emphasise", "investigate", "examine"]},
{ Question: "ukol", RightAnswer: "injection", options: ["illness", "fitness", "emphasis"]},
{ Question: "jarohatlamoq", RightAnswer: "injure", options: ["inject", "emphasise", "investigate"]},
{ Question: "jarohat", RightAnswer: "injury", options: ["injection", "illness", "fitness"]},
{ Question: "jarohatlar", RightAnswer: "injuries", options: ["injury", "injection", "illness"]},
{ Question: "operatsiya qilmoq", RightAnswer: "operate", options: ["injure", "inject", "emphasise"]},
{ Question: "operatsiya", RightAnswer: "operation", options: ["injuries", "injury", "injection"]},
{ Question: "operator", RightAnswer: "operator", options: ["operation", "injuries", "injury"]},
{ Question: "ishlayotgan", RightAnswer: "operating", options: ["ill", "unfit", "fit"]},
{ Question: "hamkorlik qilmoq", RightAnswer: "cooperate", options: ["operate", "injure", "inject"]},
{ Question: "hamkorlik", RightAnswer: "cooperation", options: ["operator", "operation", "injuries"]},
 { Question: "hamkorlik qiladigan", RightAnswer: "cooperative", options: ["operating", "ill", "unfit"]},
{ Question: "zahar", RightAnswer: "poison", options: ["cooperation", "operator", "operation"]},
{ Question: "zaharli", RightAnswer: "poisonous", options: ["cooperative", "operating", "ill"]},
{ Question: "zaharlanish", RightAnswer: "poisoning", options: ["poison", "cooperation", "operator"]},
{ Question: "tuzalmoq", RightAnswer: "recover", options: ["cooperate", "operate", "injure"]},
{ Question: "sog‘ayish", RightAnswer: "recovery", options: ["poisoning", "poison", "cooperation"]},
{ Question: "kuchli", RightAnswer: "strong", options: ["poisonous", "cooperative", "operating"]},
{ Question: "kuch", RightAnswer: "strength", options: ["recovery", "poisoning", "poison"]},
{ Question: "kuchaytirmoq", RightAnswer: "strengthen", options: ["recover", "cooperate", "operate"]},
{ Question: "kuchli tarzda", RightAnswer: "strongly", options: ["comfortably", "honestly", "evidently"]},
{ Question: "jarrohlik", RightAnswer: "surgery", options: ["strength", "recovery", "poisoning"]},
{ Question: "jarroh", RightAnswer: "surgeon", options: ["surgery", "strength", "recovery"]},
{ Question: "jarrohlik", RightAnswer: "surgical", options: ["strong", "poisonous", "cooperative"]},
{ Question: "davolamoq", RightAnswer: "treat", options: ["strengthen", "recover", "cooperate"]},
{ Question: "davolash", RightAnswer: "treatment", options: ["surgeon", "surgery", "strength"]}],
"level 22" : [
{ Question: "to‘g‘ramoq", RightAnswer: "chop", options: ["treat", "strengthen", "recover"]},
{ Question: "tilimlamoq", RightAnswer: "slice", options: ["chop", "treat", "strengthen"]},
{ Question: "qirg‘ichdan o‘tkazmoq", RightAnswer: "grate", options: ["slice", "chop", "treat"]},
{ Question: "tushlik", RightAnswer: "lunch", options: ["treatment", "surgeon", "surgery"]},
{ Question: "kechki ovqat", RightAnswer: "dinner", options: ["lunch", "treatment", "surgeon"]},
{ Question: "muzlatkich", RightAnswer: "freezer", options: ["dinner", "lunch", "treatment"]},
{ Question: "sovutkich", RightAnswer: "fridge", options: ["freezer", "dinner", "lunch"]},
{ Question: "pishirmoq (duxda)", RightAnswer: "bake", options: ["grate", "slice", "chop"]},
{ Question: "grilda qovurmoq", RightAnswer: "grill", options: ["bake", "grate", "slice"]},
{ Question: "yog‘da qovurmoq", RightAnswer: "fry", options: ["grill", "bake", "grate"]},
{ Question: "duxda qovurmoq", RightAnswer: "roast", options: ["fry", "grill", "bake"]},
{ Question: "qaynamoq", RightAnswer: "boil", options: ["roast", "fry", "grill"]},
{ Question: "likopcha", RightAnswer: "plate", options: ["fridge", "freezer", "dinner"]},
{ Question: "kosacha", RightAnswer: "bowl", options: ["plate", "fridge", "freezer"]},
{ Question: "choynak osti", RightAnswer: "saucer", options: ["bowl", "plate", "fridge"]},
{ Question: "idish/taom", RightAnswer: "dish", options: ["saucer", "bowl", "plate"]},
{ Question: "muzlatilgan", RightAnswer: "frozen", options: ["surgical", "strong", "poisonous"]},
{ Question: "sovuq", RightAnswer: "freezing", options: ["frozen", "surgical", "strong"]},
{ Question: "oshpazlik qilmoq", RightAnswer: "cook", options: ["boil", "roast", "fry"]},
{ Question: "gaz plitasi", RightAnswer: "cooker", options: ["dish", "saucer", "bowl"]},
{ Question: "bosh oshpaz", RightAnswer: "chef", options: ["cooker", "dish", "saucer"]},
{ Question: "sabzavot", RightAnswer: "vegetable", options: ["chef", "cooker", "dish"]},
{ Question: "vegetarian", RightAnswer: "vegetarian", options: ["criminal", "editorial", "professional"]},
{ Question: "vegan", RightAnswer: "vegan", options: ["vegetarian", "criminal", "editorial"]},
{ Question: "aralashtirmoq", RightAnswer: "mix", options: ["cook", "boil", "roast"]},
{ Question: "aralashtirmoq", RightAnswer: "stir", options: ["mix", "cook", "boil"]},
{ Question: "urib ko‘pik holiga keltirmoq", RightAnswer: "whisk", options: ["stir", "mix", "cook"]},
{ Question: "pech", RightAnswer: "oven", options: ["vegetable", "chef", "cooker"]},
{ Question: "gril", RightAnswer: "grill", options: ["oven", "vegetable", "chef"]},
{ Question: "gaz pechining yuqori qismi", RightAnswer: "hob", options: ["grill", "oven", "vegetable"]},
{ Question: "tez tayyor ovqat", RightAnswer: "fast food", options: ["the shape of sth", "the best medicine", "health care"]},
{ Question: "olib ketiladigan ovqat", RightAnswer: "takeaway", options: ["fast food", "the shape of sth", "the best medicine"]},
{ Question: "alkogolsiz ichimlik", RightAnswer: "soft drink", options: ["takeaway", "fast food", "the shape of sth"]},
{ Question: "gazlangan ichimlik", RightAnswer: "fizzy drink", options: ["soft drink", "takeaway", "fast food"]},
{ Question: "oshxona", RightAnswer: "kitchen", options: ["hob", "grill", "oven"]},
{ Question: "milliy oshxona", RightAnswer: "cuisine", options: ["kitchen", "hob", "grill"]},
{ Question: "choynak", RightAnswer: "kettle", options: ["cuisine", "kitchen", "hob"]},
{ Question: "choynak (choy damlash uchun)", RightAnswer: "teapot", options: ["kettle", "cuisine", "kitchen"]},
{ Question: "menyu", RightAnswer: "menu", options: ["teapot", "kettle", "cuisine"]},
{ Question: "katalog", RightAnswer: "catalogue", options: ["menu", "teapot", "kettle"]},
{ Question: "to‘satdan tashrif buyurmoq", RightAnswer: "drop in (on)", options: ["wear off", "put on", "put down"]},
{ Question: "deyarli (vaqt, yosh, raqam) yetib kelmoq", RightAnswer: "get on for", options: ["drop in (on)", "wear off", "put on"]},
{ Question: "buzilmoq (ovqat)", RightAnswer: "go off", options: ["get on for", "drop in (on)", "wear off"]},
{ Question: "davom ettirmoq", RightAnswer: "go on", options: ["go off", "get on for", "drop in (on)"]},
{ Question: "birovnikiga tashrif buyurmoq", RightAnswer: "go/come round", options: ["go on", "go off", "get on for"]},
{ Question: "davom ettirmoq", RightAnswer: "keep on", options: ["go/come round", "go on", "go off"]},
{ Question: "chiqarib tashlamoq", RightAnswer: "leave out", options: ["keep on", "go/come round", "go on"]},
{ Question: "yoqtirmay qo‘ymoq", RightAnswer: "put off", options: ["leave out", "keep on", "go/come round"]},
{ Question: "duch kelmoq", RightAnswer: "run into", options: ["put off", "leave out", "keep on"]},
{ Question: "tugatmoq", RightAnswer: "run out of", options: ["run into", "put off", "leave out"]},
{ Question: "odatlanmoq", RightAnswer: "take to", options: ["run out of", "run into", "put off"]},
{ Question: "sinab ko‘rmoq", RightAnswer: "try out", options: ["take to", "run out of", "run into"]},
{ Question: "natijaga ega bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "turn out", options: ["try out", "take to", "run out of"]},
{ Question: "kutilmaganda paydo bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "turn up", options: ["turn out", "try out", "take to"]},
{ Question: "ovqat tayyorlamoq", RightAnswer: "make a meal", options: ["spread to a place", "spread sth", "stay in shape"]},
{ Question: "ovqat tayyorlamoq", RightAnswer: "prepare food", options: ["make a meal", "spread to a place", "spread sth"]},
{ Question: "ichimlik ichmoq", RightAnswer: "have a drink", options: ["prepare food", "make a meal", "spread to a place"]},
{ Question: "ichmoq", RightAnswer: "drink (sth)", options: ["have a drink", "prepare food", "make a meal"]},
{ Question: "(kimningdir sharafiga) ichmoq", RightAnswer: "drink to sb", options: ["drink (sth)", "have a drink", "prepare food"]},
{ Question: "(kimningdir sog‘lig‘iga) ichmoq", RightAnswer: "drink to sb’s health", options: ["drink to sb", "drink (sth)", "have a drink"]},
{ Question: "kimga tost ko‘tarmoq", RightAnswer: "drink a toast to sb", options: ["drink to sb’s health", "drink to sb", "drink (sth)"]},
{ Question: "ovqatlantirmoq", RightAnswer: "feed", options: ["drink a toast to sb", "drink to sb’s health", "drink to sb"]},
{ Question: "... bilan oziqlanmoq", RightAnswer: "feed on sth", options: ["feed", "drink a toast to sb", "drink to sb’s health"]},
{ Question: "(biror narsani) to‘ldirmoq", RightAnswer: "fill sth (up)", options: ["feed on sth", "feed", "drink a toast to sb"]},
{ Question: "... bilan to‘ldirmoq", RightAnswer: "fill sth with", options: ["fill sth (up)", "feed on sth", "feed"]},
{ Question: "...ga to‘la ", RightAnswer: "filled with sth", options: ["good to sb", "good at st", "good for sb"]},
{ Question: "...ga to‘la ", RightAnswer: "full of sth", options: ["filled with sth", "good to sb", "good at st"]},
{ Question: "pishirmoq", RightAnswer: "cook a meal", options: ["fill sth with", "fill sth (up)", "feed on sth"]},
{ Question: "ovqat tayyorlamoq", RightAnswer: "prepare food", options: ["cook a meal", "fill sth with", "fill sth (up)"]},
{ Question: "tez tayyor ovqat", RightAnswer: "fast food", options: ["fizzy drink", "soft drink", "takeaway"]},
{ Question: "zararli ovqat", RightAnswer: "junk food", options: ["fast food", "fizzy drink", "soft drink"]},
{ Question: "foydali ovqat", RightAnswer: "health food", options: ["junk food", "fast food", "fizzy drink"]},
{ Question: "ovqatlanmoq", RightAnswer: "have a meal", options: ["prepare food", "cook a meal", "fill sth with"]},
{ Question: "ovqatlanishga chiqmoq", RightAnswer: "go out for a meal", options: ["have a meal", "prepare food", "cook a meal"]},
{ Question: "yozib olmoq", RightAnswer: "take a note of sth", options: ["go out for a meal", "have a meal", "prepare food"]},
{ Question: "yozib qo‘ymoq", RightAnswer: "note sth (down)", options: ["take a note of sth", "go out for a meal", "have a meal"]},
{ Question: "shu safar", RightAnswer: "on this occasion", options: ["in the shape of", "in good health", "the wrong way up"]},
{ Question: "vaqti-vaqti bilan", RightAnswer: "on occasion", options: ["on this occasion", "in the shape of", "in good health"]},
{ Question: "maxsus tadbir", RightAnswer: "special occasion", options: ["health food", "junk food", "fast food"]},
{ Question: "retseptga rioya qilmoq", RightAnswer: "follow a recipe", options: ["note sth (down)", "take a note of sth", "go out for a meal"]},
{ Question: "retsept kitobi", RightAnswer: "recipe book", options: ["special occasion", "health food", "junk food"]},
{ Question: "falokatga sabab bo‘luvchi holat", RightAnswer: "recipe for disaster", options: ["recipe book", "special occasion", "health food"]},
{ Question: "stolni yozmoq", RightAnswer: "lay the table", options: ["follow a recipe", "note sth (down)", "take a note of sth"]},
{ Question: "stol band qilmoq", RightAnswer: "reserve a table", options: ["lay the table", "follow a recipe", "note sth (down)"]},
{ Question: "idishlarni yuvmoq", RightAnswer: "wash the dishes", options: ["reserve a table", "lay the table", "follow a recipe"]},
{ Question: "qo‘lini yuvmoq", RightAnswer: "wash one’s hands", options: ["wash the dishes", "reserve a table", "lay the table"]},
{ Question: "idish yuvish mashinasi", RightAnswer: "dishwasher", options: ["recipe for disaster", "recipe book", "special occasion"]},
{ Question: "bog‘lamoq", RightAnswer: "associate with", options: ["worth st", "worried about", "worry about doing"]},
{ Question: "ehtiyot bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "careful with sth", options: ["associate with", "worth st", "worried about"]},
{ Question: "tanlamoq", RightAnswer: "choose between; choose to do", options: ["careful with sth", "associate with", "worth st"]},
{ Question: "maqtamoq", RightAnswer: "compliment sb on sth", options: ["choose between; choose to do", "careful with sth", "associate with"]},
{ Question: "...ga to‘la", RightAnswer: "full of sth", options: ["compliment sb on sth", "choose between; choose to do", "careful with sth"]},
{ Question: "yetishmovchilik", RightAnswer: "lack sth; lacking in sth", options: ["full of sth", "compliment sb on sth", "choose between; choose to do"]},
{ Question: "taklif qilmoq", RightAnswer: "offer sb sth; offer to do", options: ["lack sth; lacking in sth", "full of sth", "compliment sb on sth"]},
{ Question: "hisoblamoq", RightAnswer: "regard sb as (being) sth", options: ["offer sb sth; offer to do", "lack sth; lacking in sth", "full of sth"]},
{ Question: "eslamoq", RightAnswer: "remember to do; remember sb/st", options: ["regard sb as (being) sth", "offer sb sth; offer to do", "lack sth; lacking in sth"]},
{ Question: "tavsiya qilmoq", RightAnswer: "suggest sth...; suggest that", options: ["remember to do; remember sb/st", "regard sb as (being) sth", "offer sb sth; offer to do"]},
{ Question: "moyil bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "tend to do", options: ["suggest sth...; suggest that", "remember to do; remember sb/st", "regard sb as (being) sth"]},
{ Question: "kutmoq", RightAnswer: "wait for ...; wait and see", options: ["tend to do", "suggest sth...; suggest that", "remember to do; remember sb/st"]},
{ Question: "tayyor bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "willing to do", options: ["wait for ...; wait and see", "tend to do", "suggest sth...; suggest that"]},
{ Question: "xavotirlangan", RightAnswer: "anxious", options: ["freezing", "frozen", "surgical"]},
{ Question: "xavotir bilan", RightAnswer: "anxiously", options: ["strongly", "comfortably", "honestly"]},
{ Question: "xavotir", RightAnswer: "anxiety", options: ["catalogue", "menu", "teapot"]},
{ Question: "qadrlamoq", RightAnswer: "appreciate", options: ["whisk", "stir", "mix"]},
{ Question: "minnatdorchilik bilan", RightAnswer: "appreciative", options: ["anxious", "freezing", "frozen"]},
{ Question: "minnatdorchilik", RightAnswer: "appreciation", options: ["anxiety", "catalogue", "menu"]},
{ Question: "o‘z ichiga olmoq", RightAnswer: "contain", options: ["appreciate", "whisk", "stir"]},
{ Question: "idish", RightAnswer: "container", options: ["appreciation", "anxiety", "catalogue"]},
{ Question: "mazmun, ichidagi narsa", RightAnswer: "content", options: ["container", "appreciation", "anxiety"]},
{ Question: "yaratmoq", RightAnswer: "create", options: ["contain", "appreciate", "whisk"]},
{ Question: "ijodkor(ona)", RightAnswer: "creative", options: ["appreciative", "anxious", "freezing"]},
{ Question: "yaratuv", RightAnswer: "creation", options: ["content", "container", "appreciation"]},
{ Question: "ijodkorlik", RightAnswer: "creativity", options: ["creation", "content", "container"]},
{ Question: "yaratuvchi", RightAnswer: "creator", options: ["creativity", "creation", "content"]},
{ Question: "jirkanmoq", RightAnswer: "disgust", options: ["create", "contain", "appreciate"]},
{ Question: "jirkanch", RightAnswer: "disgusting", options: ["creative", "appreciative", "anxious"]},
{ Question: "jirkanayotgan", RightAnswer: "disgusted", options: ["disgusting", "creative", "appreciative"]},
{ Question: "o‘smoq", RightAnswer: "grow", options: ["disgust", "create", "contain"]},
{ Question: "o‘sish", RightAnswer: "growth", options: ["creator", "creativity", "creation"]},
{ Question: "kattalar", RightAnswer: "grown-up", options: ["vegan", "vegetarian", "criminal"]},
{ Question: "yetishtiruvchi", RightAnswer: "grower", options: ["growth", "creator", "creativity"]},
{ Question: "aralashtirmoq", RightAnswer: "mix", options: ["grow", "disgust", "create"]},
{ Question: "aralashma", RightAnswer: "mixture", options: ["grower", "growth", "creator"]},
{ Question: "mikser", RightAnswer: "mixer", options: ["mixture", "grower", "growth"]},
{ Question: "kelib chiqish", RightAnswer: "origin", options: ["mixer", "mixture", "grower"]},
{ Question: "original tarzda", RightAnswer: "original", options: ["disgusted", "disgusting", "creative"]},
{ Question: "paydo bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "originate", options: ["mix", "grow", "disgust"]},
{ Question: "asoschi", RightAnswer: "originator", options: ["origin", "mixer", "mixture"]},
{ Question: "tayyorlamoq", RightAnswer: "prepare", options: ["originate", "mix", "grow"]},
{ Question: "tayyorgarlik", RightAnswer: "preparation", options: ["originator", "origin", "mixer"]},
{ Question: "tayyorgarlik uchun", RightAnswer: "preparatory", options: ["original", "disgusted", "disgusting"]},
{ Question: "tayyor ", RightAnswer: "prepared", options: ["preparatory", "original", "disgusted"]},
{ Question: "xavfsiz", RightAnswer: "safe", options: ["prepared", "preparatory", "original"]},
{ Question: "xavfli", RightAnswer: "unsafe", options: ["safe", "prepared", "preparatory"]},
{ Question: "xavfsiz tarzda", RightAnswer: "safely", options: ["anxiously", "strongly", "comfortably"]},
{ Question: "xavfsizlik", RightAnswer: "safety", options: ["preparation", "originator", "origin"]},
{ Question: "saqlovchi", RightAnswer: "saver", options: ["safety", "preparation", "originator"]},
{ Question: "hayratlantirmoq", RightAnswer: "surprise", options: ["prepare", "originate", "mix"]},
{ Question: "hayratlanarli", RightAnswer: "surprising", options: ["unsafe", "safe", "prepared"]},
{ Question: "hayratlangan", RightAnswer: "surprised", options: ["surprising", "unsafe", "safe"]},
{ Question: "shirin", RightAnswer: "sweet", options: ["surprised", "surprising", "unsafe"]},
{ Question: "shirin tarzda", RightAnswer: "sweetly", options: ["safely", "anxiously", "strongly"]},
{ Question: "shakar o‘rnini bosuvchi", RightAnswer: "sweetener", options: ["saver", "safety", "preparation"]},
{ Question: "shiralik", RightAnswer: "sweetness", options: ["sweetener", "saver", "safety"]},
{ Question: "sinchkov", RightAnswer: "thorough", options: ["sweet", "surprised", "surprising"]},
{ Question: "puxta", RightAnswer: "thoroughly", options: ["sweetly", "safely", "anxiously"]},
{ Question: "puxtalik", RightAnswer: "thoroughness", options: ["sweetness", "sweetener", "saver"]}],
"level 23" : [
{ Question: "topshirmoq (imtihon)", RightAnswer: "take", options: ["surprise", "prepare", "originate"]},
{ Question: "o‘tmoq (imtihon)", RightAnswer: "pass", options: ["take", "surprise", "prepare"]},
{ Question: "sardor o‘quvchi", RightAnswer: "prefect", options: ["thoroughness", "sweetness", "sweetener"]},
{ Question: "boshlang‘ich o‘quvchi", RightAnswer: "pupil", options: ["prefect", "thoroughness", "sweetness"]},
{ Question: "talaba", RightAnswer: "student", options: ["pupil", "prefect", "thoroughness"]},
{ Question: "o‘qimoq", RightAnswer: "read", options: ["pass", "take", "surprise"]},
{ Question: "o‘rganmoq", RightAnswer: "study", options: ["read", "pass", "take"]},
{ Question: "malaka, sertifikat", RightAnswer: "qualifications", options: ["student", "pupil", "prefect"]},
{ Question: "sifatlar", RightAnswer: "qualities", options: ["qualifications", "student", "pupil"]},
{ Question: "test", RightAnswer: "test", options: ["qualities", "qualifications", "student"]},
{ Question: "imtihon", RightAnswer: "exam", options: ["test", "qualities", "qualifications"]},
{ Question: "sanamoq", RightAnswer: "count", options: ["study", "read", "pass"]},
{ Question: "o‘lchamoq", RightAnswer: "measure", options: ["count", "study", "read"]},
{ Question: "boshlang‘ich", RightAnswer: "primary", options: ["thorough", "sweet", "surprised"]},
{ Question: "o‘rta (ta’lim)", RightAnswer: "secondary", options: ["primary", "thorough", "sweet"]},
{ Question: "yuqori (maktab)", RightAnswer: "high", options: ["secondary", "primary", "thorough"]},
{ Question: "diplom, daraja", RightAnswer: "degree", options: ["exam", "test", "qualities"]},
{ Question: "sertifikat", RightAnswer: "certificate", options: ["degree", "exam", "test"]},
{ Question: "natijalar", RightAnswer: "results", options: ["certificate", "degree", "exam"]},
{ Question: "hamkasb", RightAnswer: "colleague", options: ["results", "certificate", "degree"]},
{ Question: "sinfdosh", RightAnswer: "classmate", options: ["colleague", "results", "certificate"]},
{ Question: "gapirmoq", RightAnswer: "speak", options: ["measure", "count", "study"]},
{ Question: "suhbatlashmoq", RightAnswer: "talk", options: ["speak", "measure", "count"]},
{ Question: "dars", RightAnswer: "lesson", options: ["classmate", "colleague", "results"]},
{ Question: "fan", RightAnswer: "subject", options: ["lesson", "classmate", "colleague"]},
{ Question: "erishmoq", RightAnswer: "achieve", options: ["talk", "speak", "measure"]},
{ Question: "yetib bormoq", RightAnswer: "reach", options: ["achieve", "talk", "speak"]},
{ Question: "vazifa", RightAnswer: "task", options: ["subject", "lesson", "classmate"]},
{ Question: "harakat", RightAnswer: "effort", options: ["task", "subject", "lesson"]},
{ Question: "bilmoq", RightAnswer: "know", options: ["reach", "achieve", "talk"]},
{ Question: "tanimoq", RightAnswer: "recognise", options: ["know", "reach", "achieve"]},
{ Question: "o‘rgatmoq", RightAnswer: "teach", options: ["recognise", "know", "reach"]},
{ Question: "o‘rganmoq", RightAnswer: "learn", options: ["teach", "recognise", "know"]},
{ Question: "tushunib yetmoq", RightAnswer: "catch on", options: ["turn up", "turn out", "try out"]},
{ Question: "fikrini o‘zgartirmoq", RightAnswer: "come around (to)", options: ["catch on", "turn up", "turn out"]},
{ Question: "chizib tashlamoq", RightAnswer: "cross out", options: ["come around (to)", "catch on", "turn up"]},
{ Question: "tushunib yetmoq", RightAnswer: "dawn on", options: ["cross out", "come around (to)", "catch on"]},
{ Question: "hal qilmoq, boshqarish", RightAnswer: "deal with", options: ["dawn on", "cross out", "come around (to)"]},
{ Question: "maktabni tashlamoq", RightAnswer: "drop out", options: ["deal with", "dawn on", "cross out"]},
{ Question: "anglatmoq", RightAnswer: "get at", options: ["drop out", "deal with", "dawn on"]},
{ Question: "davom ettirmoq", RightAnswer: "get on with", options: ["get at", "drop out", "deal with"]},
{ Question: "taslim bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "give in", options: ["get on with", "get at", "drop out"]},
{ Question: "yetib bormoq", RightAnswer: "keep up with", options: ["give in", "get on with", "get at"]},
{ Question: "osongina uddalamoq", RightAnswer: "sail through", options: ["keep up with", "give in", "get on with"]},
{ Question: "tushuntirib bermoq", RightAnswer: "set out", options: ["sail through", "keep up with", "give in"]},
{ Question: "o‘ylab ko‘rmoq", RightAnswer: "think over", options: ["set out", "sail through", "keep up with"]},
{ Question: "e’tibor qaratmoq", RightAnswer: "pay attention (to ...)", options: ["wash one’s hands", "wash the dishes", "reserve a table"]},
{ Question: "e’tiborini tortmoq", RightAnswer: "attract (sb’s) attention", options: ["pay attention (to ...)", "wash one’s hands", "wash the dishes"]},
{ Question: "e’tiborini nimagadir qaratmoq", RightAnswer: "draw (sb’s) attention to sth", options: ["attract (sb’s) attention", "pay attention (to ...)", "wash one’s hands"]},
{ Question: "tanaffus qilmoq", RightAnswer: "take a break", options: ["draw (sb’s) attention to sth", "attract (sb’s) attention", "pay attention (to ...)"]},
{ Question: "tushlik tanaffusi", RightAnswer: "lunch break", options: ["dishwasher", "recipe for disaster", "recipe book"]},
{ Question: "kimga tanaffus bermoq", RightAnswer: "give sb a break", options: ["take a break", "draw (sb’s) attention to sth", "attract (sb’s) attention"]},
{ Question: "muhokama qilmoq", RightAnswer: "have a discussion", options: ["give sb a break", "take a break", "draw (sb’s) attention to sth"]},
{ Question: "(kim bilan) (biror narsa haqida) muhokama qilmoq", RightAnswer: "discuss st", options: ["have a discussion", "give sb a break", "take a break"]},
{ Question: "imtihon topshirmoq", RightAnswer: "take an exam", options: ["discuss st", "have a discussion", "give sb a break"]},
{ Question: "imtihonga kirish", RightAnswer: "sit an exam", options: ["take an exam", "discuss st", "have a discussion"]},
{ Question: "uy vazifasini bajarish", RightAnswer: "do your homework", options: ["sit an exam", "take an exam", "discuss st"]},
{ Question: "uy vazifasi bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "have homework", options: ["do your homework", "sit an exam", "take an exam"]},
{ Question: "g‘oyani so‘roq qilmoq", RightAnswer: "Question an idea", options: ["have homework", "do your homework", "sit an exam"]},
{ Question: "g‘oya bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "have an idea", options: ["Question an idea", "have homework", "do your homework"]},
{ Question: "g‘oyalarni muhokama qilish", RightAnswer: "brainstorm ideas", options: ["have an idea", "Question an idea", "have homework"]},
{ Question: "zo‘r g‘oya", RightAnswer: "bright idea", options: ["lunch break", "dishwasher", "recipe for disaster"]},
{ Question: "hech qanday tasavvurga ega emas", RightAnswer: "have no idea (about)", options: ["brainstorm ideas", "have an idea", "Question an idea"]},
{ Question: "nimadir haqida ko‘p narsani bilish kerak", RightAnswer: "have a lot to learn about sth", options: ["have no idea (about)", "brainstorm ideas", "have an idea"]},
{ Question: "qanday qilishni o‘rganmoq", RightAnswer: "learn to do", options: ["have a lot to learn about sth", "have no idea (about)", "brainstorm ideas"]},
{ Question: "amaliyot orqali o‘rganmoq", RightAnswer: "learn by doing", options: ["learn to do", "have a lot to learn about sth", "have no idea (about)"]},
{ Question: "darsga bormoq", RightAnswer: "have a lesson", options: ["learn by doing", "learn to do", "have a lot to learn about sth"]},
{ Question: "saboq olmoq", RightAnswer: "learn a lesson", options: ["have a lesson", "learn by doing", "learn to do"]},
{ Question: "kimgadir saboq bermoq", RightAnswer: "teach sb a lesson", options: ["learn a lesson", "have a lesson", "learn by doing"]},
{ Question: "ikki soatlik dars", RightAnswer: "double lesson", options: ["bright idea", "lunch break", "dishwasher"]},
{ Question: "qaror qabul qilmoq", RightAnswer: "make up your mind", options: ["teach sb a lesson", "learn a lesson", "have a lesson"]},
{ Question: "yodda tutmoq", RightAnswer: "bear in mind", options: ["make up your mind", "teach sb a lesson", "learn a lesson"]},
{ Question: "ikkilanmoq", RightAnswer: "in two minds about st", options: ["the fact is ", "as a matter of fact", "in turn"]},
{ Question: "fikrini o‘zgartirmoq", RightAnswer: "change your mind", options: ["bear in mind", "make up your mind", "teach sb a lesson"]},
{ Question: "xayolga kelmoq", RightAnswer: "cross your mind", options: ["change your mind", "bear in mind", "make up your mind"]},
{ Question: "mening fikrimcha", RightAnswer: "to my mind", options: ["on occasion", "on this occasion", "in the shape of"]},
{ Question: "fikr bildirmoq", RightAnswer: "give your opinion", options: ["cross your mind", "change your mind", "bear in mind"]},
{ Question: "fikrga ega bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "hold an opinion", options: ["give your opinion", "cross your mind", "change your mind"]},
{ Question: "haqidagi fikr", RightAnswer: "opinion about", options: ["double lesson", "bright idea", "lunch break"]},
{ Question: "imtihondan o‘tmoq", RightAnswer: "pass an exam", options: ["hold an opinion", "give your opinion", "cross your mind"]},
{ Question: "binodan o‘tib ketmoq", RightAnswer: "pass a building", options: ["pass an exam", "hold an opinion", "give your opinion"]},
{ Question: "fikrini tushunmoq", RightAnswer: "see sb’s point", options: ["pass a building", "pass an exam", "hold an opinion"]},
{ Question: "ma’nosini tushunmoq", RightAnswer: "see the point in st", options: ["see sb’s point", "pass a building", "pass an exam"]},
{ Question: "ahamiyat bermoq", RightAnswer: "make a point of doing", options: ["see the point in st", "see sb’s point", "pass a building"]},
{ Question: "tushunmoq", RightAnswer: "make sense of sth", options: ["make a point of doing", "see the point in st", "see sb’s point"]},
{ Question: "bu mantiqan to‘g‘ri ", RightAnswer: "it makes sense", options: ["it’s a pity (that)", "it takes courage to do", "take place"]},
{ Question: "hazil tuyg‘usi", RightAnswer: "sense of humour", options: ["opinion about", "double lesson", "bright idea"]},
{ Question: "taklifni qabul qilmoq", RightAnswer: "accept a suggestion", options: ["make sense of sth", "make a point of doing", "see the point in st"]},
{ Question: "taklif bermoq", RightAnswer: "make a suggestion", options: ["accept a suggestion", "make sense of sth", "make a point of doing"]},
{ Question: "qila olmoq", RightAnswer: "able to do", options: ["willing to do", "wait for ...; wait and see", "tend to do"]},
{ Question: "qoyil qolmoq", RightAnswer: "admire sb", options: ["able to do", "willing to do", "wait for ...; wait and see"]},
{ Question: "maqtanmoq", RightAnswer: "boast of/about st", options: ["admire sb", "able to do", "willing to do"]},
{ Question: "qobiliyatli", RightAnswer: "capable of doing", options: ["boast of/about st", "admire sb", "able to do"]},
{ Question: "tabriklamoq", RightAnswer: "congratulate sb on st", options: ["capable of doing", "boast of/about st", "admire sb"]},
{ Question: "uddalay olmaslik", RightAnswer: "fail to do", options: ["congratulate sb on st", "capable of doing", "boast of/about st"]},
{ Question: "umid qilmoq", RightAnswer: "hope to do; hope that", options: ["fail to do", "congratulate sb on st", "capable of doing"]},
{ Question: "o‘rganmoq", RightAnswer: "learn about st", options: ["hope to do; hope that", "fail to do", "congratulate sb on st"]},
{ Question: "qilishni o‘rganmoq", RightAnswer: "learn to do", options: ["learn about st", "hope to do; hope that", "fail to do"]},
{ Question: "amalda o‘rganmoq", RightAnswer: "learn by doing", options: ["learn to do", "learn about st", "hope to do; hope that"]},
{ Question: "rozi bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "settle for sth", options: ["learn by doing", "learn to do", "learn about st"]},
{ Question: "o‘xshash", RightAnswer: "similar to", options: ["settle for sth", "learn by doing", "learn to do"]},
{ Question: "o‘qimoq", RightAnswer: "study sth; for sth", options: ["similar to", "settle for sth", "learn by doing"]},
{ Question: "muvaffaqiyatga erishmoq", RightAnswer: "succeed in st", options: ["study sth; for sth", "similar to", "settle for sth"]},
{ Question: "mos keladigan", RightAnswer: "suitable for st", options: ["succeed in st", "study sth; for sth", "similar to"]},
{ Question: "akademiya", RightAnswer: "academy", options: ["effort", "task", "subject"]},
{ Question: "akademik", RightAnswer: "academic", options: ["high", "secondary", "primary"]},
{ Question: "akademik tarzda", RightAnswer: "academically", options: ["thoroughly", "sweetly", "safely"]},
{ Question: "qatnashmoq", RightAnswer: "attend", options: ["learn", "teach", "recognise"]},
{ Question: "e’tibor", RightAnswer: "attention", options: ["academy", "effort", "task"]},
{ Question: "diqqat bilan", RightAnswer: "attentive", options: ["academic", "high", "secondary"]},
{ Question: "qatnashish", RightAnswer: "attendance", options: ["attention", "academy", "effort"]},
{ Question: "xizmatkor", RightAnswer: "attendant", options: ["attendance", "attention", "academy"]},
{ Question: "xulq-atvor qilmoq", RightAnswer: "behave", options: ["attend", "learn", "teach"]},
{ Question: "xulq-atvor", RightAnswer: "behaviour", options: ["attendant", "attendance", "attention"]},
{ Question: "tasdiqlamoq", RightAnswer: "certify", options: ["behave", "attend", "learn"]},
{ Question: "sertifikat", RightAnswer: "certificate", options: ["behaviour", "attendant", "attendance"]},
{ Question: "sertifikatlangan", RightAnswer: "certified", options: ["attentive", "academic", "high"]},
{ Question: "o‘qitmoq", RightAnswer: "educate", options: ["certify", "behave", "attend"]},
{ Question: "ta’lim", RightAnswer: "education", options: ["certificate", "behaviour", "attendant"]},
{ Question: "o‘qituvchi", RightAnswer: "educator", options: ["education", "certificate", "behaviour"]},
{ Question: "ta’limiy", RightAnswer: "educational", options: ["certified", "attentive", "academic"]},
{ Question: "muvaffaqiyatsizlikka uchramoq", RightAnswer: "fail", options: ["educate", "certify", "behave"]},
{ Question: "muvaffaqiyatsizlik", RightAnswer: "failure", options: ["educator", "education", "certificate"]},
{ Question: "zaif tomon", RightAnswer: "failing", options: ["failure", "educator", "education"]},
{ Question: "yaxshilamoq", RightAnswer: "improve", options: ["fail", "educate", "certify"]},
{ Question: "rivojlanish", RightAnswer: "improvement", options: ["failing", "failure", "educator"]},
{ Question: "yaxshilangan", RightAnswer: "improved", options: ["educational", "certified", "attentive"]},
{ Question: "kuchli", RightAnswer: "intense", options: ["improved", "educational", "certified"]},
{ Question: "intensivlik", RightAnswer: "intensity", options: ["improvement", "failing", "failure"]},
{ Question: "kuchaytirmoq", RightAnswer: "intensify", options: ["improve", "fail", "educate"]},
{ Question: "kuchli tarzda", RightAnswer: "intensely", options: ["academically", "thoroughly", "sweetly"]},
{ Question: "savodli", RightAnswer: "literate", options: ["intense", "improved", "educational"]},
{ Question: "savodsiz", RightAnswer: "illiterate", options: ["literate", "intense", "improved"]},
{ Question: "savodxonlik", RightAnswer: "literacy", options: ["intensity", "improvement", "failing"]},
{ Question: "adabiyot", RightAnswer: "literature", options: ["literacy", "intensity", "improvement"]},
{ Question: "sabab", RightAnswer: "reason", options: ["literature", "literacy", "intensity"]},
{ Question: "mantiqli", RightAnswer: "reasonable", options: ["illiterate", "literate", "intense"]},
{ Question: "mantiqan", RightAnswer: "reasonably", options: ["intensely", "academically", "thoroughly"]},
{ Question: "izoh", RightAnswer: "reasoning", options: ["reason", "literature", "literacy"]},
{ Question: "takrorlamoq", RightAnswer: "revise", options: ["intensify", "improve", "fail"]},
{ Question: "takrorlash", RightAnswer: "revision", options: ["reasoning", "reason", "literature"]},
{ Question: "ko‘rib chiqilgan", RightAnswer: "revised", options: ["reasonable", "illiterate", "literate"]},
{ Question: "olim", RightAnswer: "scholar", options: ["revision", "reasoning", "reason"]},
{ Question: "grant", RightAnswer: "scholarship", options: ["scholar", "revision", "reasoning"]},
{ Question: "ilmiy", RightAnswer: "scholarly", options: ["revised", "reasonable", "illiterate"]},
{ Question: "o‘quvga oid", RightAnswer: "scholastic", options: ["scholarly", "revised", "reasonable"]},
{ Question: "hal qilmoq", RightAnswer: "solve", options: ["revise", "intensify", "improve"]},
{ Question: "yechim", RightAnswer: "solution", options: ["scholarship", "scholar", "revision"]},
{ Question: "hal qilinadigan", RightAnswer: "solvable", options: ["scholastic", "scholarly", "revised"]},
{ Question: "o‘rganmoq", RightAnswer: "study", options: ["solve", "revise", "intensify"]},
{ Question: "talaba", RightAnswer: "student", options: ["solution", "scholarship", "scholar"]},
{ Question: "o‘qishlar", RightAnswer: "studies", options: ["student", "solution", "scholarship"]},
{ Question: "tirishqoq", RightAnswer: "studious", options: ["solvable", "scholastic", "scholarly"]},
{ Question: "o‘rgatmoq", RightAnswer: "teach", options: ["study", "solve", "revise"]},
{ Question: "o‘qituvchi", RightAnswer: "teacher", options: ["studies", "student", "solution"]},
{ Question: "o‘rgatgan", RightAnswer: "taught", options: ["studious", "solvable", "scholastic"]},
{ Question: "o‘ylamoq", RightAnswer: "think", options: ["teach", "study", "solve"]},
{ Question: "o‘y", RightAnswer: "thought", options: ["teacher", "studies", "student"]},
{ Question: "o‘ylab bo‘ladigan", RightAnswer: "thinkable", options: ["taught", "studious", "solvable"]},
{ Question: "o‘ychan", RightAnswer: "thoughtful", options: ["thinkable", "taught", "studious"]},
{ Question: "beparvo", RightAnswer: "thoughtless", options: ["thoughtful", "thinkable", "taught"]},
{ Question: "tushunmoq", RightAnswer: "understand", options: ["think", "teach", "study"]},
{ Question: "tushunish", RightAnswer: "understanding", options: ["thought", "teacher", "studies"]},
{ Question: "tushungan", RightAnswer: "understood", options: ["thoughtless", "thoughtful", "thinkable"]},
{ Question: "tushunarli", RightAnswer: "understandable", options: ["understood", "thoughtless", "thoughtful"]},
{ Question: "tushunarli tarzda", RightAnswer: "understandably", options: ["reasonably", "intensely", "academically"]}],
"level 24" : [
{ Question: "shahar", RightAnswer: "urban", options: ["understandable", "understood", "thoughtless"]},
{ Question: "shahar atrofi", RightAnswer: "suburban", options: ["urban", "understandable", "understood"]},
{ Question: "qishloq", RightAnswer: "rural", options: ["suburban", "urban", "understandable"]},
{ Question: "toza", RightAnswer: "clean (adj)", options: ["rural", "suburban", "urban"]},
{ Question: "musaffo", RightAnswer: "clear (adj)", options: ["clean (adj)", "rural", "suburban"]},
{ Question: "momaqaldiroq", RightAnswer: "thunder", options: ["understanding", "thought", "teacher"]},
{ Question: "chaqmoq", RightAnswer: "lightning", options: ["thunder", "understanding", "thought"]},
{ Question: "tutun aralash tuman", RightAnswer: "smog", options: ["lightning", "thunder", "understanding"]},
{ Question: "tuman", RightAnswer: "fog", options: ["smog", "lightning", "thunder"]},
{ Question: "tutun", RightAnswer: "smoke", options: ["fog", "smog", "lightning"]},
{ Question: "yengil tuman", RightAnswer: "mist", options: ["smoke", "fog", "smog"]},
{ Question: "shiddat bilan yog‘moq", RightAnswer: "pour", options: ["understand", "think", "teach"]},
{ Question: "mayda yomg‘ir yog‘moq", RightAnswer: "drizzle", options: ["pour", "understand", "think"]},
{ Question: "suv toshqini", RightAnswer: "flood", options: ["mist", "smoke", "fog"]},
{ Question: "global", RightAnswer: "global", options: ["clear (adj)", "clean (adj)", "rural"]},
{ Question: "butun dunyo bo‘ylab", RightAnswer: "worldwide", options: ["global", "clear (adj)", "clean (adj)"]},
{ Question: "ob-havo", RightAnswer: "weather", options: ["flood", "mist", "smoke"]},
{ Question: "iqlim", RightAnswer: "climate", options: ["weather", "flood", "mist"]},
{ Question: "atrof-muhit", RightAnswer: "environment", options: ["climate", "weather", "flood"]},
{ Question: "o‘rab turgan joylar", RightAnswer: "surroundings", options: ["environment", "climate", "weather"]},
{ Question: "tekislik", RightAnswer: "plain", options: ["surroundings", "environment", "climate"]},
{ Question: "yer", RightAnswer: "land", options: ["plain", "surroundings", "environment"]},
{ Question: "dala", RightAnswer: "field", options: ["land", "plain", "surroundings"]},
{ Question: "cho‘l", RightAnswer: "desert", options: ["field", "land", "plain"]},
{ Question: "ob-havo bashorati", RightAnswer: "forecast", options: ["desert", "field", "land"]},
{ Question: "bashorat", RightAnswer: "prediction", options: ["forecast", "desert", "field"]},
{ Question: "shamol", RightAnswer: "wind", options: ["prediction", "forecast", "desert"]},
{ Question: "havo", RightAnswer: "air", options: ["wind", "prediction", "forecast"]},
{ Question: "qirilib ketgan", RightAnswer: "extinct", options: ["worldwide", "global", "clear (adj)"]},
{ Question: "yo‘qolib ketish xavfi ostida", RightAnswer: "endangered", options: ["extinct", "worldwide", "global"]},
{ Question: "chiqindi", RightAnswer: "waste", options: ["air", "wind", "prediction"]},
{ Question: "axlat", RightAnswer: "litter", options: ["waste", "air", "wind"]},
{ Question: "chiqindi", RightAnswer: "rubbish", options: ["litter", "waste", "air"]},
{ Question: "suv ombori", RightAnswer: "reservoir", options: ["rubbish", "litter", "waste"]},
{ Question: "ko‘l", RightAnswer: "lake", options: ["reservoir", "rubbish", "litter"]},
{ Question: "ko‘lmak", RightAnswer: "puddle", options: ["lake", "reservoir", "rubbish"]},
{ Question: "hovuzcha", RightAnswer: "pond", options: ["puddle", "lake", "reservoir"]},
{ Question: "qayta ishlash", RightAnswer: "recycle", options: ["drizzle", "pour", "understand"]},
{ Question: "qayta ishlatish", RightAnswer: "reuse", options: ["recycle", "drizzle", "pour"]},
{ Question: "talab qilmoq", RightAnswer: "call for", options: ["think over", "set out", "sail through"]},
{ Question: "bekor qilmoq", RightAnswer: "call off", options: ["call for", "think over", "set out"]},
{ Question: "ob-havo yaxshilanmoq", RightAnswer: "clear up", options: ["call off", "call for", "think over"]},
{ Question: "uzib qo‘ymoq (aloqa, elektr)", RightAnswer: "cut off", options: ["clear up", "call off", "call for"]},
{ Question: "sustlashmoq (shamol, kuch)", RightAnswer: "die down", options: ["cut off", "clear up", "call off"]},
{ Question: "ta’mirlamoq", RightAnswer: "do up", options: ["die down", "cut off", "clear up"]},
{ Question: "qabul qilib, kurashmoq", RightAnswer: "face up to", options: ["do up", "die down", "cut off"]},
{ Question: "kayfiyatni tushirmoq", RightAnswer: "get down", options: ["face up to", "do up", "die down"]},
{ Question: "sababini ko‘rsatmoq", RightAnswer: "put down to", options: ["get down", "face up to", "do up"]},
{ Question: "o‘chirmoq (olov)", RightAnswer: "put out", options: ["put down to", "get down", "face up to"]},
{ Question: "boshlanib, uzoq davom etmoq", RightAnswer: "set in", options: ["put out", "put down to", "get down"]},
{ Question: "ramz bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "stand for", options: ["set in", "put out", "put down to"]},
{ Question: "buzmoq", RightAnswer: "tear down", options: ["stand for", "set in", "put out"]},
{ Question: "tashlab yubormoq", RightAnswer: "throw away", options: ["tear down", "stand for", "set in"]},
{ Question: "boshqaruvni yo‘qotmoq", RightAnswer: "lose control", options: ["make a suggestion", "accept a suggestion", "make sense of sth"]},
{ Question: "boshqaruvda", RightAnswer: "in control", options: ["to my mind", "on occasion", "on this occasion"]},
{ Question: "boshqaruvdan chiqib ketgan ", RightAnswer: "out of control", options: ["full of sth", "filled with sth", "good to sb"]},
{ Question: "ta’sir ko‘rsatmoq", RightAnswer: "have an effect", options: ["lose control", "make a suggestion", "accept a suggestion"]},
{ Question: "kuchga kirmoq", RightAnswer: "take effect", options: ["have an effect", "lose control", "make a suggestion"]},
{ Question: "tugatmoq", RightAnswer: "come to the end of sth", options: ["take effect", "have an effect", "lose control"]},
{ Question: "oxirida", RightAnswer: "in the end", options: ["in control", "to my mind", "on occasion"]},
{ Question: "...ning oxirida", RightAnswer: "at the end", options: ["in the end", "in control", "to my mind"]},
{ Question: "yerda", RightAnswer: "on the floor", options: ["at the end", "in the end", "in control"]},
{ Question: "yerda", RightAnswer: "on the ground", options: ["on the floor", "at the end", "in the end"]},
{ Question: "birinchi qavat", RightAnswer: "first floor", options: ["sense of humour", "opinion about", "double lesson"]},
{ Question: "shovqin-suron qilmoq", RightAnswer: "make a fuss", options: ["come to the end of sth", "take effect", "have an effect"]},
{ Question: "qachongacha", RightAnswer: " as long as", options: ["on the ground", "on the floor", "at the end"]},
{ Question: "ko‘p vaqt olmoq", RightAnswer: "take a long time", options: ["make a fuss", "come to the end of sth", "take effect"]},
{ Question: "juda xohlamoq", RightAnswer: "long to do", options: ["take a long time", "make a fuss", "come to the end of sth"]},
{ Question: "nimanidir juda xohlamoq", RightAnswer: "long for sth", options: ["long to do", "take a long time", "make a fuss"]},
{ Question: "ko‘z tashlamoq", RightAnswer: "take a look at", options: ["long for sth", "long to do", "take a long time"]},
{ Question: "o‘xshamoq", RightAnswer: "look like", options: ["take a look at", "long for sth", "long to do"]},
{ Question: "qaramoq/qidirmoq", RightAnswer: "look a", options: ["look like", "take a look at", "long for sth"]},
{ Question: "tartibsizlik qilmoq", RightAnswer: "make a mess", options: ["look a", "look like", "take a look at"]},
{ Question: "tartibsizlikda", RightAnswer: "in a mess", options: [" as long as", "on the ground", "on the floor"]},
{ Question: "javobgarlikni bo'yniga olmoq", RightAnswer: "take responsibility for st", options: ["make a mess", "look a", "look like"]},
{ Question: "dush qabul qilmoq", RightAnswer: "take a shower", options: ["take responsibility for st", "make a mess", "look a"]},
{ Question: "qisqa yomg‘ir", RightAnswer: "a rain shower", options: ["first floor", "sense of humour", "opinion about"]},
{ Question: "ko‘rib qolmoq", RightAnswer: "catch sight of", options: ["take a shower", "take responsibility for st", "make a mess"]},
{ Question: "(nimanidir) ko‘rib turish", RightAnswer: "in sight of sth", options: ["in a mess", " as long as", "on the ground"]},
{ Question: "bir qarashda ", RightAnswer: "at first sight", options: ["it makes sense", "it’s a pity (that)", "it takes courage to do"]},
{ Question: "ko‘ngli qolgan ", RightAnswer: "disappointed by ", options: ["out of control", "full of sth", "filled with sth"]},
{ Question: "ob-havo prognozi", RightAnswer: "weather forecast", options: ["a rain shower", "first floor", "sense of humour"]},
{ Question: "o‘zini yomon his qilmoq", RightAnswer: "under the weather", options: ["in two minds about st", "the fact is ", "as a matter of fact"]},
{ Question: "butun dunyo bo‘ylab", RightAnswer: "all over the world", options: ["in sight of sth", "in a mess", " as long as"]},
{ Question: "butun dunyo bo‘ylab", RightAnswer: "around the world", options: ["all over the world", "in sight of sth", "in a mess"]},
{ Question: "butun dunyo bo‘ylab", RightAnswer: "throughout the world", options: ["around the world", "all over the world", "in sight of sth"]},
{ Question: "dunyo rekordi", RightAnswer: "world record", options: ["weather forecast", "a rain shower", "first floor"]},
{ Question: "xabardor", RightAnswer: "aware of sth", options: ["suitable for st", "succeed in st", "study sth; for sth"]},
{ Question: "qoplangan", RightAnswer: "covered in sth", options: ["aware of sth", "suitable for st", "succeed in st"]},
{ Question: "ko‘ngli qolgan", RightAnswer: "disappointed with", options: ["covered in sth", "aware of sth", "suitable for st"]},
{ Question: "bundan tashqari", RightAnswer: "except st", options: ["disappointed with", "covered in sth", "aware of sth"]},
{ Question: "kutmoq", RightAnswer: "expect", options: ["except st", "disappointed with", "covered in sth"]},
{ Question: "tanish", RightAnswer: "familiar with sth; familiar to sb", options: ["expect", "except st", "disappointed with"]},
{ Question: "mashhur", RightAnswer: "famous for st", options: ["familiar with sth; familiar to sb", "expect", "except st"]},
{ Question: "qaramoq", RightAnswer: "glance at", options: ["famous for st", "familiar with sth; familiar to sb", "expect"]},
{ Question: "qiyin", RightAnswer: "hard to do", options: ["glance at", "famous for st", "familiar with sth; familiar to sb"]},
{ Question: "oldini olmoq", RightAnswer: "prevent sth; prevent sb from doing", options: ["hard to do", "glance at", "famous for st"]},
{ Question: "yetishmaslik", RightAnswer: "short of sth", options: ["prevent sth; prevent sb from doing", "hard to do", "glance at"]},
{ Question: "ogohlantirmoq", RightAnswer: "warn sb about st", options: ["short of sth", "prevent sth; prevent sb from doing", "hard to do"]},
{ Question: "aniq", RightAnswer: "accurate", options: ["endangered", "extinct", "worldwide"]},
{ Question: "aniqlik bilan", RightAnswer: "accurately", options: ["understandably", "reasonably", "intensely"]},
{ Question: "noto‘g‘rilik", RightAnswer: "inaccuracy", options: ["pond", "puddle", "lake"]},
{ Question: "xavf", RightAnswer: "danger", options: ["inaccuracy", "pond", "puddle"]},
{ Question: "xavfli", RightAnswer: "dangerous", options: ["accurate", "endangered", "extinct"]},
{ Question: "xavf ostiga qo‘ymoq", RightAnswer: "endanger", options: ["reuse", "recycle", "drizzle"]},
{ Question: "yo‘qolib ketish xavfi ostidagi", RightAnswer: "endangered", options: ["dangerous", "accurate", "endangered"]},
{ Question: "rivojlantirmoq", RightAnswer: "develop", options: ["endanger", "reuse", "recycle"]},
{ Question: "rivojlangan", RightAnswer: "developed", options: ["endangered", "dangerous", "accurate"]},
{ Question: "rivojlanayotgan", RightAnswer: "developing", options: ["developed", "endangered", "dangerous"]},
{ Question: "ishlab chiquvchi", RightAnswer: "developer", options: ["danger", "inaccuracy", "pond"]},
{ Question: "rivojlanish", RightAnswer: "development", options: ["developer", "danger", "inaccuracy"]},
{ Question: "atrof-muhit", RightAnswer: "environment", options: ["development", "developer", "danger"]},
{ Question: "ekologik", RightAnswer: "environmental", options: ["developing", "developed", "endangered"]},
{ Question: "ekolog", RightAnswer: "environmentalist", options: ["environment", "development", "developer"]},
{ Question: "oxirgi daraja", RightAnswer: "extremity", options: ["environmentalist", "environment", "development"]},
{ Question: "haddan tashqari", RightAnswer: "extreme", options: ["environmental", "developing", "developed"]},
{ Question: "ekstremist", RightAnswer: "extremist", options: ["extremity", "environmentalist", "environment"]},
{ Question: "muzlatmoq", RightAnswer: "freeze", options: ["develop", "endanger", "reuse"]},
{ Question: "muzlagan", RightAnswer: "frozen", options: ["extreme", "environmental", "developing"]},
{ Question: "sovuq", RightAnswer: "freezing", options: ["frozen", "extreme", "environmental"]},
{ Question: "muzlatkich", RightAnswer: "freezer", options: ["extremist", "extremity", "environmentalist"]},
{ Question: "yer yuzi", RightAnswer: "globe", options: ["freezer", "extremist", "extremity"]},
{ Question: "global", RightAnswer: "global", options: ["freezing", "frozen", "extreme"]},
{ Question: "buyuk", RightAnswer: "great", options: ["global", "freezing", "frozen"]},
{ Question: "juda", RightAnswer: "greatly", options: ["accurately", "understandably", "reasonably"]},
{ Question: "buyuklik", RightAnswer: "greatness", options: ["globe", "freezer", "extremist"]},
{ Question: "zarar", RightAnswer: "harm", options: ["greatness", "globe", "freezer"]},
{ Question: "zararli", RightAnswer: "harmful", options: ["great", "global", "freezing"]},
{ Question: "zararsiz", RightAnswer: "harmless", options: ["harmful", "great", "global"]},
{ Question: "zararlangan", RightAnswer: "harmed", options: ["harmless", "harmful", "great"]},
{ Question: "ehtimol", RightAnswer: "likely", options: ["harmed", "harmless", "harmful"]},
{ Question: "ehtimolsiz", RightAnswer: "unlikely", options: ["likely", "harmed", "harmless"]},
{ Question: "ehtimollik", RightAnswer: "likelihood", options: ["harm", "greatness", "globe"]},
{ Question: "past", RightAnswer: "low", options: ["unlikely", "likely", "harmed"]},
{ Question: "pasaytirmoq", RightAnswer: "lower", options: ["freeze", "develop", "endanger"]},
{ Question: "pastlik", RightAnswer: "lowness", options: ["likelihood", "harm", "greatness"]},
{ Question: "tabiat", RightAnswer: "nature", options: ["lowness", "likelihood", "harm"]},
{ Question: "tabiiy", RightAnswer: "natural", options: ["low", "unlikely", "likely"]},
{ Question: "qo‘shni", RightAnswer: "neighbour", options: ["nature", "lowness", "likelihood"]},
{ Question: "mahalla", RightAnswer: "neighbourhood", options: ["neighbour", "nature", "lowness"]},
{ Question: "qo‘shni (hudud)", RightAnswer: "neighbouring", options: ["natural", "low", "unlikely"]},
{ Question: "ifloslantirmoq", RightAnswer: "pollute", options: ["lower", "freeze", "develop"]},
{ Question: "ifloslangan", RightAnswer: "polluted", options: ["neighbouring", "natural", "low"]},
{ Question: "ifloslanish", RightAnswer: "pollution", options: ["neighbourhood", "neighbour", "nature"]},
{ Question: "ifloslantiruvchi", RightAnswer: "pollutant", options: ["pollution", "neighbourhood", "neighbour"]},
{ Question: "yashamoq", RightAnswer: "reside", options: ["pollute", "lower", "freeze"]},
{ Question: "yashash joyi", RightAnswer: "residence", options: ["pollutant", "pollution", "neighbourhood"]},
{ Question: "yashovchi", RightAnswer: "resident", options: ["residence", "pollutant", "pollution"]},
{ Question: "yashash uchun mo‘ljallangan", RightAnswer: "residential", options: ["polluted", "neighbouring", "natural"]},
{ Question: "quyosh", RightAnswer: "sun", options: ["resident", "residence", "pollutant"]},
{ Question: "quyoshli", RightAnswer: "sunny", options: ["residential", "polluted", "neighbouring"]},
{ Question: "quyosh nuri", RightAnswer: "sunshine", options: ["sun", "resident", "residence"]}],
"level 25" : [
{ Question: "iqtisodiy", RightAnswer: "economic", options: ["sunny", "residential", "polluted"]},
{ Question: "tejamkor", RightAnswer: "economical", options: ["economic", "sunny", "residential"]},
{ Question: "chegirma", RightAnswer: "discount", options: ["sunshine", "sun", "resident"]},
{ Question: "taklif", RightAnswer: "offer", options: ["discount", "sunshine", "sun"]},
{ Question: "kassada", RightAnswer: "till", options: ["world record", "weather forecast", "a rain shower"]},
{ Question: "nazorat nuqtasi (supermarket kassasi)", RightAnswer: "checkout", options: ["till", "world record", "weather forecast"]},
{ Question: "chek", RightAnswer: "receipt", options: ["offer", "discount", "sunshine"]},
{ Question: "hisob", RightAnswer: "bill", options: ["receipt", "offer", "discount"]},
{ Question: "narx", RightAnswer: "price", options: ["bill", "receipt", "offer"]},
{ Question: "qiymat", RightAnswer: "cost", options: ["price", "bill", "receipt"]},
{ Question: "mahsulotlar", RightAnswer: "products", options: ["cost", "price", "bill"]},
{ Question: "tovarlar", RightAnswer: "goods", options: ["products", "cost", "price"]},
{ Question: "ishlab chiqarmoq", RightAnswer: "make", options: ["reside", "pollute", "lower"]},
{ Question: "brend", RightAnswer: "brand", options: ["goods", "products", "cost"]},
{ Question: "mayda pul", RightAnswer: "change", options: ["brand", "goods", "products"]},
{ Question: "naqd pul", RightAnswer: "cash", options: ["change", "brand", "goods"]},
{ Question: "qaytarilgan pul", RightAnswer: "refund", options: ["cash", "change", "brand"]},
{ Question: "almashinuv", RightAnswer: "exchange", options: ["refund", "cash", "change"]},
{ Question: "arzonlashtirilgan narx", RightAnswer: "bargain", options: ["exchange", "refund", "cash"]},
{ Question: "sotuv", RightAnswer: "sale", options: ["bargain", "exchange", "refund"]},
{ Question: "boylik", RightAnswer: "wealth", options: ["sale", "bargain", "exchange"]},
{ Question: "katta boylik", RightAnswer: "fortune", options: ["wealth", "sale", "bargain"]},
{ Question: "qalbaki", RightAnswer: "fake", options: ["economical", "economic", "sunny"]},
{ Question: "plastik", RightAnswer: "plastic", options: ["fake", "economical", "economic"]},
{ Question: "ishonmoq, umid qilmoq", RightAnswer: "bank on", options: ["throw away", "tear down", "stand for"]},
{ Question: "tasodifan uchratmoq", RightAnswer: "come across", options: ["bank on", "throw away", "tear down"]},
{ Question: "qiyin topiladigan narsani qo‘lga kiritmoq", RightAnswer: "come by", options: ["come across", "bank on", "throw away"]},
{ Question: "meros qilib olmoq", RightAnswer: "come into", options: ["come by", "come across", "bank on"]},
{ Question: "...siz yashamoq", RightAnswer: "do without", options: ["come into", "come by", "come across"]},
{ Question: "tirikchilik qilmoq", RightAnswer: "get by", options: ["do without", "come into", "come by"]},
{ Question: "tugatmoq, yeb qo‘ymoq", RightAnswer: "get through", options: ["get by", "do without", "come into"]},
{ Question: "tekinga bermoq; sirni oshkor qilmoq", RightAnswer: "give away", options: ["get through", "get by", "do without"]},
{ Question: "tirikchilik qilmoq (biror narsadan)", RightAnswer: "live on", options: ["give away", "get through", "get by"]},
{ Question: "atrofiga qarab chiqmoq", RightAnswer: "look round", options: ["live on", "give away", "get through"]},
{ Question: "chekka yozib bermoq", RightAnswer: "make out", options: ["look round", "live on", "give away"]},
{ Question: "qoplamoq, kompensatsiya qilmoq", RightAnswer: "make up for", options: ["make out", "look round", "live on"]},
{ Question: "pul yig‘moq", RightAnswer: "put by", options: ["make up for", "make out", "look round"]},
{ Question: "asta-sekin pul yig‘moq", RightAnswer: "save up", options: ["put by", "make up for", "make out"]},
{ Question: "...ning miqdori", RightAnswer: "an amount of sth", options: ["checkout", "till", "world record"]},
{ Question: "katta miqdorda", RightAnswer: "in large amounts", options: ["throughout the world", "around the world", "all over the world"]},
{ Question: "...ga teng bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "amount to", options: ["catch sight of", "take a shower", "take responsibility for st"]},
{ Question: "(kimdandir) pul olish", RightAnswer: "charge sb (an amount of money)", options: ["amount to", "catch sight of", "take a shower"]},
{ Question: "to‘lov qilmoq", RightAnswer: "pay a charge", options: ["charge sb (an amount of money)", "amount to", "catch sight of"]},
{ Question: "javobgarlikni o‘z zimmasiga olmoq", RightAnswer: "take charge (of sth...)", options: ["pay a charge", "charge sb (an amount of money)", "amount to"]},
{ Question: "javobgar bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "in charge (of sth...)", options: ["in large amounts", "throughout the world", "around the world"]},
{ Question: "qarzda", RightAnswer: "in debt", options: ["in charge (of sth...)", "in large amounts", "throughout the world"]},
{ Question: "qarzga kirib qolmoq", RightAnswer: "get in debt", options: ["take charge (of sth...)", "pay a charge", "charge sb (an amount of money)"]},
{ Question: "qarzni to‘lamoq", RightAnswer: "clear a debt", options: ["get in debt", "take charge (of sth...)", "pay a charge"]},
{ Question: "kimga minnatdor bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "owe sb a debt of gratitude", options: ["clear a debt", "get in debt", "take charge (of sth...)"]},
{ Question: "talab yuqori", RightAnswer: "in demand", options: ["in debt", "in charge (of sth...)", "in large amounts"]},
{ Question: "talabga binoan", RightAnswer: "on demand", options: ["in demand", "in debt", "in charge (of sth...)"]},
{ Question: "nimagadir talab", RightAnswer: "a demand for sth", options: ["an amount of sth", "checkout", "till"]},
{ Question: "yetarli bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "have enough", options: ["owe sb a debt of gratitude", "clear a debt", "get in debt"]},
{ Question: "qilishga yetarli (narsa) bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "have enough sth", options: ["have enough", "owe sb a debt of gratitude", "clear a debt"]},
{ Question: "yetarli, bas ", RightAnswer: "enough is enough", options: ["at first sight", "it makes sense", "it’s a pity (that)"]},
{ Question: "kimningdir o‘z hisobidan", RightAnswer: "at sb’s own expense", options: ["on demand", "in demand", "in debt"]},
{ Question: "xarajat qilmoq", RightAnswer: "go to the expense", options: ["have enough sth", "have enough", "owe sb a debt of gratitude"]},
{ Question: "ish xarajati", RightAnswer: "business expense", options: ["a demand for sth", "an amount of sth", "checkout"]},
{ Question: "xizmat safari uchun hisob", RightAnswer: "expense account", options: ["business expense", "a demand for sth", "an amount of sth"]},
{ Question: "katta boylik topmoq", RightAnswer: "make a fortune", options: ["go to the expense", "have enough sth", "have enough"]},
{ Question: "juda qimmatga tushmoq", RightAnswer: "cost (you) a fortune", options: ["make a fortune", "go to the expense", "have enough sth"]},
{ Question: "boyib ketmoq", RightAnswer: "make your fortune", options: ["cost (you) a fortune", "make a fortune", "go to the expense"]},
{ Question: "...ning ko‘payishi", RightAnswer: "an increase in sth", options: ["expense account", "business expense", "a demand for sth"]},
{ Question: "ish haqi oshishi", RightAnswer: "a wage increase", options: ["an increase in sth", "expense account", "business expense"]},
{ Question: "hech bo‘lmasa", RightAnswer: "at least", options: ["at sb’s own expense", "on demand", "in demand"]},
{ Question: "eng kamida", RightAnswer: "at the very least", options: ["at least", "at sb’s own expense", "on demand"]},
{ Question: "oxirgi emas, muhim ", RightAnswer: "last but not least", options: ["enough is enough", "at first sight", "it makes sense"]},
{ Question: "pul topmoq", RightAnswer: "make money", options: ["make your fortune", "cost (you) a fortune", "make a fortune"]},
{ Question: "pul sarflamoq", RightAnswer: "spend money (on sth...)", options: ["make money", "make your fortune", "cost (you) a fortune"]},
{ Question: "pul yetishmaydi ", RightAnswer: "short of money", options: ["disappointed by ", "out of control", "full of sth"]},
{ Question: "pul uchun qilmoq", RightAnswer: "do sth for the money", options: ["spend money (on sth...)", "make money", "make your fortune"]},
{ Question: "payqamoq", RightAnswer: "notice sb doing/do", options: ["do sth for the money", "spend money (on sth...)", "make money"]},
{ Question: "e’tibor qaratmoq", RightAnswer: "take notice of sth", options: ["notice sb doing/do", "do sth for the money", "spend money (on sth...)"]},
{ Question: "qisqa muddatda", RightAnswer: "at short notice", options: ["at the very least", "at least", "at sb’s own expense"]},
{ Question: "ogohlantirmoq", RightAnswer: "give sb notice of", options: ["take notice of sth", "notice sb doing/do", "do sth for the money"]},
{ Question: "foyda ko‘rmoq", RightAnswer: "make a profit", options: ["give sb notice of", "take notice of sth", "notice sb doing/do"]},
{ Question: "pul tejamoq", RightAnswer: "save money", options: ["make a profit", "give sb notice of", "take notice of sth"]},
{ Question: "keyinga saqlab qo‘ymoq", RightAnswer: "save sth for later", options: ["save money", "make a profit", "give sb notice of"]},
{ Question: "xarid qilmoq", RightAnswer: "do the shopping", options: ["save sth for later", "save money", "make a profit"]},
{ Question: "xaridga chiqmoq", RightAnswer: "go shopping", options: ["do the shopping", "save sth for later", "save money"]},
{ Question: "savdo markazi", RightAnswer: "shopping centre", options: ["a wage increase", "an increase in sth", "expense account"]},
{ Question: "faqat vitrina tomosha qilish", RightAnswer: "window shopping", options: ["shopping centre", "a wage increase", "an increase in sth"]},
{ Question: "qurb qilmoq", RightAnswer: "afford to do", options: ["warn sb about st", "short of sth", "prevent sth; prevent sb from doing"]},
{ Question: "tortishmoq", RightAnswer: "argue with sb", options: ["afford to do", "warn sb about st", "short of sth"]},
{ Question: "yolvoroq", RightAnswer: "beg sb (for sth); beg sb to do", options: ["argue with sb", "afford to do", "warn sb about st"]},
{ Question: "tegishli bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "belong to", options: ["beg sb (for sth); beg sb to do", "argue with sb", "afford to do"]},
{ Question: "qarzga olmoq", RightAnswer: "borrow sth (from sb)", options: ["belong to", "beg sb (for sth); beg sb to do", "argue with sb"]},
{ Question: "haq olmoq", RightAnswer: "charge sb", options: ["borrow sth (from sb)", "belong to", "beg sb (for sth); beg sb to do"]},
{ Question: "talab qilmoq", RightAnswer: "demand sth (from sb); demand that", options: ["charge sb", "borrow sth (from sb)", "belong to"]},
{ Question: "unutmoq", RightAnswer: "forget to do; forget doing", options: ["demand sth (from sb); demand that", "charge sb", "borrow sth (from sb)"]},
{ Question: "qarzga bermoq", RightAnswer: "lend sth to sb; lend sb sth", options: ["forget to do; forget doing", "demand sth (from sb); demand that", "charge sb"]},
{ Question: "to‘lamoq", RightAnswer: "pay sb; pay sth", options: ["lend sth to sb; lend sb sth", "forget to do; forget doing", "demand sth (from sb); demand that"]},
{ Question: "foyda ko‘rmoq", RightAnswer: "profit from st", options: ["pay sb; pay sth", "lend sth to sb; lend sb sth", "forget to do; forget doing"]},
{ Question: "qutqarmoq, tejab qo‘ymoq", RightAnswer: "save sb from sth...; save sth", options: ["profit from st", "pay sb; pay sth", "lend sth to sb; lend sb sth"]},
{ Question: "sarflamoq", RightAnswer: "spend sth", options: ["save sb from sth...; save sth", "profit from st", "pay sb; pay sth"]},
{ Question: "qabul qilmoq", RightAnswer: "accept", options: ["make", "reside", "pollute"]},
{ Question: "qabul qilish", RightAnswer: "acceptance", options: ["fortune", "wealth", "sale"]},
{ Question: "qabul qilinadigan", RightAnswer: "acceptable", options: ["plastic", "fake", "economical"]},
{ Question: "qabul qilinadigan tarzda", RightAnswer: "acceptably", options: ["greatly", "accurately", "understandably"]},
{ Question: "yordam bermoq", RightAnswer: "assist", options: ["accept", "make", "reside"]},
{ Question: "yordam", RightAnswer: "assistance", options: ["acceptance", "fortune", "wealth"]},
{ Question: "yordamchi", RightAnswer: "assistant", options: ["assistance", "acceptance", "fortune"]},
{ Question: "kun", RightAnswer: "day", options: ["assistant", "assistance", "acceptance"]},
{ Question: "har kuni", RightAnswer: "daily", options: ["acceptable", "plastic", "fake"]},
{ Question: "kundalik", RightAnswer: "everyday", options: ["daily", "acceptable", "plastic"]},
{ Question: "iqtisod", RightAnswer: "economy", options: ["day", "assistant", "assistance"]},
{ Question: "iqtisodiy", RightAnswer: "economic", options: ["everyday", "daily", "acceptable"]},
{ Question: "tejamkor", RightAnswer: "economical", options: ["economic", "everyday", "daily"]},
{ Question: "iqtisod fanlari", RightAnswer: "economics", options: ["economy", "day", "assistant"]},
{ Question: "iqtisodchi", RightAnswer: "economist", options: ["economics", "economy", "day"]},
{ Question: "tugatmoq", RightAnswer: "end", options: ["assist", "accept", "make"]},
{ Question: "tugamaydigan", RightAnswer: "endless", options: ["economical", "economic", "everyday"]},
{ Question: "yakun", RightAnswer: "ending", options: ["economist", "economics", "economy"]},
{ Question: "cheksiz", RightAnswer: "unending", options: ["endless", "economical", "economic"]},
{ Question: "xarajat", RightAnswer: "expense", options: ["ending", "economist", "economics"]},
{ Question: "qimmat", RightAnswer: "expensive", options: ["unending", "endless", "economical"]},
{ Question: "xarajatlar", RightAnswer: "expenses", options: ["expense", "ending", "economist"]},
{ Question: "moliyaviy", RightAnswer: "finance", options: ["expenses", "expense", "ending"]},
{ Question: "moliyaviy", RightAnswer: "financial", options: ["expensive", "unending", "endless"]},
{ Question: "moliya", RightAnswer: "finances", options: ["finance", "expenses", "expense"]},
{ Question: "investitsiya qilmoq", RightAnswer: "invest", options: ["end", "assist", "accept"]},
{ Question: "sarmoya", RightAnswer: "investment", options: ["finances", "finance", "expenses"]},
{ Question: "sarmoyador", RightAnswer: "investor", options: ["investment", "finances", "finance"]},
{ Question: "hasham", RightAnswer: "luxury", options: ["investor", "investment", "finances"]},
{ Question: "hashamlar", RightAnswer: "luxuries", options: ["luxury", "investor", "investment"]},
{ Question: "hashamatli", RightAnswer: "luxurious", options: ["financial", "expensive", "unending"]},
{ Question: "to‘lamoq", RightAnswer: "pay", options: ["invest", "end", "assist"]},
{ Question: "to‘langan", RightAnswer: "paid", options: ["luxurious", "financial", "expensive"]},
{ Question: "to‘lov", RightAnswer: "payment", options: ["luxuries", "luxury", "investor"]},
{ Question: "to‘lanadigan", RightAnswer: "payable", options: ["paid", "luxurious", "financial"]},
{ Question: "kambag‘al", RightAnswer: "poor", options: ["payable", "paid", "luxurious"]},
{ Question: "nochor tarzda", RightAnswer: "poorly", options: ["acceptably", "greatly", "accurately"]},
{ Question: "qashshoqlik", RightAnswer: "poverty", options: ["payment", "luxuries", "luxury"]},
{ Question: "haqiqiy", RightAnswer: "real", options: ["poor", "payable", "paid"]},
{ Question: "haqiqiy emas", RightAnswer: "unreal", options: ["real", "poor", "payable"]},
{ Question: "haqiqat", RightAnswer: "reality", options: ["poverty", "payment", "luxuries"]},
{ Question: "tushunib yetish", RightAnswer: "realisation", options: ["reality", "poverty", "payment"]},
{ Question: "tushunmoq", RightAnswer: "realise", options: ["pay", "invest", "end"]},
{ Question: "real tarzda", RightAnswer: "realistic", options: ["unreal", "real", "poor"]},
{ Question: "boylik", RightAnswer: "wealth", options: ["realisation", "reality", "poverty"]},
{ Question: "boy", RightAnswer: "wealthy", options: ["realistic", "unreal", "real"]}],
"level 26" : [
{ Question: "zavqlanmoq", RightAnswer: "enjoy", options: ["realise", "pay", "invest"]},
{ Question: "hordiq chiqarishga sabab bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "entertain", options: ["enjoy", "realise", "pay"]},
{ Question: "sahna", RightAnswer: "scene", options: ["wealth", "realisation", "reality"]},
{ Question: "sahna dekoratsiyasi", RightAnswer: "scenery", options: ["scene", "wealth", "realisation"]},
{ Question: "sahna (joy)", RightAnswer: "stage", options: ["scenery", "scene", "wealth"]},
{ Question: "roman", RightAnswer: "novel", options: ["stage", "scenery", "scene"]},
{ Question: "badiiy adabiyot", RightAnswer: "fiction", options: ["novel", "stage", "scenery"]},
{ Question: "spektakl", RightAnswer: "play", options: ["fiction", "novel", "stage"]},
{ Question: "roll o‘ynamoq", RightAnswer: "act", options: ["entertain", "enjoy", "realise"]},
{ Question: "bosh rolni ijro etmoq", RightAnswer: "star", options: ["act", "entertain", "enjoy"]},
{ Question: "musiqa guruhi", RightAnswer: "band", options: ["play", "fiction", "novel"]},
{ Question: "orkestr", RightAnswer: "orchestra", options: ["band", "play", "fiction"]},
{ Question: "guruh", RightAnswer: "group", options: ["orchestra", "band", "play"]},
{ Question: "komik (hazilkash)", RightAnswer: "comic", options: ["group", "orchestra", "band"]},
{ Question: "multfilm", RightAnswer: "cartoon", options: ["comic", "group", "orchestra"]},
{ Question: "komik aktyor", RightAnswer: "comedian", options: ["cartoon", "comic", "group"]},
{ Question: "tinglov (san’atkor uchun)", RightAnswer: "audition", options: ["comedian", "cartoon", "comic"]},
{ Question: "mashq (general repititsiya)", RightAnswer: "rehearsal", options: ["audition", "comedian", "cartoon"]},
{ Question: "sharh", RightAnswer: "review", options: ["rehearsal", "audition", "comedian"]},
{ Question: "tanqid", RightAnswer: "criticism", options: ["review", "rehearsal", "audition"]},
{ Question: "tomosha qilmoq", RightAnswer: "watch", options: ["star", "act", "entertain"]},
{ Question: "ko‘rmoq", RightAnswer: "see", options: ["watch", "star", "act"]},
{ Question: "qaramoq", RightAnswer: "look", options: ["see", "watch", "star"]},
{ Question: "repetitsiya qilmoq", RightAnswer: "rehearse", options: ["look", "see", "watch"]},
{ Question: "mashq qilmoq", RightAnswer: "practise", options: ["rehearse", "look", "see"]},
{ Question: "chipta", RightAnswer: "ticket", options: ["criticism", "review", "rehearsal"]},
{ Question: "to‘lov", RightAnswer: "fee", options: ["ticket", "criticism", "review"]},
{ Question: "tinglamoq", RightAnswer: "listen", options: ["practise", "rehearse", "look"]},
{ Question: "eshitmoq", RightAnswer: "hear", options: ["listen", "practise", "rehearse"]},
{ Question: "qaytadan sodir bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "come (a)round", options: ["save up", "put by", "make up for"]},
{ Question: "ishonmoq", RightAnswer: "count on", options: ["come (a)round", "save up", "put by"]},
{ Question: "uxlab qolmoq", RightAnswer: "drop off", options: ["count on", "come (a)round", "save up"]},
{ Question: "ovozni bostirmoq", RightAnswer: "drown out", options: ["drop off", "count on", "come (a)round"]},
{ Question: "ishonib qolmoq (aldovga)", RightAnswer: "fall for", options: ["drown out", "drop off", "count on"]},
{ Question: "yaxshi munosabatda bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "get along (with)", options: ["fall for", "drown out", "drop off"]},
{ Question: "eslab qolmoq (qandaydir tarzda)", RightAnswer: "go down (as)", options: ["get along (with)", "fall for", "drown out"]},
{ Question: "yoqib qolmoq", RightAnswer: "grow on", options: ["go down (as)", "get along (with)", "fall for"]},
{ Question: "ko‘nglini qoldirmoq", RightAnswer: "let down", options: ["grow on", "go down (as)", "get along (with)"]},
{ Question: "nomini qo‘ymoq", RightAnswer: "name after", options: ["let down", "grow on", "go down (as)"]},
{ Question: "sahnaga qo‘ymoq (konsert, spektakl)", RightAnswer: "put on", options: ["name after", "let down", "grow on"]},
{ Question: "o‘zini ko‘rsatmoq", RightAnswer: "show off", options: ["put on", "name after", "let down"]},
{ Question: "kimningdir o‘xshash jihatini olmoq", RightAnswer: "take after", options: ["show off", "put on", "name after"]},
{ Question: "mashhur bo‘lib ketmoq", RightAnswer: "take off", options: ["take after", "show off", "put on"]},
{ Question: "kimnidir masxara qilmoq", RightAnswer: "make fun of sb", options: ["go shopping", "do the shopping", "save sth for later"]},
{ Question: "quvnoq vaqt o‘tkazmoq", RightAnswer: "have fun", options: ["make fun of sb", "go shopping", "do the shopping"]},
{ Question: "hazil aytmoq", RightAnswer: "tell a joke", options: ["have fun", "make fun of sb", "go shopping"]},
{ Question: "(biror narsa haqida) hazillashmoq", RightAnswer: "joke about st", options: ["tell a joke", "have fun", "make fun of sb"]},
{ Question: "kim bilan hazillashmoq", RightAnswer: "joke with sb", options: ["joke about st", "tell a joke", "have fun"]},
{ Question: "...ga kulmoq", RightAnswer: "laugh at/about", options: ["joke with sb", "joke about st", "tell a joke"]},
{ Question: "qattiq kulmoq", RightAnswer: "laugh out loud", options: ["laugh at/about", "joke with sb", "joke about st"]},
{ Question: "kuchli kulmoq", RightAnswer: "roar with laughter", options: ["laugh out loud", "laugh at/about", "joke with sb"]},
{ Question: "kulmoq", RightAnswer: "have a laugh", options: ["roar with laughter", "laugh out loud", "laugh at/about"]},
{ Question: "qatnashmoq", RightAnswer: "take part in st", options: ["have a laugh", "roar with laughter", "laugh out loud"]},
{ Question: "bir qismi bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "be a part of sth", options: ["take part in st", "have a laugh", "roar with laughter"]},
{ Question: "biror narsani bermoq / ajratmoq", RightAnswer: "part with sth", options: ["be a part of sth", "take part in st", "have a laugh"]},
{ Question: "rolda chiqmoq", RightAnswer: "have a part", options: ["part with sth", "be a part of sth", "take part in st"]},
{ Question: "rol o‘ynamoq", RightAnswer: "play a role", options: ["have a part", "part with sth", "be a part of sth"]},
{ Question: "bilan o‘ynamoq", RightAnswer: "play with", options: ["play a role", "have a part", "part with sth"]},
{ Question: "chalmoq / o‘ynamoq", RightAnswer: "play sth", options: ["play with", "play a role", "have a part"]},
{ Question: "roli bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "have a role to play", options: ["play sth", "play with", "play a role"]},
{ Question: "spektaklda chiqmoq", RightAnswer: "act in a play", options: ["have a role to play", "play sth", "play with"]},
{ Question: "spektakl tomosha qilmoq", RightAnswer: "watch a play", options: ["act in a play", "have a role to play", "play sth"]},
{ Question: "navbatga turmoq", RightAnswer: "join a queue", options: ["watch a play", "act in a play", "have a role to play"]},
{ Question: "navbatda", RightAnswer: "in a queue", options: ["at short notice", "at the very least", "at least"]},
{ Question: "navbatga turmoq", RightAnswer: "queue up", options: ["join a queue", "watch a play", "act in a play"]},
{ Question: "navbat kutmoq", RightAnswer: "stand/wait in a queue", options: ["queue up", "join a queue", "watch a play"]},
{ Question: "ko‘rsatmoq (spektakl, dastur)", RightAnswer: "put on a show", options: ["stand/wait in a queue", "queue up", "join a queue"]},
{ Question: "minnatdorchilik bildirmoq", RightAnswer: "show appreciation (for ...)", options: ["put on a show", "stand/wait in a queue", "queue up"]},
{ Question: "nimanidir ko‘rsatmoq", RightAnswer: "show sth to sb", options: ["show appreciation (for ...)", "put on a show", "stand/wait in a queue"]},
{ Question: "kimga nimanidir ko‘rsatmoq", RightAnswer: "show sb sth", options: ["show sth to sb", "show appreciation (for ...)", "put on a show"]},
{ Question: "namoyishda", RightAnswer: "on show", options: ["in a queue", "at short notice", "at the very least"]},
{ Question: "diqqat markazida bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "steal the show", options: ["under the weather", "in two minds about st", "the fact is "]},
{ Question: "televizion dastur", RightAnswer: "TV show", options: ["window shopping", "shopping centre", "a wage increase"]},
{ Question: "shou biznes", RightAnswer: "show business", options: ["TV show", "window shopping", "shopping centre"]},
{ Question: "chuqur ovozda", RightAnswer: "in a deep voice", options: ["on show", "in a queue", "at short notice"]},
{ Question: "yaxshi ovozga ega bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "have a good voice", options: ["show sb sth", "show sth to sb", "show appreciation (for ...)"]},
{ Question: "fikr bildirmoq", RightAnswer: "voice an opinion (about sth)", options: ["have a good voice", "show sb sth", "show sth to sb"]},
{ Question: "o‘zingizni uyda his qiling", RightAnswer: "make yourself at home", options: ["steal the show", "under the weather", "in two minds about st"]},
{ Question: "uyda bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "stay at home", options: ["voice an opinion (about sth)", "have a good voice", "show sb sth"]},
{ Question: "uyga bormoq", RightAnswer: "go home", options: ["stay at home", "voice an opinion (about sth)", "have a good voice"]},
{ Question: "uyga yo‘l olmoq", RightAnswer: "make your way home", options: ["go home", "stay at home", "voice an opinion (about sth)"]},
{ Question: "taassurot qoldirmoq", RightAnswer: "give sb the impression", options: ["make your way home", "go home", "stay at home"]},
{ Question: "taqlid qilmoq", RightAnswer: "do an impression of sb", options: ["give sb the impression", "make your way home", "go home"]},
{ Question: "taassurotga ega bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "have the impression", options: ["do an impression of sb", "give sb the impression", "make your way home"]},
{ Question: "taassurot qoldirmoq", RightAnswer: "make an impression (on sb)", options: ["have the impression", "do an impression of sb", "give sb the impression"]},
{ Question: "uzr so‘ramoq", RightAnswer: "apologise for st", options: ["spend sth", "save sb from sth...; save sth", "profit from st"]},
{ Question: "chetlab o‘tmoq", RightAnswer: "avoid", options: ["apologise for st", "spend sth", "save sb from sth...; save sth"]},
{ Question: "albatta qilmoq", RightAnswer: "bound to do", options: ["avoid", "apologise for st", "spend sth"]},
{ Question: "loyiq bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "deserve", options: ["bound to do", "avoid", "apologise for st"]},
{ Question: "zavqlanmoq", RightAnswer: "enjoy yourself; enjoy st", options: ["deserve", "bound to do", "avoid"]},
{ Question: "xursand bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "happy to do; happy for sb; happy about st", options: ["enjoy yourself; enjoy st", "deserve", "bound to do"]},
{ Question: "o‘rniga", RightAnswer: "instead of st", options: ["happy to do; happy for sb; happy about st", "enjoy yourself; enjoy st", "deserve"]},
{ Question: "yoqtirmoq", RightAnswer: "like st", options: ["instead of st", "happy to do; happy for sb; happy about st", "enjoy yourself; enjoy st"]},
{ Question: "va’da bermoq", RightAnswer: "promise to do; promise sb (sth); promise that", options: ["like st", "instead of st", "happy to do; happy for sb; happy about st"]},
{ Question: "isbotlamoq", RightAnswer: "prove to do; prove sth", options: ["promise to do; promise sb (sth); promise that", "like st", "instead of st"]},
{ Question: "aytmoq", RightAnswer: "say sth", options: ["prove to do; prove sth", "promise to do; promise sb (sth); promise that", "like st"]},
{ Question: "kerak bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "supposed to do", options: ["say sth", "prove to do; prove sth", "promise to do; promise sb (sth); promise that"]},
{ Question: "iste’dodli", RightAnswer: "talented at st", options: ["supposed to do", "say sth", "prove to do; prove sth"]},
{ Question: "harakat qilmoq", RightAnswer: "act", options: ["hear", "listen", "practise"]},
{ Question: "faol", RightAnswer: "active", options: ["wealthy", "realistic", "unreal"]},
{ Question: "aktyorlik", RightAnswer: "acting", options: ["fee", "ticket", "criticism"]},
{ Question: "aktyor, aktrisa", RightAnswer: "actor, actress", options: ["acting", "fee", "ticket"]},
{ Question: "harakat", RightAnswer: "action", options: ["actor, actress", "acting", "fee"]},
{ Question: "faoliyat", RightAnswer: "activity", options: ["action", "actor, actress", "acting"]},
{ Question: "ko‘nglini ko‘tarmoq", RightAnswer: "amuse", options: ["act", "hear", "listen"]},
{ Question: "kulgi tarzida", RightAnswer: "amusing", options: ["active", "wealthy", "realistic"]},
{ Question: "ko‘ngilocharlik", RightAnswer: "amusement", options: ["activity", "action", "actor, actress"]},
{ Question: "zeriktirmoq", RightAnswer: "bore", options: ["amuse", "act", "hear"]},
{ Question: "zerikarli", RightAnswer: "boring", options: ["amusing", "active", "wealthy"]},
{ Question: "zerikkan", RightAnswer: "bored", options: ["boring", "amusing", "active"]},
{ Question: "zerikish", RightAnswer: "boredom", options: ["amusement", "activity", "action"]},
{ Question: "suhbatlashmoq", RightAnswer: "converse", options: ["bore", "amuse", "act"]},
{ Question: "suhbat", RightAnswer: "conversation", options: ["boredom", "amusement", "activity"]},
{ Question: "hozirgi", RightAnswer: "current", options: ["bored", "boring", "amusing"]},
{ Question: "ayni paytda", RightAnswer: "currently", options: ["poorly", "acceptably", "greatly"]},
{ Question: "hordiq chiqarish", RightAnswer: "entertain", options: ["converse", "bore", "amuse"]},
{ Question: "ko‘ngilochar", RightAnswer: "entertaining", options: ["current", "bored", "boring"]},
{ Question: "ko‘ngilochar dastur", RightAnswer: "entertainment", options: ["conversation", "boredom", "amusement"]},
{ Question: "ko‘ngilochar dasturchi", RightAnswer: "entertainer", options: ["entertainment", "conversation", "boredom"]},
{ Question: "hayajonlantirmoq", RightAnswer: "excite", options: ["entertain", "converse", "bore"]},
{ Question: "hayajonli", RightAnswer: "exciting", options: ["entertaining", "current", "bored"]},
{ Question: "hayajon bilan", RightAnswer: "excited", options: ["exciting", "entertaining", "current"]},
{ Question: "hayajon", RightAnswer: "excitement", options: ["entertainer", "entertainment", "conversation"]},
{ Question: "shuhrat", RightAnswer: "fame", options: ["excitement", "entertainer", "entertainment"]},
{ Question: "mashhur", RightAnswer: "famous", options: ["excited", "exciting", "entertaining"]},
{ Question: "jalb qilmoq", RightAnswer: "involve", options: ["excite", "entertain", "converse"]},
{ Question: "jalb qilingan", RightAnswer: "involved", options: ["famous", "excited", "exciting"]},
{ Question: "jalb qilish", RightAnswer: "involvement", options: ["fame", "excitement", "entertainer"]},
{ Question: "chiqish qilmoq", RightAnswer: "perform", options: ["involve", "excite", "entertain"]},
{ Question: "chiqish qilayotgan", RightAnswer: "performing", options: ["involved", "famous", "excited"]},
{ Question: "chiqish", RightAnswer: "performance", options: ["involvement", "fame", "excitement"]},
{ Question: "ijrochi", RightAnswer: "performer", options: ["performance", "involvement", "fame"]},
{ Question: "mashhur", RightAnswer: "popular", options: ["performing", "involved", "famous"]},
{ Question: "mashhur emas", RightAnswer: "unpopular", options: ["popular", "performing", "involved"]},
{ Question: "ommaviy tarzda", RightAnswer: "popularly", options: ["currently", "poorly", "acceptably"]},
{ Question: "mashhurlik", RightAnswer: "popularity", options: ["performer", "performance", "involvement"]},
{ Question: "taklif qilmoq", RightAnswer: "suggest", options: ["perform", "involve", "excite"]},
{ Question: "taklif qilingan", RightAnswer: "suggested", options: ["unpopular", "popular", "performing"]},
{ Question: "ishorali", RightAnswer: "suggestive", options: ["suggested", "unpopular", "popular"]},
{ Question: "taklif", RightAnswer: "suggestion", options: ["popularity", "performer", "performance"]},
{ Question: "aytmoq", RightAnswer: "say", options: ["suggest", "perform", "involve"]},
{ Question: "maqol", RightAnswer: "saying", options: ["suggestion", "popularity", "performer"]},
{ Question: "farqlanmoq", RightAnswer: "vary", options: ["say", "suggest", "perform"]},
{ Question: "o‘zgaruvchan", RightAnswer: "variable", options: ["suggestive", "suggested", "unpopular"]},
{ Question: "o‘zgarmas tarzda", RightAnswer: "variably", options: ["popularly", "currently", "poorly"]},
{ Question: "turli", RightAnswer: "varying", options: ["variable", "suggestive", "suggested"]},
{ Question: "rang-barang", RightAnswer: "varied", options: ["varying", "variable", "suggestive"]},
{ Question: "turlicha", RightAnswer: "various", options: ["variably", "popularly", "currently"]},
{ Question: "o‘zgarish", RightAnswer: "variation", options: ["saying", "suggestion", "popularity"]},
{ Question: "turfa", RightAnswer: "variety", options: ["variation", "saying", "suggestion"]}],
"level 27" : [
{ Question: "kiyib olmoq", RightAnswer: "put on", options: ["take off", "take after", "show off"]},
{ Question: "kiyib yurmoq", RightAnswer: "wear", options: ["vary", "say", "suggest"]},
{ Question: "mato", RightAnswer: "cloth", options: ["variety", "variation", "saying"]},
{ Question: "kiyim", RightAnswer: "clothing", options: ["cloth", "variety", "variation"]},
{ Question: "qarash/ko‘rinish", RightAnswer: "look", options: ["clothing", "cloth", "variety"]},
{ Question: "tashqi ko‘rinish", RightAnswer: "appearance", options: ["look", "clothing", "cloth"]},
{ Question: "kostyum", RightAnswer: "costume", options: ["appearance", "look", "clothing"]},
{ Question: "kostyum", RightAnswer: "suit", options: ["costume", "appearance", "look"]},
{ Question: "bluzka", RightAnswer: "blouse", options: ["suit", "costume", "appearance"]},
{ Question: "ustki kiyim", RightAnswer: "top", options: ["blouse", "suit", "costume"]},
{ Question: "ta’minlamoq", RightAnswer: "supply", options: ["wear", "vary", "say"]},
{ Question: "ishlab chiqarmoq", RightAnswer: "produce", options: ["supply", "wear", "vary"]},
{ Question: "bo‘yoq", RightAnswer: "dye", options: ["top", "blouse", "suit"]},
{ Question: "bo‘yoq (rang)", RightAnswer: "paint", options: ["dye", "top", "blouse"]},
{ Question: "dizayn", RightAnswer: "design", options: ["paint", "dye", "top"]},
{ Question: "ishlab chiqarish", RightAnswer: "manufacture", options: ["design", "paint", "dye"]},
{ Question: "tez ko‘z tashlash", RightAnswer: "glimpse", options: ["manufacture", "design", "paint"]},
{ Question: "tez qarash", RightAnswer: "glance", options: ["glimpse", "manufacture", "design"]},
{ Question: "mos kelmoq", RightAnswer: "fit", options: ["produce", "supply", "wear"]},
{ Question: "mos tushmoq", RightAnswer: "suit", options: ["fit", "produce", "supply"]},
{ Question: "mos bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "match", options: ["suit", "fit", "produce"]},
{ Question: "hozirgi", RightAnswer: "current", options: ["varied", "varying", "variable"]},
{ Question: "yangi", RightAnswer: "new", options: ["current", "varied", "varying"]},
{ Question: "zamonaviy", RightAnswer: "modern", options: ["new", "current", "varied"]},
{ Question: "o‘rtacha", RightAnswer: "average", options: ["modern", "new", "current"]},
{ Question: "har kungi", RightAnswer: "everyday", options: ["average", "modern", "new"]},
{ Question: "urfga aylanish", RightAnswer: "catch on", options: ["put on", "take off", "take after"]},
{ Question: "yo‘q qilmoq", RightAnswer: "do away with", options: ["catch on", "put on", "take off"]},
{ Question: "chizmoq, tuzmoq (rejalar va h.k.)", RightAnswer: "draw up", options: ["do away with", "catch on", "put on"]},
{ Question: "dabdabali kiyinish", RightAnswer: "dress up", options: ["draw up", "do away with", "catch on"]},
{ Question: "ko‘rib chiqmoq, o‘ylab chiqmoq", RightAnswer: "go over", options: ["dress up", "draw up", "do away with"]},
{ Question: "ulg‘ayib chiqib ketmoq (kiyimdan)", RightAnswer: "grow out of", options: ["go over", "dress up", "draw up"]},
{ Question: "meros qilib qoldirmoq", RightAnswer: "hand down", options: ["grow out of", "go over", "dress up"]},
{ Question: "saf tortmoq", RightAnswer: "line up", options: ["hand down", "grow out of", "go over"]},
{ Question: "tezda kirib chiqmoq", RightAnswer: "pop in(to)", options: ["line up", "hand down", "grow out of"]},
{ Question: "joylarni ko‘rsatib chiqmoq", RightAnswer: "show (a)round", options: ["pop in(to)", "line up", "hand down"]},
{ Question: "yechmoq (kiyim)", RightAnswer: "take off", options: ["show (a)round", "pop in(to)", "line up"]},
{ Question: "yirtib tashlamoq", RightAnswer: "tear up", options: ["take off", "show (a)round", "pop in(to)"]},
{ Question: "kiyib ko‘rmoq", RightAnswer: "try on", options: ["tear up", "take off", "show (a)round"]},
{ Question: "eskirmoq, yaroqsiz holga kelmoq", RightAnswer: "wear out", options: ["try on", "tear up", "take off"]},
{ Question: "san’at ko‘rgazmasi", RightAnswer: "art exhibition", options: ["show business", "TV show", "window shopping"]},
{ Question: "san’at galereyasi", RightAnswer: "art gallery", options: ["art exhibition", "show business", "TV show"]},
{ Question: "san’at asari", RightAnswer: "work of art", options: ["art gallery", "art exhibition", "show business"]},
{ Question: "kiyim kiyib olmoq", RightAnswer: "put on clothes", options: ["make an impression (on sb)", "have the impression", "do an impression of sb"]},
{ Question: "kiyim yechmoq", RightAnswer: "take off clothes", options: ["put on clothes", "make an impression (on sb)", "have the impression"]},
{ Question: "kiyim kiyib ko‘rmoq", RightAnswer: "try on clothes", options: ["take off clothes", "put on clothes", "make an impression (on sb)"]},
{ Question: "kiyim kiyib yurmoq", RightAnswer: "wear clothes", options: ["try on clothes", "take off clothes", "put on clothes"]},
{ Question: "modada", RightAnswer: "in fashion", options: ["in a deep voice", "on show", "in a queue"]},
{ Question: "modadan chiqqan", RightAnswer: "out of fashion", options: ["in fashion", "in a deep voice", "on show"]},
{ Question: "...ning birikmasi", RightAnswer: "combination of", options: ["work of art", "art gallery", "art exhibition"]},
{ Question: "kimnidir (biror narsasi uchun) maqtamoq", RightAnswer: "compliment sb on sth", options: ["wear clothes", "try on clothes", "take off clothes"]},
{ Question: "namuna qilib olmoq", RightAnswer: "follow an example", options: ["compliment sb on sth", "wear clothes", "try on clothes"]},
{ Question: "namuna ko‘rsatmoq", RightAnswer: "set an example", options: ["follow an example", "compliment sb on sth", "wear clothes"]},
{ Question: "namunasi bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "be an example", options: ["set an example", "follow an example", "compliment sb on sth"]},
{ Question: "kimdan namuna olmoq", RightAnswer: "take an example (from sb)", options: ["be an example", "set an example", "follow an example"]},
{ Question: "modada", RightAnswer: "in fashion", options: ["out of fashion", "in fashion", "in a deep voice"]},
{ Question: "modadan chiqmoq", RightAnswer: "go out of fashion", options: ["take an example (from sb)", "be an example", "set an example"]},
{ Question: "modani kuzatmoq", RightAnswer: "follow fashion", options: ["go out of fashion", "take an example (from sb)", "be an example"]},
{ Question: "moda modeli", RightAnswer: "fashion model", options: ["combination of", "work of art", "art gallery"]},
{ Question: "moda namoyishi", RightAnswer: "fashion show", options: ["fashion model", "combination of", "work of art"]},
{ Question: "soch oldirmoq", RightAnswer: "have a haircut", options: ["follow fashion", "go out of fashion", "take an example (from sb)"]},
{ Question: "sochni tartibga keltirtirmoq", RightAnswer: "have your hair done", options: ["have a haircut", "follow fashion", "go out of fashion"]},
{ Question: "yangi soch turmagi", RightAnswer: "have a new hairstyle", options: ["have your hair done", "have a haircut", "follow fashion"]},
{ Question: "pardoz qilmoq", RightAnswer: "put on make-up", options: ["have a new hairstyle", "have your hair done", "have a haircut"]},
{ Question: "pardozni artib tashlamoq", RightAnswer: "take off make-up", options: ["put on make-up", "have a new hairstyle", "have your hair done"]},
{ Question: "pardoz bilan yurmoq", RightAnswer: "wear make-up", options: ["take off make-up", "put on make-up", "have a new hairstyle"]},
{ Question: "katak naqsh", RightAnswer: "a checked pattern", options: ["fashion show", "fashion model", "combination of"]},
{ Question: "uslubga ega bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "have style", options: ["wear make-up", "take off make-up", "put on make-up"]},
{ Question: "uslubda", RightAnswer: "in style", options: ["in fashion", "out of fashion", "in fashion"]},
{ Question: "uslubdan chiqqan", RightAnswer: "out of style", options: ["in style", "in fashion", "out of fashion"]},
{ Question: "...dagi yo‘nalish", RightAnswer: "a trend in sth", options: ["a checked pattern", "fashion show", "fashion model"]},
{ Question: "yo‘nalishga ergashmoq", RightAnswer: "follow a trend", options: ["have style", "wear make-up", "take off make-up"]},
{ Question: "yo‘nalish belgilamoq", RightAnswer: "set a trend", options: ["follow a trend", "have style", "wear make-up"]},
{ Question: "yaxshi didga ega bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "have good taste", options: ["set a trend", "follow a trend", "have style"]},
{ Question: "yaxshi did bilan", RightAnswer: "in good taste", options: ["out of style", "in style", "in fashion"]},
{ Question: "maslahat bermoq", RightAnswer: "advise sb to do", options: ["talented at st", "supposed to do", "say sth"]},
{ Question: "xavotirda bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "anxious about sth...; anxious to do", options: ["advise sb to do", "talented at st", "supposed to do"]},
{ Question: "tanqid qilmoq", RightAnswer: "criticise sb", options: ["anxious about sth...; anxious to do", "advise sb to do", "advise against st", "talented at st"]},
{ Question: "talab qilmoq", RightAnswer: "insist on sth...; insist that", options: ["criticise sb", "anxious about sth...; anxious to do", "advise sb to do"]},
{ Question: "ko‘p miqdorda", RightAnswer: "plenty of sth; plenty more sth", options: ["insist on sth...; insist that", "criticise sb", "anxious about sth...; anxious to do"]},
{ Question: "tayyorlamoq", RightAnswer: "prepare for sth; prepare to do", options: ["plenty of sth; plenty more sth", "insist on sth...; insist that", "criticise sb"]},
{ Question: "faxr qilmoq", RightAnswer: "proud; proud to do", options: ["prepare for sth; prepare to do", "plenty of sth; plenty more sth", "insist on sth...; insist that"]},
{ Question: "tilga olmoq", RightAnswer: "refer to sth; refer sb to sth", options: ["proud; proud to do", "prepare for sth; prepare to do", "plenty of sth; plenty more sth"]},
{ Question: "ko‘rinmoq", RightAnswer: "seem to be; it seems that", options: ["refer to sth; refer sb to sth", "proud; proud to do", "prepare for sth; prepare to do"]},
{ Question: "tikilib qaramoq", RightAnswer: "stare at", options: ["seem to be; it seems that", "refer to sth; refer sb to sth", "proud; proud to do"]},
{ Question: "foydalanmoq", RightAnswer: "use sth; use sth to do", options: ["stare at", "seem to be; it seems that", "refer to sth; refer sb to sth"]},
{ Question: "foydali", RightAnswer: "useful for sth...; useful to sb", options: ["use sth; use sth to do", "stare at", "seem to be; it seems that"]},
{ Question: "reklama qilmoq", RightAnswer: "advertise", options: ["match", "suit", "fit"]},
{ Question: "reklama", RightAnswer: "ad(vert)", options: ["glance", "glimpse", "manufacture"]},
{ Question: "reklama qilish", RightAnswer: "advertising", options: ["ad(vert)", "glance", "glimpse"]},
{ Question: "reklama beruvchi", RightAnswer: "advertiser", options: ["advertising", "ad(vert)", "glance"]},
{ Question: "jalb qilmoq", RightAnswer: "attract", options: ["advertise", "match", "suit"]},
{ Question: "jozibali", RightAnswer: "attractive", options: ["everyday", "average", "modern"]},
{ Question: "jalb qilish", RightAnswer: "attraction", options: ["advertiser", "advertising", "ad(vert)"]},
{ Question: "go‘zallik", RightAnswer: "beauty", options: ["attraction", "advertiser", "advertising"]},
{ Question: "chiroyli", RightAnswer: "beautiful", options: ["attractive", "everyday", "average"]},
{ Question: "qaror qilmoq", RightAnswer: "decide", options: ["attract", "advertise", "match"]},
{ Question: "qaror", RightAnswer: "decision", options: ["beauty", "attraction", "advertiser"]},
{ Question: "qat’iy", RightAnswer: "decisive", options: ["beautiful", "attractive", "everyday"]},
{ Question: "qaror qilinmagan", RightAnswer: "undecided", options: ["decisive", "beautiful", "attractive"]},
{ Question: "xohlamoq", RightAnswer: "desire", options: ["decide", "attract", "advertise"]},
{ Question: "istalgan", RightAnswer: "desirable", options: ["undecided", "decisive", "beautiful"]},
{ Question: "hayajonlanmoq", RightAnswer: "enthuse", options: ["desire", "decide", "attract"]},
{ Question: "ishtiyoqmand", RightAnswer: "enthusiastic", options: ["desirable", "undecided", "decisive"]},
{ Question: "ishtiyoq", RightAnswer: "enthusiasm", options: ["decision", "beauty", "attraction"]},
{ Question: "ishqiboz", RightAnswer: "enthusiast", options: ["enthusiasm", "decision", "beauty"]},
{ Question: "kutmoq", RightAnswer: "expect", options: ["enthuse", "desire", "decide"]},
{ Question: "kutilgan", RightAnswer: "expected", options: ["enthusiastic", "desirable", "undecided"]},
{ Question: "kutish", RightAnswer: "expectation", options: ["enthusiast", "enthusiasm", "decision"]},
{ Question: "umid", RightAnswer: "expectancy", options: ["expectation", "enthusiast", "enthusiasm"]},
{ Question: "moda", RightAnswer: "fashion", options: ["expectancy", "expectation", "enthusiast"]},
{ Question: "urfga mos", RightAnswer: "fashionable", options: ["expected", "enthusiastic", "desirable"]},
{ Question: "moda bo‘yicha", RightAnswer: "fashionably", options: ["various", "variably", "popularly"]},
{ Question: "yoqtirmoq", RightAnswer: "like", options: ["expect", "enthuse", "desire"]},
{ Question: "o‘xshash", RightAnswer: "alike", options: ["fashionable", "expected", "enthusiastic"]},
{ Question: "yoqtirmaslik", RightAnswer: "dislike", options: ["like", "expect", "enthuse"]},
{ Question: "o‘xshamaydigan", RightAnswer: "unlike", options: ["alike", "fashionable", "expected"]},
{ Question: "o‘xshashlik", RightAnswer: "likeness", options: ["fashion", "expectancy", "expectation"]},
{ Question: "yoqimli", RightAnswer: "likeable", options: ["unlike", "alike", "fashionable"]},
{ Question: "qiziqish", RightAnswer: "liking", options: ["likeness", "fashion", "expectancy"]},
{ Question: "ishlab chiqarmoq", RightAnswer: "produce", options: ["dislike", "like", "expect"]},
{ Question: "mahsulot", RightAnswer: "product", options: ["liking", "likeness", "fashion"]},
{ Question: "ishlab chiqaruvchi", RightAnswer: "producer", options: ["product", "liking", "likeness"]},
{ Question: "ishlab chiqarish", RightAnswer: "production", options: ["producer", "product", "liking"]},
{ Question: "samarali", RightAnswer: "productive", options: ["likeable", "unlike", "alike"]},
{ Question: "o‘xshash", RightAnswer: "similar", options: ["productive", "likeable", "unlike"]},
{ Question: "o‘xshamagan", RightAnswer: "dissimilar", options: ["similar", "productive", "likeable"]},
{ Question: "o‘xshashlik", RightAnswer: "similarity", options: ["production", "producer", "product"]},
{ Question: "uslub", RightAnswer: "style", options: ["similarity", "production", "producer"]},
{ Question: "zamonaviy", RightAnswer: "stylish", options: ["dissimilar", "similar", "productive"]},
{ Question: "uslubshunos", RightAnswer: "stylist", options: ["style", "similarity", "production"]},
{ Question: "zamonaviylik", RightAnswer: "stylishness", options: ["stylist", "style", "similarity"]},
{ Question: "muvaffaqiyat qozonmoq", RightAnswer: "succeed", options: ["produce", "dislike", "like"]},
{ Question: "muvaffaqiyat", RightAnswer: "success", options: ["stylishness", "stylist", "style"]},
{ Question: "muvaffaqiyatli", RightAnswer: "successful", options: ["stylish", "dissimilar", "similar"]},
{ Question: "foydalanmoq", RightAnswer: "use", options: ["succeed", "produce", "dislike"]},
{ Question: "foydalanish", RightAnswer: "usage", options: ["success", "stylishness", "stylist"]},
{ Question: "foydali", RightAnswer: "useful", options: ["successful", "stylish", "dissimilar"]},
{ Question: "foydasiz", RightAnswer: "useless", options: ["fashionably", "various", "variably"]},
{ Question: "foydalanuvchi", RightAnswer: "user", options: ["usage", "success", "stylishness"]},
{ Question: "foydalanishga yaroqli", RightAnswer: "usable", options: ["useful", "successful", "stylish"]}],
"level 28" : [
{ Question: "ish beruvchi", RightAnswer: "employer", options: ["user", "usage", "success"]},
{ Question: "ishchi", RightAnswer: "employee", options: ["employer", "user", "usage"]},
{ Question: "xodimlar", RightAnswer: "staff", options: ["a trend in sth", "a checked pattern", "fashion show"]},
{ Question: "ish haqi (kunlik/haftalik)", RightAnswer: "wage", options: ["employee", "employer", "user"]},
{ Question: "maosh (oylik)", RightAnswer: "salary", options: ["wage", "employee", "employer"]},
{ Question: "haq to‘lash", RightAnswer: "pay", options: ["hurt", "murder", "blame"]},
{ Question: "qo‘shimcha ish vaqti", RightAnswer: "overtime", options: ["salary", "wage", "employee"]},
{ Question: "lavozim ko‘tarilishi", RightAnswer: "promotion", options: ["overtime", "salary", "wage"]},
{ Question: "nafaqa", RightAnswer: "pension", options: ["promotion", "overtime", "salary"]},
{ Question: "ish", RightAnswer: "job", options: ["pension", "promotion", "overtime"]},
{ Question: "ish (umuman)", RightAnswer: "work", options: ["pay", "hurt", "murder"]},
{ Question: "martaba", RightAnswer: "career", options: ["job", "pension", "promotion"]},
{ Question: "qatnab ishlash", RightAnswer: "commute", options: ["use", "succeed", "produce"]},
{ Question: "yetkazib bermoq", RightAnswer: "deliver", options: ["commute", "use", "succeed"]},
{ Question: "kompaniya", RightAnswer: "company", options: ["career", "job", "pension"]},
{ Question: "firma", RightAnswer: "firm", options: ["company", "career", "job"]},
{ Question: "biznes", RightAnswer: "business", options: ["firm", "company", "career"]},
{ Question: "ishlab topmoq", RightAnswer: "earn", options: ["deliver", "commute", "use"]},
{ Question: "yutmoq", RightAnswer: "win", options: ["earn", "deliver", "commute"]},
{ Question: "erishmoq", RightAnswer: "gain", options: ["win", "earn", "deliver"]},
{ Question: "nafaqaga chiqmoq", RightAnswer: "retire", options: ["gain", "win", "earn"]},
{ Question: "iste’foga chiqmoq", RightAnswer: "resign", options: ["retire", "gain", "win"]},
{ Question: "kasaba uyushmasi", RightAnswer: "union", options: ["business", "firm", "company"]},
{ Question: "xayriya", RightAnswer: "charity", options: ["union", "business", "firm"]},
{ Question: "oshirish", RightAnswer: "raise", options: ["work", "pay", "hurt"]},
{ Question: "ko‘tarilish", RightAnswer: "rise", options: ["raise", "work", "pay"]},
{ Question: "ishdan haydamoq", RightAnswer: "fire", options: ["resign", "retire", "gain"]},
{ Question: "ishdan bo‘shatmoq", RightAnswer: "sack", options: ["fire", "resign", "retire"]},
{ Question: "qisqartirish sababli ishdan bo‘shatmoq", RightAnswer: "make redundant", options: ["turn down", "take over", "take on"]},
{ Question: "va’dasidan qaytmoq", RightAnswer: "back out", options: ["wear out", "try on", "tear up"]},
{ Question: "chiqarib sotuvga qo‘ymoq", RightAnswer: "bring out", options: ["back out", "wear out", "try on"]},
{ Question: "yopmoq (kompaniya)", RightAnswer: "close down", options: ["bring out", "back out", "wear out"]},
{ Question: "oxirigacha davom ettirmoq", RightAnswer: "see through (to)", options: ["close down", "bring out", "back out"]},
{ Question: "g‘amxo‘rlik qilmoq", RightAnswer: "see to", options: ["see through (to)", "close down", "bring out"]},
{ Question: "qat’iyat bilan boshlamoq", RightAnswer: "set to", options: ["see to", "see through (to)", "close down"]},
{ Question: "maqsad yo‘lida ish boshlamoq", RightAnswer: "set out", options: ["set to", "see to", "see through (to)"]},
{ Question: "(biznes, tashkilot) boshlamoq", RightAnswer: "set up", options: ["set out", "set to", "see to"]},
{ Question: "tezligini kamaytirmoq", RightAnswer: "slow down", options: ["set up", "set out", "set to"]},
{ Question: "tezlashtirmoq", RightAnswer: "speed up", options: ["slow down", "set up", "set out"]},
{ Question: "vaqtincha o‘rnini bosmoq", RightAnswer: "stand in for", options: ["speed up", "slow down", "set up"]},
{ Question: "ish boshlamoq/qabul qilmoq", RightAnswer: "take on", options: ["stand in for", "speed up", "slow down"]},
{ Question: "boshqaruvni qo‘lga olmoq", RightAnswer: "take over", options: ["take on", "stand in for", "speed up"]},
{ Question: "rad qilmoq", RightAnswer: "turn down", options: ["take over", "take on", "stand in for"]},
{ Question: "kelishuvga erishmoq", RightAnswer: "come to/reach (an) agreement (on/about sth)", options: ["have good taste", "set a trend", "follow a trend"]},
{ Question: "kelishuvga ko‘ra", RightAnswer: "in agreement (on/about sth)", options: ["in good taste", "out of style", "in style"]},
{ Question: "kelishuv tuzmoq", RightAnswer: "make an arrangement", options: ["come to/reach (an) agreement (on/about sth)", "have good taste", "set a trend"]},
{ Question: "kelishuvga ega bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "have an arrangement", options: ["make an arrangement", "come to/reach (an) agreement (on/about sth)", "have good taste"]},
{ Question: "(biror narsa uchun) kelishuv", RightAnswer: "arrangement for sth", options: ["staff", "a trend in sth", "a checked pattern"]},
{ Question: "kim bilan kelishilgan", RightAnswer: "in agreement with sb", options: ["in agreement (on/about sth)", "in good taste", "out of style"]},
{ Question: "(kim bilandir) ish qilmoq", RightAnswer: "do business", options: ["have an arrangement", "make an arrangement", "come to/reach (an) agreement (on/about sth)"]},
{ Question: "ishda", RightAnswer: "in business", options: ["in agreement with sb", "in agreement (on/about sth)", "in good taste"]},
{ Question: "xizmat safari bilan bormoq", RightAnswer: "go somewhere on business", options: ["do business", "have an arrangement", "make an arrangement"]},
{ Question: "xizmat safari", RightAnswer: "business trip", options: ["arrangement for sth", "staff", "a trend in sth"]},
{ Question: "kichik biznes", RightAnswer: "small business", options: ["business trip", "arrangement for sth", "staff"]},
{ Question: "yirik biznes", RightAnswer: "big business", options: ["small business", "business trip", "arrangement for sth"]},
{ Question: "shikoyat qilmoq", RightAnswer: "make a complaint", options: ["go somewhere on business", "do business", "have an arrangement"]},
{ Question: "shikoyat xati", RightAnswer: "letter of complaint", options: ["big business", "small business", "business trip"]},
{ Question: "dam olish kuni olmoq", RightAnswer: "take a day off", options: ["make a complaint", "go somewhere on business", "do business"]},
{ Question: "asosiy ish", RightAnswer: "day job", options: ["letter of complaint", "big business", "small business"]},
{ Question: "kunduzgi smena", RightAnswer: "day shift", options: ["day job", "letter of complaint", "big business"]},
{ Question: "qaror qabul qilmoq", RightAnswer: "make a decision ", options: ["take a day off", "make a complaint", "go somewhere on business"]},
{ Question: "qaror qabul qilmoq", RightAnswer: "reach a decision (about sth)", options: ["make a decision ", "take a day off", "make a complaint"]},
{ Question: "burchga ega bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "have a duty", options: ["reach a decision (about sth)", "make a decision ", "take a day off"]},
{ Question: "burch hissi", RightAnswer: "a sense of duty", options: ["day shift", "day job", "letter of complaint"]},
{ Question: "navbatchilikda", RightAnswer: "on duty", options: ["in business", "in agreement with sb", "in agreement (on/about sth)"]},
{ Question: "harakat qilmoq", RightAnswer: "make an effort", options: ["have a duty", "reach a decision (about sth)", "make a decision "]},
{ Question: "(biror ishga) kuch sarflash", RightAnswer: "put effort into st", options: ["make an effort", "have a duty", "reach a decision (about sth)"]},
{ Question: "tajribaga ega bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "gain experience", options: ["put effort into st", "make an effort", "have a duty"]},
{ Question: "(biror narsa/ishda) tajribali ", RightAnswer: "experienced in st", options: ["short of money", "disappointed by ", "out of control"]},
{ Question: "qiziqish bildirmoq", RightAnswer: "take an interest in st", options: ["gain experience", "put effort into st", "make an effort"]},
{ Question: "qilish sizga foydali ", RightAnswer: "in your interest to do", options: ["last but not least", "enough is enough", "at first sight"]},
{ Question: "ish qilmoq", RightAnswer: "do a job", options: ["take an interest in st", "gain experience", "put effort into st"]},
{ Question: "ishga ega bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "have a job", options: ["do a job", "take an interest in st", "gain experience"]},
{ Question: "ishga murojaat qilmoq", RightAnswer: "apply for a job", options: ["have a job", "do a job", "take an interest in st"]},
{ Question: "ishga joylashmoq", RightAnswer: "take a job", options: ["apply for a job", "have a job", "do a job"]},
{ Question: "ish suhbat", RightAnswer: "job interview", options: ["a sense of duty", "day shift", "day job"]},
{ Question: "ish taklifi", RightAnswer: "job offer", options: ["job interview", "a sense of duty", "day shift"]},
{ Question: "ish e’loni", RightAnswer: "job advert", options: ["job offer", "job interview", "a sense of duty"]},
{ Question: "dam olish kuni olmoq", RightAnswer: "take a day off", options: ["take a job", "apply for a job", "have a job"]},
{ Question: "(kimga) to‘lov qilmoq", RightAnswer: "pay sb", options: ["take a day off", "take a job", "apply for a job"]},
{ Question: "(kimga) maqtov aytmoq", RightAnswer: "pay sb a compliment", options: ["pay sb", "take a day off", "take a job"]},
{ Question: "yaxshi maosh olish", RightAnswer: "get good pay", options: ["pay sb a compliment", "pay sb", "take a day off"]},
{ Question: "javobgarlikni zimmasigaolmoq", RightAnswer: "take responsibility", options: ["get good pay", "pay sb a compliment", "pay sb"]},
{ Question: "ish qilmoq", RightAnswer: "do some work", options: ["take responsibility", "get good pay", "pay sb a compliment"]},
{ Question: "bajaradigan ish bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "have work to do", options: ["do some work", "take responsibility", "get good pay"]},
{ Question: "mehnat qilmoq", RightAnswer: "work hard", options: ["have work to do", "do some work", "take responsibility"]},
{ Question: "ishga sho‘ng‘igan ", RightAnswer: "hard at work", options: ["experienced in st", "short of money", "disappointed by "]},
{ Question: "ishsiz", RightAnswer: "out of work", options: ["on duty", "in business", "in agreement with sb"]},
{ Question: "ish joyi", RightAnswer: "place of work", options: ["job advert", "job offer", "job interview"]},
{ Question: "uydan ishlamoq", RightAnswer: "work from home", options: ["work hard", "have work to do", "do some work"]},
{ Question: "...dan yo‘q bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "absent from sth", options: ["useful for sth...; useful to sb", "use sth; use sth to do", "stare at"]},
{ Question: "...ga hujjat topshirmoq", RightAnswer: "apply for sth", options: ["absent from sth", "useful for sth...; useful to sb", "use sth; use sth to do"]},
{ Question: "...ga biriktirmoq", RightAnswer: "attach sth to sth", options: ["apply for sth", "absent from sth", "useful for sth...; useful to sb"]},
{ Question: "boshlamoq", RightAnswer: "begin doing sth", options: ["attach sth to sth", "apply for sth", "absent from sth"]},
{ Question: "...ga tayanmoq", RightAnswer: "depend on", options: ["begin doing/to do sth", "attach sth to sth", "apply for sth"]},
{ Question: "...da tajribali bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "experienced in", options: ["depend on", "begin doing/to do sth", "attach sth to sth"]},
{ Question: "foydali bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "good for sb", options: ["experienced in", "depend on", "begin doing/to do sth"]},
{ Question: "malaka olmoq", RightAnswer: "qualify as sth", options: ["good for sb", "experienced in", "depend on"]},
{ Question: "mas’ul bo‘lmoq", RightAnswer: "responsible for st", options: ["qualify as sth", "good for sb", "experienced in"]},
{ Question: "ixtisoslashmoq", RightAnswer: "specialise in st", options: ["responsible for st", "qualify as sth", "good for sb"]},
{ Question: "tayyorlanmoq", RightAnswer: "train to do", options: ["specialise in st", "responsible for st", "qualify as sth"]},
{ Question: "... sifatida ishlamoq", RightAnswer: "work as", options: ["train to do", "specialise in st", "responsible for st"]},
{ Question: "qo‘shmoq", RightAnswer: "add", options: ["sack", "fire", "resign"]},
{ Question: "qo‘shish", RightAnswer: "addition", options: ["charity", "union", "business"]},
{ Question: "qo‘shimcha", RightAnswer: "additional", options: ["usable", "useful", "successful"]},
{ Question: "hujjat topshirmoq", RightAnswer: "apply", options: ["add", "sack", "fire"]},
{ Question: "qo‘llaniladigan", RightAnswer: "applicable", options: ["additional", "usable", "useful"]},
{ Question: "amaliy", RightAnswer: "applied", options: ["applicable", "additional", "usable"]},
{ Question: "ariza topshiruvchi", RightAnswer: "applicant", options: ["addition", "charity", "union"]},
{ Question: "ariza", RightAnswer: "application", options: ["applicant", "addition", "charity"]},
{ Question: "savdo", RightAnswer: "commerce", options: ["application", "applicant", "addition"]},
{ Question: "tijoriy", RightAnswer: "commercial", options: ["applied", "applicable", "additional"]},
{ Question: "bag‘ishlamoq", RightAnswer: "dedicate", options: ["apply", "add", "sack"]},
{ Question: "sadoqatli", RightAnswer: "dedicated", options: ["commercial", "applied", "applicable"]},
{ Question: "bag‘ishlash", RightAnswer: "dedication", options: ["commerce", "application", "applicant"]},
{ Question: "ta’sir", RightAnswer: "effect", options: ["dedication", "commerce", "application"]},
{ Question: "samarali", RightAnswer: "effective", options: ["dedicated", "commercial", "applied"]},
{ Question: "ishga olmoq", RightAnswer: "employ", options: ["dedicate", "apply", "add"]},
{ Question: "ishli", RightAnswer: "employed", options: ["effective", "dedicated", "commercial"]},
{ Question: "ishga yaroqli", RightAnswer: "employable", options: ["employed", "effective", "dedicated"]},
{ Question: "ishga joylashish", RightAnswer: "employment", options: ["effect", "dedication", "commerce"]},
{ Question: "ish beruvchi", RightAnswer: "employer", options: ["employment", "effect", "dedication"]},
{ Question: "ishchi", RightAnswer: "employee", options: ["employer", "employment", "effect"]},
{ Question: "yordam", RightAnswer: "help", options: ["employee", "employer", "employment"]},
{ Question: "foydali", RightAnswer: "helpful", options: ["employable", "employed", "effective"]},
{ Question: "ojiz", RightAnswer: "helpless", options: ["useless", "fashionably", "various"]},
{ Question: "porsiya (ovqat)", RightAnswer: "helping", options: ["help", "employee", "employer"]},
{ Question: "yordamchi", RightAnswer: "helper", options: ["helping", "help", "employee"]},
{ Question: "sanoat", RightAnswer: "industry", options: ["helper", "helping", "help"]},
{ Question: "sanoatga oid", RightAnswer: "industrial", options: ["helpful", "employable", "employed"]},
{ Question: "mehnatsevar", RightAnswer: "industrious", options: ["industrial", "helpful", "employable"]},
{ Question: "mashina", RightAnswer: "machine", options: ["industry", "helper", "helping"]},
{ Question: "mexanizm", RightAnswer: "machinery", options: ["machine", "industry", "helper"]},
{ Question: "boshqarmoq", RightAnswer: "manage", options: ["employ", "dedicate", "apply"]},
{ Question: "boshqaruv", RightAnswer: "managing", options: ["machinery", "machine", "industry"]},
{ Question: "boshqaruv", RightAnswer: "management", options: ["managing", "machinery", "machine"]},
{ Question: "boshqaruvchi", RightAnswer: "manager", options: ["management", "managing", "machinery"]},
{ Question: "uchrashmoq", RightAnswer: "meet", options: ["manage", "employ", "dedicate"]},
{ Question: "uchrashuv", RightAnswer: "meeting", options: ["manager", "management", "managing"]},
{ Question: "kasb", RightAnswer: "profession", options: ["meeting", "manager", "management"]},
{ Question: "professional", RightAnswer: "professional", options: ["industrious", "industrial", "helpful"]},
{ Question: "malaka olmoq", RightAnswer: "qualify", options: ["meet", "manage", "employ"]},
{ Question: "malakali", RightAnswer: "qualified", options: ["professional", "industrious", "industrial"]},
{ Question: "malaka olish", RightAnswer: "qualifying", options: ["profession", "meeting", "manager"]},
{ Question: "malaka", RightAnswer: "qualification", options: ["qualifying", "profession", "meeting"]},
{ Question: "mas’ul", RightAnswer: "responsible", options: ["qualified", "professional", "industrious"]},
{ Question: "mas’uliyatsiz", RightAnswer: "irresponsible", options: ["responsible", "qualified", "professional"]},
{ Question: "mas’uliyat bilan", RightAnswer: "responsibly", options: ["helpless", "useless", "fashionably"]},
{ Question: "mas’uliyat", RightAnswer: "responsibility", options: ["qualification", "qualifying", "profession"]},
{ Question: "nazorat qilmoq", RightAnswer: "supervise", options: ["qualify", "meet", "manage"]},
{ Question: "nazorat", RightAnswer: "supervision", options: ["responsibility", "qualification", "qualifying"]},
{ Question: "rahbar/nazoratchi", RightAnswer: "supervisor", options: ["supervision", "responsibility", "qualification"]},
{ Question: "ish", RightAnswer: "work", options: ["supervisor", "supervision", "responsibility"]},
{ Question: "yaroqli", RightAnswer: "workable", options: ["irresponsible", "responsible", "qualified"]},
{ Question: "ishchi", RightAnswer: "worker", options: ["work", "supervisor", "supervision"]},
{ Question: "zavod/fabrika", RightAnswer: "works", options: ["worker", "work", "supervisor"]}]
}
    
